Work life balance is your problem. It
工作与生活平衡是你的问题。它
isn't the employer's responsibility.
这不是雇主的责任。
Look, I have four kids and I had to
你看，我有四个孩子，我不得不……
figure out how I would think about my
弄清楚我会如何看待我的
own ambition balanced with my parenting.
个人抱负与育儿责任之间需要取得平衡。
That's the truth. And we have to have a
这是事实。我们必须有一个
level of honesty about what it takes to
对所需条件的诚实程度
be really successful. But is it possible
取得真正的成功。但这有可能吗？
to be number one but still have all of
成为第一，但仍然拥有所有的一切
my evenings and weekends? No, you're
我的晚上和周末？不，你是
not. No, no. If if it's possible, tell
不是。不，不。如果可能的话，请告诉我
me who she is and I'll show you a liar.
告诉我她是谁，我就让你看清谁是骗子。
Emma Greed has rewritten the fashion
艾玛·格里德重新定义了时尚
business rule book. As the co-founder of
商业规则手册。作为联合创始人
multi-billion dollar brands like Good
像Good这样的数十亿美元品牌
American and Skims with the Kardashians,
美国和Skims与卡戴珊家族，
she's now revealing the secrets behind
她现在要揭开背后的秘密
her unstoppable success. You know this
她势不可挡的成功。你知道这一点
Emma here? Where'd you get these photos?
艾玛在这里吗？这些照片你是从哪里弄来的？
How old are you here? 15. And how do you
你多大了？ 15. 你如何
feel about her? I feel like this person
对她有什么感觉？我感觉自己像这个人
was like dying to escape her
就像死去一样想要逃离她。
circumstances. I was raised by a single
情况。我由一位单身母亲抚养长大。
mom, one of four girls, and I had a very
妈妈，四个女儿中的一个，我和她非常
big hand in raising them to help my mom
在抚养他们长大成人方面发挥了重要作用，以便帮助我的妈妈。
keep our family afloat. But I thank God
维持我们家的生计。但我感谢上帝
every day for the type of upbringing
每天都要接受这种类型的教育
that I had because it was hammered into
我之所以拥有它，是因为它被锤炼成这样。
me that nothing is going to come easy.
我明白，没有什么是轻而易举就能得到的。
And that made me who I am. Grit. Fast
而正是这些经历造就了今天的我。砂砾。快速地
forward and I'm Carol CEO, someone who
向前看，我是首席执行官卡罗尔，一个……
goes out and raises hundreds of millions
他走出去筹集了数亿美元
of dollars. Somebody who starts an
美元。开始的人
agency in multiple countries. I have
在多个国家设有代理机构。我有
zero qualifications to do any of that.
完全没有资格做这些事。
Like I didn't have talent as a designer,
就好像我没有设计天赋似的，
but I will just make it happen. There's
但我会想办法实现它。有
a lot of things I want to go into. What
有很多事情我想深入探讨。什么
are the three most important things in
这三件事是最重要的。
being successful in business? Do you
在商业上取得成功？你
think it's possible for someone to make
认为有人有可能做到这一点
themsel gritty? How do we not give so
他们自己很坚韧吗？我们怎能不给予如此之多？
many my sexuality and then pitch Chloe?
我的性取向，然后向克洛伊推销？
What was that journey like? I'll tell
那段旅程是怎样的？我会告诉
you the truth.
告诉你真相。
This has always blown my mind a little
这件事一直让我有点难以置信。
bit. 53% of you that listen to this show
少量。 53% 的听众收听了这个节目
regularly haven't yet subscribed to the
经常还没有订阅
show. So, could I ask you for a favor
展示。所以，我能请你帮个忙吗？
before we start? If you like the show
开始之前？如果你喜欢这个节目
and you like what we do here and you
你喜欢我们在这里做的事情，你
want to support us, the free simple way
想支持我们吗？免费又简单的方式！
that you can do just that is by hitting
你可以通过点击来做到这一点。
the subscribe button. And my commitment
订阅按钮。我的承诺
to you is if you do that, then I'll do
对你来说，如果你那样做，那么我也会那样做。
everything in my power, me and my team,
我和我的团队将竭尽全力
to make sure that this show is better
为了确保这个节目更好
for you every single week. We'll listen
每周都为您准备。我们会听的。
to your feedback. We'll find the guests
感谢您的反馈。我们会找到客人。
that you want me to speak to, and we'll
你想让我跟谁谈谈，我们就会
continue to do what we do. Thank you so
继续做我们正在做的事情。非常感谢
much. Emma, what do I need to understand
很多。艾玛，我需要了解什么
about your earliest context in order to
关于你最早的成长环境，以便
understand the woman, the very, very
理解这个女人，非常非常
unique woman, the very successful woman
独一无二的女性，非常成功的女性
that is sat in front of me today? And
今天坐在我面前的这个人是谁？和
when I ask that question, I'm looking
当我问这个问题时，我是在观察。
for the characteristics that were most
最显著的特征
formative in creating the woman that is
对塑造女性的性格至关重要
Emma. What a great way to start. I think
艾玛。真是个绝佳的开始。我认为
that that's a great question for me
那对我来说真是个好问题。
because so much of who I am and how I
因为我的很多特质都与我的性格和为人处事方式息息相关。
feel about who I am comes from where I'm
我对自己身份的认同感源于我的所处环境。
from. And you know, I I say all the
从。你知道，我说所有的
time, I'm from East London. I like to
我来自伦敦东区。我喜欢
make that distinction because I feel
之所以要做出这样的区分，是因为我觉得
like such a Londoner and I feel like
就像一个地道的伦敦人，我觉得
that, you know, being from East London,
你知道，我来自伦敦东区。
coming from that place is so much a part
来自那个地方是很重要的一部分。
of my character. It's so much a part of
我的性格。它与……息息相关
what is important to me. Like that idea
对我来说最重要的是什么。我喜欢这个想法
of being, you know, someone that is
你知道，就是成为那样的人
reliable, someone that is honest, not
可靠的，诚实的人，而不是
just, you know, sometimes but all the
你知道，有时候，但所有
time. and I'm one of four girls. I was
时间。我是四个女孩中的一个。我当时
raised by a single mom. And it was so
由单亲母亲抚养长大。就是这样
much kind of hammered into me that this
这件事已经被反复灌输给我了。
is where you're from. This is not where
那是你的家乡。这里不是这里
you need to stay. The world is your
你必须留下。世界是你的
oyster. You can do anything. You're just
牡蛎。你无所不能。你只是
going to have to work really, really
我真的得非常努力才行。
hard. And I think all around me, I saw a
难的。我觉得在我周围，我看到了……
lot of people that were working hard. I
很多人都在努力工作。我
saw a lot of people that were hustling
看到很多人都在忙着赚钱。
and doing what they needed to do just to
他们做着他们必须做的事情，仅仅是为了
get through the day. But I had this
熬过这一天。但我有这个
feeling very much inside of me that if I
我内心深处强烈地感觉到，如果我
wanted more for myself, it was all
我想要更多，这一切都是
completely within reach. And I think
完全触手可及。我觉得
that really came from this like East
那真的来自东方
London mentality and all the people that
伦敦人的心态以及所有那些
were around me. I didn't need to do my
他们都在我周围。我不需要做我的
research to realize that you are a big
研究后才意识到你是一个大人物
sister
姐姐
because you've got some serious big
因为你有一些非常大的……
sister energy. Even with me, we've known
姐妹能量。即使对我来说，我们也知道
each other for a little while now. So
我们已经相处了一段时间了。所以
you're the oldest of four sisters. I am
你是四姐妹中的老大。我是
indeed. How did that shape you? I think
的确。那件事对你产生了怎样的影响？我认为
in a really big way. You know, I have a
以一种非常大的方式。你知道，我有一个
pretty interesting relationship with my
我和我之间的关系相当有趣。
mom. You know, my dad left when we were
妈妈。你知道，我爸爸在我们很小的时候就离开了。
much younger. And our family dynamic is
年轻得多。我们的家庭关系是
like she's the dad, I'm the mom, and we
就像她是爸爸，我是妈妈，我们
have three kids together. And and I
他们共有三个孩子。而且我
really, you know, I think if you asked
真的，你知道，我觉得如果你问
any of my sisters, they'd say Emma had
我任何一个姐妹都会说，艾玛有
this very big hand in raising us in in
正是这只大手将我们抚养成人。
being pretty formative in our childhood.
对我们的童年影响很大。
You know, I would get up as a kid. I'd
你知道，我小时候就会起床。 ID
iron three school shirts. I'd make three
熨三件校服衬衫。我会做三个
pack lunches. My mom would, you know, go
自带午餐。我妈妈会，你知道，去
off to work. I'd get all the kids in
上班去了。我会把所有孩子都带进来。
school and half the time turn back
上学，而且一半时间都回不去
around and come home to watch this
四处转转，​​然后回家看这个
morning. That that was my life. You
早晨。那就是我的人生。你
know, there was the odd day I decided to
我知道，偶尔有一天我会决定
stay there, but more often than not, I
待在那里，但大多数时候，我
was just, you know, about trying to help
只是想帮忙而已。
my mom keep our family afloat. And I
我妈妈是家里的顶梁柱。我
think that that made me super
我觉得这让我超级
responsible at an early age, but it also
从小就承担责任，而且
gave me a very early indication of like
这让我很早就意识到了这一点
how I didn't want to live my life. I
我根本不想过这样的生活。我
knew that the milkman hadn't been paid.
我知道送奶工还没拿到工资。
I knew that there were bills dropping on
我知道账单马上就要来了。
the, you know, on the doormat kind of
你知道，就是那种放在门垫上的
every day. And I felt that at a very
每天。我当时就感觉到了。
young age and I felt the heaviness of
年轻，我感到压力巨大
that. And I knew it was all down to my
那。我知道这一切都归结于我
mom to uh to make ends meet and to and
妈妈为了维持生计，为了……
to figure that out so that we could all
弄清楚这一点，这样我们才能……
be okay. And I I kind of decided at a
没事的。我当时就决定了
very very young age that I didn't want
很小的时候我就不想那样了
any of that anxiety and I didn't want
我不想承受任何焦虑，我也不想这样。
that heaviness to to stay around and to
那种沉重感挥之不去，并且
weigh on me as I grew up. I feel like
随着年龄增长，这些事情一直困扰着我。我觉得
children aren't supposed to grow up with
孩子们不应该在这样的环境中长大。
the heaviness of bills on the doormat.
门垫上沉甸甸的账单。
Whether they are or they aren't, I
无论他们是不是，我
actually I thank God every day for the
事实上，我每天都感谢上帝。
type of upbringing that I had because I
我所受的那种教育方式，是因为我
think a it it's made me who I am. And I
我认为正是它造就了现在的我。我
guess there were parts of my childhood
我想，我的童年也包含着一些片段吧。
that essentially like just didn't exist
那基本上就不存在。
because I didn't have the ability to
因为我没有能力
like, you know, and still to this day,
你知道，直到今天依然如此。
it's so interesting actually like the
这真的很有意思，就像……
idea of like just playing isn't part of
玩耍的想法并不属于……
like who I am. But it gave me a lot of
我喜欢我这样的人。但这给了我很多
other things. It gave me a sense of, you
其他事情。它让我感觉到，你
know, I'm I'm an extremely maternal
我知道，我是一个非常有母性的人。
person and it gave me this kind of like
这个人，它给了我这种感觉……
empathetic route that is like I'm here
同理心路线，就像“我在这里”一样。
to look after a lot of other people and
照顾许多其他人，
I know I do that very very well. My
我知道我在这方面做得非常好。我的
energy had to be about, you know, making
能量必然与制造有关，你知道的。
sure my sisters were fed and making sure
确保我的姐妹们吃饱穿暖，并确保
that the house was clean and making sure
确保房子干净整洁。
we were safe because as wonderful as
我们很安全，因为尽管很美好
East London was, it was also a place
东伦敦曾经是，它也是一个地方
where you needed to have your wits about
你需要保持清醒的头脑
you. You needed to make sure that you'd
你。你需要确保你会
bought your bike in. You needed to make
你买了辆自行车。你需要……
sure that you were safe. And so my
确信你很安全。所以，我的
primary instinct wasn't like, "Let me
第一反应并不是“让我……”
have a laugh right now. Let me see what
现在就笑一笑吧。让我看看有什么
my friends are doing." My primary
我的朋友们正在做。”我的主要
instinct was, "How do I ensure
本能反应是：“我该如何确保
everybody's safe and the doors locked
大家都安全，门也锁好了。
and we're going to be good?" And at that
我们会没事的吗？就在这时
young age, before the age of, let's say,
年轻的时候，比如说，在……年龄之前
before the age of 16, if I met you as a
在16岁之前，如果我遇到你……
15-year-old and said, "What you want to
15岁的他说：“你想要什么？”
be when you're older?" What would you
你老了以后想做什么？
have said to me? Fashion designer.
你跟我说过什么？时装设计师。
Fashion designer. Straight away. Yeah.
时装设计师。马上。是的。
Fashion designer. I was obsessed. Well,
时装设计师。我当时非常着迷。出色地，
you've got to remember, you know, I was
你得记住，你知道，我曾经是
born in 82 and in the early 90s in
出生于 82 年，90 年代初
England, it was like the glory days of
英格兰，就像昔日的辉煌岁月。
fashion. You know, you had all of those
时尚。你知道，你拥有过所有这些。
supermodels, the Kates and the Naomi
超模们，凯特和娜奥米
and, you know, amazing designers,
还有，你知道，优秀的设计师们
McQueen and Galliano and the British
麦昆、加利亚诺和英国人
kind of Brit art scene and the, you
英国艺术圈的某种风格，还有，你
know, British music scene. It was just
了解英国音乐圈。只是
an amazing time in England. But to me,
在英国度过了一段美好的时光。但对我而言，
fashion was this means of escape. It was
时尚是这种逃避现实的途径。那是
this fantasy industry. I didn't know
这个幻想产业。我不知道
anyone that worked in fashion. My which
任何从事时尚行业的人。我的哪个
is so crazy. My grandma worked in a bra
太疯狂了。我奶奶在一家胸罩店工作。
factory, which I laugh about all the
工厂，我为此嘲笑一切
time now thinking about how many bras I
现在有时间思考我到底有多少件胸罩了
make. But that was like as close as
制作。但那已经是极限了。
anything I knew like anyone that had
我所知道的一切都像任何一个有这种意识的人一样。
worked in like the apparel business. I
曾在服装行业工作过。我
certainly didn't understand the idea of
当然，他并不理解这个概念。
entrepreneurialism, having your own
创业精神，拥有自己的
business. To me, it was just a fantasy
商业。对我来说，那只是一场幻想。
like I'm here in plasto. It's [__] How
就像我身处塑料世界一样。真烂。如何
do I get away from it? And you know this
我能摆脱它吗？你知道这一点
it to me it was like it's almost like
对我来说，这就像……
the movies could have just as well been
这些电影本来也可以是
Hollywood. It was like that's over
好莱坞。感觉一切都结束了。
there. It's beautiful. It's glamorous.
那里。很美丽。它很迷人。
Wouldn't that be fantastic to be part of
能成为其中的一员，那该有多棒啊！
that somehow? And what was I was
那样吗？而我究竟是什么？
thinking the other day about money. I
前几天在想钱的事。我
was speaking to a friend and we were
我当时正在和朋友聊天，我们
discussing money as if it was a person
把金钱当作人来讨论。
and playing through the attachment style
并通过依恋风格进行表演
you would have with that person, you
你会和那个人在一起，你
know, like the secure attachment, the
知道，就像牢固的连接一样，
anxious, the avoidant. At a young age,
焦虑型、回避型。年轻的时候，
what was money as a person in the room
房间里的人，金钱的意义是什么？
in your life growing up in the family?
在你的成长过程中，在家庭中经历了什么？
Like like the the best
就像最好的一样
best friend, like the best thing ever. I
最好的朋友，就像世上最美好的事一样。我
mean, you know, I we worshiped money. We
我的意思是，你知道，我们崇拜金钱。我们
worshiped money. We worshiped what money
他们崇拜金钱。我们崇拜金钱
could bring. We worshiped the material
可能带来。我们崇拜物质
stuff that you could get for having the
拥有以下物品可以获得
money. It was all about the car and the
钱。一切都与那辆车有关。
bag and the thing and the thing. That
包、东西和东西。那
was it. Was money around a lot? There
是吗？当时钱很多吗？那里
was none of it around. Absolutely none.
周围什么都没有。完全没有。
I mean, I knew I knew people that had
我的意思是，我知道我认识一些人，他们有
money, but they were kind of over there
钱，但他们当时在那边。
doing their thing. They were not part of
他们各自忙着自己的事情。他们不属于……
my thing. But it was it was so obvious
我的爱好。但这显而易见
to me when I was a kid that uh money was
对我来说，小时候，呃，钱是
something that I needed to find. So in
我需要找到的东西。所以在
my head that was always like playing out
我脑子里总是想着这些事
in my mind of like how do I get away
我脑子里一直在想，我该如何逃脱
from that being my reality? And I've,
难道这就是我的现实吗？而且我，
you know, I wanted to leave where I was,
你知道，我当时想离开我待的地方。
you know, I wanted to be, I used to have
你知道，我曾经想成为那样的人，我曾经拥有过。
this like vision and I would draw this
这就像愿景一样，我会把它画出来。
fireplace and this beautiful Christmas
壁炉和这美丽的圣诞节
tree and this credenza and I would, you
树、这件餐具柜，还有我，你
know, and I'd imagine like that's the
我知道，我想大概就是这样吧
house of of my dreams and it's so you're
我梦想中的房子，而且它对你来说太完美了。
going to think I'm insane. But years
他们会觉得我疯了。但多年
later, the first So I had Gray on
后来，第一个所以我让格雷上
December um December 20th and got him
12月20日，我抓住了他。
back home, sat down with my baby in my
回到家，我抱着宝宝坐在我的……
living room for the first time and
第一次走进客厅
literally burst into tears and my
我突然嚎啕大哭，我的
husband was oh my god isn't it like
我老公当时就说：“我的天哪，是不是就像……”
amazing we got this baby and I was like
太棒了，我们终于有了这个宝宝，我当时就想：
no it's amazing I drew this scene. This
不，这太棒了，这场景是我画的。这
is the scene that I drew my whole
那是我画的全部场景。
childhood and had this beautiful
童年时期，我拥有这段美好的时光。
townhouse in Clark and well and it was
克拉克的一栋联排别墅，而且它还很好。
like the window and the credenza and the
比如窗户、餐具柜和……
Christmas tree and I was like b like I
圣诞树，我当时就想，就像……
did it and I I will never forget the
我做到了，我永远不会忘记。
moment. It was it almost eclipsed having
片刻。它几乎掩盖了拥有
the baby. I was like this is insane.
婴儿。我当时就想，这太疯狂了。
Like I visualized it. I made that
正如我所想象的那样。我做的
happen. I've drawn this 500 times and
发生。我已经画过这幅画500次了。
here it is and here I am. And if you
它就在这里，我也在这里。如果你
were to give someone some advice, just
如果要给某人一些建议，就
jumping ahead and doing some topline
直接跳到前面做一些重点工作
stuff on how to make their drawing Yeah.
关于如何绘制他们的画作的内容。是的。
come true in their life. Yeah. As you
在他们的生活中实现。是的。正如你
reflect back on the like core components
回顾一下类似的核心组件
of that manifestation becoming a
这种表现形式变成了
reality. What are those core components?
现实。这些核心组成部分是什么？
Cuz we've all got a drawing in our head.
因为我们每个人的脑海中都有一幅图画。
Yeah. Yeah. Of course. Yeah. Well, first
是的。是的。当然。是的。首先，
of all, I wouldn't tell them to draw it
我绝对不会让他们画它。
cuz that's just not me. I wouldn't that
因为我就是那样的人。我不会那样做。
wouldn't that wouldn't be part of what I
那岂不是不属于我所说的内容吗？
would say. Absolutely not. I think that
会这么说。绝对不是。我认为
certainly in this space of like you know
当然，在这个领域，你知道的。
mindset manifestation visualization
思维模式显化可视化
there's a lot of toxic positivity around
周围充斥着很多有害的正能量。
here for women and what you need to do
这里是为女性准备的，以及你需要做什么
is like get to work like that is the
就像那样开始工作一样。
first thing to say so I I I have like
首先要说的是，我……我喜欢
yes you can dream it you can believe it
是的，你可以梦想，你可以相信。
you can create a vision board all the
你可以制作愿景板
things but don't forget what comes under
事情，但别忘了下面是什么
that and what comes under that is an
那以及它之下的一切都是
enormous amount of work and an enormous
大量的工作和巨大的
amount of planning I think that what I
我认为，计划的量就是我所需要做的。
do uniquely well, Stephen, is that I
斯蒂芬，我做得特别出色的一点是……
have an ability to focus on what I'm
能够专注于我正在做的事情
doing. I have an ability to get better
正在做。我有能力变得更好
at what I'm doing, right? Like to
我正在做的事情，对吧？喜欢
constantly get better at whatever it is
不断提升自己，无论做什么
that I'm focusing on. And then I have an
这是我目前关注的重点。然后我还有一个
ability to drown out and kind of
能够淹没和某种程度上
disregard the noise of everyone around
别理会周围人的喧闹声
me. And those three things are important
我。这三件事都很重要。
because focus is like it's like a force
因为专注就像一种力量。
multiplier in work, right? When you have
工作中的乘数效应，对吧？当你拥有
a plan and you have a focus and you can
有了计划，有了重点，你就可以……
kind of go into what it is that you find
深入探讨一下你发现的东西。
important and double down on a very
非常重要，并且要加倍投入。
finite number of things. That's what
数量有限的事物。就是这样
propels you forward. And I was very
推动你前进。我当时非常
fixated on working in fashion. But I
一心想从事时尚行业。但我
also knew that I didn't have talent as a
我也知道我没有这方面的天赋。
designer. And as much as I wanted to be
设计师。尽管我非常想成为
a fashion designer, I couldn't draw.
我是一名时装设计师，但我不会画画。
That drawing wasn't a very good one
那幅画画得不太好。
actually. If you look at it now, it's
实际上。如果你现在来看，它是
like I couldn't sketch. I don't have
好像我不会画画似的。我没有
much creative talent. What I am is a
极具创造力。我的身份是
great enabler to talent. I can sit next
是人才的强大助力。我可以坐在旁边
to a talent and understand their vision
了解人才并理解他们的愿景
and figure out a way to turn that vision
并想办法将这种愿景变为现实
into a reality, but the creative part
变成现实，但创意部分
isn't what I do so well. And so really
这不是我擅长的领域。所以真的
understanding like what is your plan and
了解你的计划是什么，以及
how you can double down and get into the
如何加倍投入并进入
things that you are uniquely good at and
你特别擅长的事情
that you uniquely have skills for is
你拥有独特技能的领域是
important. I think getting outside of
重要的。我认为走出舒适区
your head is like really important
你的脑袋真的非常重要
because so many people have dreams and
因为很多人都有梦想，
ambitions and ideas, but it just exists
它有抱负和想法，但它仅仅存在着。
here. Like what I do is a lot of action.
这里。我喜欢做的事情很多都是行动。
Like I made like hundreds of calls. Like
我好像打了几百个电话。喜欢
I always talk about this thing of at
我总是谈到这件事。
some point cuz this was like before
某个时候，因为这就像以前一样。
email. I would send a lot of letters and
电子邮件。我会寄很多信，
I thought no one's getting back to me.
我以为没人会回复我。
Maybe they're not getting the letters.
也许他们没收到信。
So I started like handd delivering
所以我开始亲自递送。
things around the West End. I would buzz
西区周边的事物。我会嗡嗡作响
on little doors of PR agencies and be
在公关公司的小门前，
like, "Hi, you know, my name's Emma and
比如，“嗨，你知道，我叫艾玛，
I sent you a letter, but I don't know if
我给你寄了一封信，但我不知道是否
you got it." People like, "Yeah,
你明白了。”人们会说，“是的，
whatever, love." But sometimes they'd
随便吧，亲爱的。”但有时他们会
let you up. And sometimes you've had a
放你起来。有时你会遇到
conversation with somebody and whatever,
和某人聊天什么的，
right? So, I really believe in this kind
正确的？所以，我真的相信这种
of idea of action. And then you've just
行动的理念。然后你就……
got to like just really when I talk
我说话的时候真的得特别注意这一点
about this idea of disregarding what
关于这种无视……的想法
people think, there's just so much noise
人们觉得，到处都是噪音。
and you have to have like this
你必须像这样
single-minded focus on what you're
一心专注于你所做的事情
doing. And I've I've been really good at
正在做。而且我一直都很擅长
drowning out the noise, not just from
盖过噪音，不仅仅是来自
what goes on inside me and what you
我内心的想法和你的想法
know, my own kind of fear, but also
我知道，我也有自己的恐惧，但同时
what's happening around you. And I think
你周围正在发生的事情。我觉得
that those things are really really key.
这些事情真的非常关键。
When you say drowning out the noise,
当你说要盖过噪音时，
there's a lot of things I want to go
我有很多想去的地方
into there, but you talk about drowning
进入那里，但你却谈到了溺水
out the noise. I'll focus on that
消除噪音。我会专注于此。
because it was the last thing. How do
因为这是最后一件事。如何
you balance drowning out the noise with
你在用以下方式压抑噪音之间取得了平衡
another principle that I know is
我知道的另一个原则是：
important to you, which is feedback?
对你来说，反馈最重要吗？
Yeah. Especially from customers because
是的。尤其是来自顾客的
customers will be saying, "We hate this.
顾客会说：“我们讨厌这样。”
Customers always hate change and they
顾客总是讨厌改变，而且他们
also don't know what they want. So, how
也不知道自己想要什么。那么，如何
do you how do you know what to drown out
你知道该如何屏蔽什么声音吗？
and what to consider to be feedback? I
什么样的才算反馈？我
think that that's really it's a it's a
认为那真的是它，那是一个
great question and you know it's
问得好，你知道的。
interesting because I am actually a
有趣的是，我实际上就是
person who takes in a lot of
吸收大量信息的人
information. If I'm trying to make like
信息。如果我想表现得像
a really big decision that I don't feel
这是一个我并不觉得很重大的决定。
fully qualified to make, which by the
完全有资格制作，由
way happens to me all the time because
这种情况经常发生在我身上，因为
I'm still learning so much. I will call
我还有很多东西要学。我会打电话
a lot of people that I think are in the
我认为很多人都在……
know, but at the end of the day I have
我知道，但最终我还是……
to call the play, right? And often if
来指挥比赛，对吧？而且通常情况下，如果
you if you call up seven or eight people
如果你打电话给七八个人……
they're going to have different opinions
他们肯定会有不同的意见。
there. There'll be different patterns
那里。会有不同的模式
that emerge. There will be contrarian
出现。总会有持相反意见者。
type of you know something that comes
你知道，就是那种会来的东西。
out of that. And so you have to then
从中脱颖而出。所以你当时就必须这么做。
still like go where is my gut? What
还是想问，我的直觉在哪里？什么
feels good to me? What's right for my
感觉不错？什么才是最适合我的
customer? I think it's very different
顾客？我觉得很不一样。
when you get customer feedback because
当你收到客户反馈时，因为
what I've learned is that everything
我学到的是，一切
your customer says is true because it's
你的客户说这是真的，因为事实就是如此。
true to them. And so what I do is like
对他们忠诚。所以我的做法是这样的
of course we have a balanced view. We
当然，我们持有的是平衡的观点。我们
try to like speak to as many customers.
尽量多和顾客交流。
We're doing giant surveys and you take,
我们正在进行大规模调查，而你参与其中，
you know, the sum of of those parts. But
你知道，就是这些部分的总和。但
when it comes down to customer feedback,
谈到客户反馈时，
I think it is it's ingested in a very
我认为它是被摄入的，而且非常
very different way than like that kind
与那种方式截然不同
of decision-making feedback. When I make
决策反馈。当我制作时
a decision on behalf of my business,
代表我的企业做出的决定，
that has to come from my gut and from
那必须发自我的直觉和内心
the intentions of where I want that
我希望去的地方的意图是……
business to go. When I'm doing things
生意要开始了。当我做事情的时候
for customers, it's very different
对顾客而言，情况则截然不同。
because you just want to please
因为你只是想取悦别人
customers. You you referenced that
顾客。你提到了这一点。
calling around people that you respect
打电话给你尊敬的人。
all the time. I do it constantly.
一直如此。我经常这样做。
I had someone say that refer to this as
有人说，可以这样称呼它：
your like personal board of directors.
就像拥有一个私人董事会一样。
Oh, I love that. Which is these like
哦，我喜欢这个。这些就像
five or seven people that you typically
五到七个你通常会认识的人
call, maybe it's 10. Um, who's on your
打电话，可能是10号吧。嗯，谁在跟你通话？
personal board of directors? Like who
私人董事会？比如谁
are these people that are taking these
这些人正在服用这些药物吗？
phone calls? And why are you calling
电话？你为什么打电话？
them? What is it about them that makes
他们？他们身上究竟有什么特质让他们如此出众
them a reliable partner in decisions?
他们是否是值得信赖的决策伙伴？
Well, you know, a first person I speak
嗯，你知道，我跟第一人称说话。
to my husband a lot because obviously we
对我丈夫来说很多，因为很明显我们
work together and Yens has a unique
共同合作，Yens 拥有独特的优势。
understanding of me, of my weaknesses,
理解我，理解我的缺点，
of what might be stopping me from making
是什么阻止了我创作
a decision. So, I feel like I go to him
一项决定。所以我觉得我应该去找他。
a lot because he will, oh, he's going to
很多，因为他会，哦，他要
tell me the truth. I mean, he's, you
告诉我实话。我的意思是，他，你
know, he's told me to like some of the
我知道，他让我喜欢上一些……
biggest unlocks in my life and my career
我人生和职业生涯中最大的突破
have come from Yens. And I will never
源自日元。我永远不会
ever forget, Stephen, like one of my
斯蒂芬，你永远不会忘记，就像我的一个朋友一样。
first board meetings, one of my first
第一次董事会会议，也是我最早参加的会议之一。
companies, it was called ITB and I would
公司，它被称为ITB，我会
get so nervous ahead of a board meeting
董事会会议前总是非常紧张
and he'd be like, "Why are you so
他会说：“你为什么这么……”
nervous?" And I'd be like, "I don't
紧张吗？我会说：“我不紧张。”
know." Cuz I'm I'm a good chatter. I'm a
我知道。“因为我能说会道。我是一个
good presenter. I can sell anything.
优秀的演讲者。我什么都能卖。
But, you know, I would get to these
但是，你知道，我会做到这些的。
board meetings and I would just fall
董事会会议，我就会彻底崩溃。
apart. And he said to me, just wrong
分开。他对我说，完全错了。
timing, by the way, if you're going to
顺便提一下时间安排，如果你打算……
give, you know, your wife a little bit
你知道，给你的妻子一点……
of feedback. Literally, just before we
反馈。确切地说，就在我们之前
went in, he said, "You know what? really
他进去后说：“你知道吗？真的
I I know why you are suffering here,
我知道你在这里受苦的原因，
Emma. You have an employee
艾玛。你有一名员工
mentality and I I mean I was 26 or 27
心态，我的意思是，我当时26岁或27岁。
years old. I couldn't think about
岁。我当时无法思考……
anything else in the whole meeting
会议期间还有其他事情吗？
because I was like he's completely
因为我觉得他完全
right. I have an employee mentality.
正确的。我拥有员工的心态。
Well, why? Because I'd only ever been an
为什么呢？因为我一直以来都只是个
employee up until that point. But I was
直到那时为止的员工。但我当时
looking instead of, you know, being
只是看着，而不是，你知道的，成为
there as the CEO to guide the board into
作为首席执行官，他的职责是指导董事会。
a decision. I was looking for everybody
一项决定。我一直在寻找所有人
else to tell me what to do. And so I was
否则就告诉我该怎么做。于是，我……
seeking their approval instead of going
寻求他们的认可而不是去
in and saying, "Here's the direction.
进去并说：“这是方向。”
This is what we're doing. Everybody come
这就是我们正在做的事情。大家都来
with me and these are the reasons D."
我同意，原因如下：D。”
And so it was such an interesting
所以，这真是一件很有趣的事。
insight and I think that you could only
洞察力，我认为你只能
or I could have only heard that from
或者我只能从……那里听说。
somebody so close to me. So at that
一个与我关系非常亲近的人。所以当时
early stage in your career, what role
职业生涯早期，担任什么角色
are mentors playing? Because we're
导师们在上场吗？因为我们是
talking about personal boards of
谈论个人董事会
directors here. Yeah. These are in some
各位导演在此。是的。这些在某些
respects mentors, right?
尊重导师，对吧？
Do they matter? And I say this, Emma,
它们重要吗？艾玛，我还要说一句：
because I have kids coming up to me all
因为孩子们都围着我转。
the time saying, "Steve, I need a
当时有人说：“史蒂夫，我需要一个
mentor." And they sometimes say, "Can
导师。”他们有时还会说，“可以
you be my mentor?" And I'm thinking,
你愿意做我的导师吗？” 我心想，
"Fucking hell, I've done 17,000 hours of
“我的天哪，我已经玩了17000个小时了。”
podcasting and you haven't learned a
播客，而你还没学会……
[__] thing." That was the mentorship.
“真是个混蛋。” 这就是所谓的指导。
That was the mentorship. How what's your
这就是导师制。你的情况如何？
what's your take on finding a mentor and
你对寻找导师有什么看法？
how pivotal and important that is to
这对……来说是多么关键和重要啊
become a successful person. Listen, you
成为一个成功的人。听着，你
know, from my own experience, I don't
就我自己的经验而言，我不知道。
think I had any mentors. You know, I I
我想我以前有过导师吧。你知道，我
started work like well, let's talk about
工作开始了，好吧，我们来谈谈吧。
real work, right? So it's like I've had
真正的工作，对吧？所以就好像我一直……
a job since I was 12 years old. I've
我从12岁就开始工作了。我已经
worked a paper round and then I worked
我先是送报纸，然后又工作了一段时间。
in the delies and then I worked in
我在熟食店工作，然后我在……
clothes shops. And when I got my first
服装店。当我得到我的第一个
real job in an office in a fashion show
在时装秀的办公室里做一份真正的工作
production company, I was 18 years old.
制作公司，当时我18岁。
So I've had a salaried job in a place
所以，我之前在某个地方有一份领固定薪水的工作。
that was working towards something that
那是为了实现某个目标而努力的
I felt was interesting and in the the
我觉得很有趣，而且在
kind of direction of where I wanted to
我想要的方向
go since I was 18. At that point, you
我从18岁就开始去了。那时候，你
make whoever is around you, if you're
如果你身边的人都在，那就让他们知道你是什么样的人。
smart, you make whoever is around you
聪明，你让周围的人都变得聪明。
your mentor. I used to sit in front of
你的导师。我过去常常坐在前面
my boss and everybody thought that was
我的老板和所有人都认为那是
so unfortunate because my she could see
真不幸，因为她能看到
my screen and that was like the
我的屏幕，就像……
beginnings of online shopping. Netaporte
网上购物的起源。 Netaporte
was our uh client and we all had a
是我们的客户，我们所有人都……
discount. So everyone would sit on
折扣。所以大家都会坐在……
Netaporte all day except me because my
除了我以外，其他人整天都在用Netaporte，因为我
boss sat behind me and they were like
老板坐在我身后，他们就像
what a nightmare. And I was like no not
真是场噩梦。我当时就想，不，不是
a nightmare at all. Whatever she says
简直是一场噩梦。不管她说什么
when she's on her sales calls I would
当她进行销售拜访时，我会
write down and I would use them later on
记下来，以后会用到。
on my sales calls. Now was she my
在我的销售电话中。她现在是我的吗？
mentor? No, she was my boss, but I used
导师？不，她是我老板，但我以前……
her as such because I would learn from
之所以这样，是因为我可以从她身上学习。
her. I take, you know, I even like copy
她。你知道，我甚至喜欢复印。
her outfits, you know, like I would do
她的穿着打扮，你知道，就像我会做的那样。
the whole thing. And so for me, she was
全部。所以对我来说，她就是
really formative. But I don't think that
非常有影响力。但我并不这么认为。
you should walk around looking for a
你应该四处走走，找找看。
mentor. I think you have to walk around
导师。我觉得你得四处走走。
asking questions because anyone who's
提问是因为任何人都会问
going to be a good mentor probably
可能会成为一名优秀的导师
doesn't have time to mentor you first.
没时间先指导你。
Secondly, like depending who you are and
其次，这取决于你是谁，
what your exposure is, you're not going
无论你的风险敞口有多大，你都不会去
to have the right people around you to
身边要有合适的人
get mentored. So you've just got to be
接受导师指导。所以你必须……
super inquisitive and I think it's
超级好奇心强，我觉得是
really important to take where you are
了解你所在的位置非常重要
and figure out like who is around you
弄清楚你周围都有谁。
and where can you get that type of
哪里可以买到那种类型的？
mentorship from. For me in the beginning
来自……的指导。对我来说，一开始
I would just take whatever client I had
我当时就接手所有客户。
like if I come into contact with the CMO
比如，如果我接触到首席营销官的话。
or the CEO I just ask him a question.
或者直接问CEO一个问题。
I'd be in the meeting I'd be like I have
我会在会议上，我会说我已经……
two other questions for you. It have
还有两个问题想问你。它有
nothing to do with the work that we're
这和我们正在做的工作无关。
doing or the you know whatever brief I
做或者你知道的，任何简短的事情我
was there to deliver and I'd ask a
当时在那里是为了送货，我会问一个
question. And what what part of you do
问题。而你身体的哪一部分在做什么？
you think if I
你觉得如果我
removed and this could be a skill or a
已移除，这可能是一项技能或
characteristic
特征
would definitely assure that you
我一定会向您保证
wouldn't be where you are today? Like
如果不是这样，你今天就不会取得这样的成就了吗？喜欢
what is this the sacred part of you that
这是你身上神圣的一部分吗？
is defining cuz people see Emma today
之所以如此重要，是因为人们今天看到了艾玛。
and they see these skills and this
他们看到了这些技能和这些
knowledge and all this stuff and these
知识以及所有这些东西
relationships and these businesses and
关系以及这些企业和
this success but what is the like cuz
这种成功，但感觉如何呢？
you said I'm dyslexic and I know I think
你说我有阅读障碍，我知道我觉得
you left school you dropped out of
你离开了学校，你辍学了。
school at 15 and then you went to
15岁上学，然后你去了
college for a while and you dropped out
你上了一段时间大学，然后辍学了。
there too. I'm a serial dropout. So it's
那里也是。我是一个屡次辍学的人。所以是
not something you learned necessarily in
这并非你一定能学到的东西
school. So I'm wondering what the
学校。所以我想知道……
characteristic is that was the like the
特点是它就像
wind in one sails that brought you here
带你来这里的风帆
and what if I removed that thing you
如果我把那个东西拿走呢？
definitely wouldn't be here and he could
他肯定不会在这里，而且他可能
only give me one thing. I mean listen we
只给我一样东西。我的意思是，听着，我们
didn't call it that then but it would
当时没这么叫，但它会是这样的。
come down to grit. Grit, right? I think
归根结底，还是毅力的问题。毅力，对吧？我认为
that that is what we would say now. You
这就是我们现在会说的话。你
know, Angela Duckworth like coined that
你知道吗，安吉拉·达克沃斯（Angela Duckworth）创造了这个词。
phrase, I guess, or that term and wrote
我猜是这个短语，或者那个术语，然后写道
that fantastic book about grit that all
那本关于毅力的精彩著作
everybody read and was like, "Oh my god,
大家读完后都惊呼：“我的天哪！”
I just want my kids to have grit." Like,
我只是希望我的孩子有毅力。比如，
my kids want for nothing. They're not
我的孩子们什么都不缺。他们不是
going to be gritty. Like, it's just
将会很艰苦。就像，就这么简单
facts. You don't you don't grow up in
事实。你不会，你不会在……长大
Belair gritty, you know? But I think
你知道，贝尔艾尔很接地气。但我认为
that if you if I think about what it
如果你，如果我思考一下它是什么
what it is for me and and still is, I'm
对我而言，它过去是、现在是、将来也仍然是，我
just gritty. I'm very clear about what I
就是粗糙。我非常清楚我
want and what I need and I will find a
我想要什么，我需要什么，我都会找到。
way whatever it is. You know, I am not
不管是什么方式。你知道，我不是
any of the things that you would have on
你会带的任何东西
my resume. You know, an apparel CEO,
我的简历。你知道，一位服装公司的首席执行官，
someone who goes out and raises hundreds
出去筹集数百美元的人
of millions of dollars, somebody who
数百万美元，某人
starts an agency in multiple countries.
在多个国家成立代理机构。
I have zero qualifications to do any of
我没有任何资格去做任何事情。
that stuff. I will just make it happen
那些东西。我会想办法实现它。
because I'm in the moment. I see the
因为我活在当下。我看到了
opportunity and I am prepared. And I'm
机会来了，我已经准备好了。而我是
prepared because it's like I have done
我已经做好了准备，就像我做过的那样。
all the work to get to the point where
为达到这一点所做的所有努力
that thing that is in front of me, I
我眼前的那个东西，我
will make it happen. I've done enough
我会促成此事。我已经做得够多了。
work to say, okay, like I can take this
努力让自己说，好吧，就像我可以接受这个
to the that next place. And is that grit
前往下一个地方。那是毅力吗？
an ember that life blew on? Because I
生命之风吹拂下的余烬？因为我
wonder if I'd gone back and I'd met Emma
我想知道如果我回去的话，会不会遇到艾玛。
at 18 years old whether she would have
18岁时，她是否会……
said it like to me like that.
他就是那样跟我说的。
No, Emma at 18 years old would have been
不，18岁的艾玛本来应该是
like it's so interesting. You know, we
真是太有趣了。你知道，我们
don't have yearbooks in in England, but
英国没有年鉴，但是
if if we did, I reckon I would have been
如果那样的话，我想我会……
like the most likely to succeed. I don't
比如最有可能成功的人。我不
think anyone at school was like, "Oh,
我觉得学校里肯定有人会说：“哦，
she's a bit of a waste girl." No, it's
她有点儿不修边幅。“不，是……”
like I had that mentality that I was
我当时就是那种心态，觉得自己是
away from the pack, that I was going to
远离人群，我原本打算
do something
做点什么
special, but also my mentality was like
很特别，但我的心态也像这样
whatever it takes. You know, if I could
不惜一切代价。你知道，如果我能
if I think about the most important
如果我思考最重要的事
words for career
职业相关的词汇
advancement, like the the three most
进步，例如前三名
important words, I'd be like, I'll do
重要的词，我会说，我会做的
that. That was me. I had my hand up my
那。那是我。我举起了手
whole life. I'll do that. Like every
一生。我会这么做。就像所有
single time anytime anyone has asked me
每次有人问我
whatever it took, wherever I have been
无论付出什么代价，无论我身在何处
in whichever workplace, I was like, I'll
无论在哪个工作场所，我都会想，我会
do it. I'll do that. And and that is
去做。我会这么做。就是这样。
what like people started to look at me
人们开始看着我
as someone that would just figure it
就像那种会自己想明白的人一样
out, right? It's not like I had any
出去了，对吧？我又不是什么都没有。
particular skill. I just put myself in a
特殊技能。我只是把自己置于一个
situation and in the space
情况和空间
of let me have a go every single time.
让我每次都尝试一下。
To me, it makes perfect sense. It makes
我觉得这完全合情合理。它制造
perfect sense because you grew up in a
完全正确，因为你成长在一个
situation as an older sister where you
作为姐姐，你面临的情况是……
were playing the role of a dad where you
我们扮演的是父亲的角色，而你
did have to put your hand up and say,
确实需要举手说：
"I'll do that." Mhm. You did have to
“我会这么做。”嗯。你确实不得不这么做。
make the lunches. And I sometimes think
准备午餐。我有时会想
back to my own life and think about how
回到我自己的生活中，思考着……
avoid of independence is maybe a scary
避免独立或许是一件可怕的事。
thing to some parents, but it's also an
对一些父母来说，这很重要，但同时这也是……
incredibly useful thing for a kid to
对孩子来说非常有用的东西
learn that I have to get myself from A
我明白我必须从A地脱身。
to B. Yes. Whether it's from home to
给 B。是的。无论是从家到
school or from home to dinner or from
学校或从家到晚餐地点
home to whatever it might be. And that I
无论它是什么，它都可以成为你的家。而我
don't know. I looked at your life and go
不知道。我审视了你的人生，然后离开
okay you had this massive void of
好吧，你当时有一个巨大的空白
independence and in there grows skills
独立性，并在其中培养技能
belief and understanding about life that
对生命的信念和理解
most others don't get. So it's no
大多数人都不明白。所以，不是这样的
surprise that at such a young age you
令人惊讶的是，你年纪轻轻就做到了。
were you thought you could do stuff cuz
你以为你能做这些事是因为
so many people they have an idea they
很多人都有这样的想法
know where they are now and they kind of
他们知道他们现在在哪里，而且他们有点
might have an idea of where they want to
他们可能已经对他们想去的地方有了大致的想法。
be but the gap between it is not
是，但两者之间的差距并非
something they've ever had to traverse
这是他们曾经经历过的艰难险阻。
like they've never had to walk it. Do
就好像他们从来没走过这条路一样。做
you think it's possible for someone to
你认为有人有可能
make themsel gritty? You know, you've
让他们自己变得粗糙？你知道，你已经
got team members, employees, you can see
团队成员、员工，你可以看到
the variance in gritty and ungritty,
粗糙与不粗糙之间的差异，
resilience. And I see a lot of
弹力。我看到很多
ungrittiness that Yeah. Go on. Where
是的，缺乏颗粒感。继续。在哪里
where do you see the ungrittiness? And
你觉得哪里不够粗犷？和
is it possible to make yourself great?
有可能让自己变得伟大吗？
Have you ever seen someone go from what
你见过有人从什么状态变成什么状态吗？
should we call it? What's the opposite
我们应该这么称呼它吗？相反的是什么？
of grittiness? Floppy. I don't know. I
粗糙感？软盘。我不知道。我
don't know what the opposite of
不知道反义词是什么
grittiness is, actually. Um I soft I
实际上，这就是所谓的“粗糙感”。嗯，我软了。
guess. Yes. Listen, I I do. if you want
猜测。是的。听着，我确实愿意。如果你想
it, like anything else, right? It's got
它和其他事物一样，对吧？它有
it's all
这一切都是
about do you actually want to be that
你真的想成为那样的人吗？
way and to behave that way. And we were
以这种方式行事。我们当时
talking about this actually, funny
说起来真有意思
enough, on the way over because, you
够了，在来的路上，因为你
know, I I just came from my own office 2
我知道，我刚从我自己的办公室过来。2
minutes away. It's
几分钟路程。它是
Friday. All of the product teams are in.
星期五。所有产品团队都已到位。
The rest of the office is pretty empty.
办公室其他地方都很空。
And you know, and I think postco people
你知道，我觉得postco的人
have really taken the liberty
真是擅自行动了
of as we allow them, right? they can
只要我们允许，对吧？他们可以
come in four days a week. And it's
每周来四天。而且是
interesting because we talk so so much
有趣的是，我们聊了很多。
about the flexibility of working from
关于远程办公的灵活性
home and what Zoom life has kind of done
居家生活以及Zoom带来的种种改变
for business, but we don't talk about
为了生意，但我们不谈论
any of the rigidity of it and what it
它的任何僵化之处以及它是什么
takes away from work. And I can tell you
耽误工作。我可以告诉你
and I can guarantee you that had I been
我可以向你保证，如果我当时
a work from home person in my 20s, I
我是一名二十多岁的居家办公人士，
would not be where I am now. There is no
那样我就不会有现在的成就了。没有
doubt in my mind and I think about some
我心中充满疑虑，我开始思考一些事情。
you know I met my husband at work. I
你知道吗，我和我丈夫是在工作中认识的。我
made some of my best strongest
创作了我一些最优秀、最强劲的作品。
relationships in my life that are the
我生命中最重要的人际关系是
most important things to me and the
对我来说最重要的是
foundation of my happiness and my like
我幸福和喜爱的基础
being a solid person at work. That's
在工作中做一个可靠的人。那是
where those relationships come from. And
这些关系从何而来？和
so I think it's really interesting now
所以我觉得现在真的很有意思。
that we have this aversion of like
我们对这种事物有种厌恶感
wanting to be away from the office all
想离开办公室
of the time. And I'm like, "Oh, that's
当时的情况。我当时就想，“哦，那是……”
like it's so interesting to me because
我觉得这很有趣，因为
I'm like such a I'm like an imperson. I
我简直就像个冒牌货。我
want to be with people. I want to
想和人在一起。我想要
collaborate. I want to do things
合作。我想做事
quickly." And the culture of work right
迅速。”以及正确的工作文化
now makes that so hard. So I think yes,
现在这让事情变得如此困难。所以我觉得是的。
you can treat teach someone to have
你可以教导别人如何对待他们。
grit, but I can't teach you on a screen,
毅力很重要，但我无法通过屏幕教你。
babe. I can't reach you. You won't see
宝贝。我联系不上你。你不会看到的
how I move. And in that same way that I
我的动作。同样地，我
had this woman that sat behind me and I
我身后坐着一位女士，我
would take notes of everything she said.
我会记下她说的每一句话。
That happened in real time, right? She
那是实时发生的，对吧？她
would walk out of the room and I'd be on
他会走出房间，而我会……
my next new business call saying her
我下一个新业务电话说她
lines. Like it was just that quick and
线条。就好像一切都发生得那么快。
that immediate and I would test it out
我会立即进行测试。
and I'd make it my own. All of that is
我会把它变成我自己的东西。所有这些都是
lost. And so I feel a little bit sad for
丢失的。所以，我感到有点难过。
the way that we're working right now
我们目前的工作方式
because I don't think that we're having
因为我觉得我们并没有……
that exchange of, you know, what happens
那种交流，你知道，就是发生的事。
when you're in a really dynamic
当你处于一个非常动态的环境中时
environment and you're able to learn
环境允许你学习
from people around you because we're not
来自你周围的人，因为我们不是
as together as we once were. When you're
我们依然像以前那样亲密无间。当你
looking around your team and thinking
环顾你的团队，思考着
that person's going to be a star in the
那个人将来会成为明星。
future, that person's going to be a star
未来，这个人会成为明星
in the future, which I'm always doing,
将来，我一直都在这样做，
which I'm always doing as well. And this
我也一直都是这么做的。而这
is why always, always, always. What are
所以总是，总是，总是。什么是
the factors or the characteristics of
因素或特征
those people that you look at in your
你注视的那些人
office and go that's she's going to be a
去办公室，然后她就要去上班了。
star, he's going to be a star. What is
他将会成为明星。什么是
it about them? What are they doing that
跟他们有关吗？他们在做什么？
others aren't doing? Well, I you know,
其他人没做的？嗯，你知道，
and people ask me this all the time. I
人们总是问我这个问题。我
think that the sure way to put yourself
想想让自己显得更自信的最好方法。
in a position for more responsibility
处于能够承担更多责任的位置
for a promotion is to be excellent at
晋升的关键在于表现出色
what you're doing, right? Like I I find
你正在做的事情，对吧？就像我发现的那样
it really difficult when people are
当人们……的时候，这真的很难。
like, you know, I'd really like to do
你知道，我真的很想做
this thing over there. I'd really like
那边那个东西。我真的很想
that opportunity. And I'm like, but
那个机会。我当时就想，但是……
you're only 70% good at what you're
你只擅长你所做的事情的70%。
doing now. like I'm looking at the 120%
现在正在做。就像我看着那120%一样
people, the people that are smashing it
人们，那些正在取得巨大成功的人
in the role that they're at now before
在他们现在担任的这个角色之前
they're going to go anywhere else. So
他们会去其他任何地方。所以
that's the first thing to say. But I
这是首先要说的。但我
don't think it's any I I again I have
我不认为这是任何我再次拥有的东西。
hire much more for attitude over
态度比招聘更重要
experience, right? I really want the
经验，对吧？我真的很想要
people that come in with like a winning
那些带着必胜信念而来的人
mentality, a figure it out mentality.
心态，一种想办法解决的心态。
And also what I love is this these
而且我喜欢的还有这些
people that have like an understanding
那些有类似理解的人
across the business. It's like you are
整个业务范围内。就像你是
an amazing thoroughbed, you know,
一张非常棒的床，你知道的。
wholesale salesperson, but you really
批发销售员，但你真的
want to learn ecom and you really want
想学习电子商务，而且你真的很想
to learn about stores and you really
了解商店，你真的
have a good understanding what's
要充分了解什么是
happening planning and merchandising.
活动策划和商品销售。
Like, you know, in business leadership
比如，你知道，在商业领导力方面。
language, they call them the T-shaped
他们称之为T形语言
leaders, but it's like that's what
领导者，但就好像就是这样
that's what I care about. People that
那是我最关心的事。那些人
have an interest in the entirety of our
对我们所有人的兴趣
business and they can see outside of the
商业领域，他们可以看到外部世界。
lane or the division that they work in.
他们所在的部门或分部。
And so, that becomes interesting to me.
所以，这引起了我的兴趣。
But to me it's so much more in
但对我来说，它的意义远不止于此。
mentality, energy,
心态、精力、
enthusiasm, attitude. I'm also one of
热情，态度。我也是其中之一
the things that I think is massively
我认为非常重要的那些事情
overlooked. But a key thing now is
被忽略了。但现在最关键的一点是
flexibility because I hire a lot of
因为我雇佣了很多员工，所以需要一定的灵活性。
people that are in their 40s and 50s,
40岁到50岁的人，
right, for super senior executive
对，对于高级管理人员来说。
leadership level roles. But if you come
领导层职位。但如果你来
to me from a competitor and you believe
对我来说，这是来自竞争对手的信息，而你相信
that the only way to get from here to
从这里到那里的唯一方法是
here is the way you've been doing it for
这就是你一直以来的做法
the last 20 years, that's problematic to
过去20年，这存在问题
me. I need you to come both with the
我。我需要你们俩一起来。
experience and a level of flexibility
经验和一定的灵活性
because technology means that the
因为科技意味着
customer and the uh the consumer
顾客和呃，消费者
experience is changing all the time. So
经验是不断变化的。所以
that ability to say I've got all of this
那种能够说“我拥有这一切”的能力
knowledge but I'm I'm willing and ready
虽然我缺乏相关知识，但我愿意并且已经准备好了。
to flex is like really important. So I I
灵活运用肌肉真的非常重要。所以，我
need I need all those things. I need a
我需要所有这些东西。我需要一个
lot. Stephen, you don't say. But what
很多。斯蒂芬，你可真会说。但是什么
are the red flags? Very demanding. Tell
这些是危险信号吗？要求很高。告诉
me tell me some sentences I could say in
请告诉我一些我可以说的句子
an interview with you that would be
一次与您的访谈将是
immediate red flags. Oh, I've got a good
立即出现的危险信号。哦，我有一个不错的
one. So, can you talk to me about work
一。那么，你能跟我谈谈工作吗？
life balance in this
生活平衡
organization? Sorry, babe. I'm leaving.
组织？对不起，宝贝。我要走了。
I'm Get out. Here's the thing. Work life
我要离开。事情是这样的。工作生活
balance is your problem. Like, that's
平衡是你的问题。比如，那就是
yours to figure out because the way we
这需要你自己去想，因为我们的方式
run organizations now is that no one
现在运营组织的人，没有人。
misses a dentist appointment or a
错过牙医预约或
doctor's appointment or a haircut or
预约看医生或理发或
their kids parent teacher conference at
他们的孩子家长会
our organizations. That's just not how
我们的组织。事情并非如此。
we work anymore, right? like you come
我们现在还工作吗？就像你来一样
in, you have set hours, but you you know
上班时间是固定的，但你知道
there's flexibility within the the your
你的范围内存在灵活性。
working life. It's not like, oh my
工作生活。这不是，哦，我的
goodness, such and such is not at their
善良，某某并不在他们
desk. That's just not how we work
桌子。我们不是那样工作的。
anymore. So when somebody talks to me
不再是了。所以当有人跟我说话的时候
about their work life balance in an
关于他们的工作与生活平衡
interview process, I'm like, something
面试过程，我当时就想，这算什么？
is wrong with you. You haven't been able
你有问题。你一直无法
to figure that out. That's not the way
弄清楚这一点。这不是办法。
you win this interview. I'm not trying
你赢得了这次面试。我不是故意的
to give this away. I'm not trying to
把它送出去。我不是故意的
give this away, but because it might
把它送人，但因为它可能
[__] me over saying this, but um we do a
说这话真让人恼火，但是，嗯，我们确实……
screening survey and one of the
筛选调查和其中之一
questions tests for this. So I actually
针对此问题的测试题。所以，我其实
know the exact percentage of the general
知道总体的确切百分比
public that when asked this question
公众被问及这个问题时
will pick work life balance as one of
将工作与生活平衡作为其中一项选择。
the most important things and it's
最重要的事情，而且是
roughly 33%. 33. So 33% of people on our
大约 33%。 33. 所以，我们这里33%的人
screening survey will say that work life
筛选调查将显示工作生活
balance is more important to them than
对他们来说，平衡比什么都重要
another range of options including doing
其他一系列选择包括：
perfect work, beating the competition,
完美的工作，击败了竞争对手。
leading and inspiring others, having a
领导和激励他人，拥有
happy team, etc. They'll pick work life
快乐的团队等等。他们会选择工作生活
balance as being one of their most
平衡是他们最看重的品质之一。
important things. So it's a lot of
重要的事情。所以有很多
people that prioritize this. And it's
把这件事放在首位的人。而且是
not to say for me, let's listen, it's
不是说对我来说，我们听听，是
not to say for me that it's a bad thing,
对我来说，这并不是说这是件坏事。
but it's it's not what I would pick. No
但这并非我的选择。不
babe, it's not what you would pick
宝贝，这不是你会选的。
because you're ambitious as anything. So
因为你野心勃勃。所以
maybe, you know, it's very interesting,
或许，你知道，这很有意思。
right? Because I wonder if you put on
正确的？因为我想知道你是否穿上
that list of options earning 10% more
那份收益高出 10% 的期权清单
year on year getting a meaningful bonus,
年复一年获得丰厚的奖金，
right? Like because here's the thing,
正确的？因为事情是这样的，
these things correlate. And that's what
这些事情之间存在关联。就是这样。
people don't understand. In order to run
人们不理解。为了运行
an organization where there is the
一个组织，其中包含
ability for your people to have a good
让你的人民拥有良好的能力
work life balance, you have to be
工作与生活平衡，你必须……
profitable. The company has to be, you
有利可图。公司必须是，你
know, in line with, if not beating its
知道，与……一致，即使不击败它
competition. We have to be able to run
竞赛。我们必须能够奔跑
an efficient business to give people
一个高效的企业，为人们提供服务
what they need. The two things go hand
他们需要什么。这两件事密不可分。
in hand. And so I have this idea that
已到手。所以我就有了这个想法……
with the people that I work with, like
与我一起工作的人，比如
we're in a social, like we're in a
我们身处一个社交场合，就像我们身处一个
contract together, right? It's like
共同签订合同，对吧？就像
you're going to work really hard and in
你会非常努力地工作，而且
return you should get an amazing place
回来后你应该会得到一个很棒的地方
to work. you should get an incredible
去工作。你应该得到一个令人难以置信的
environment that is feeding you in ways
环境以各种方式滋养着你
that are not just about your your job,
这不仅仅关乎你的工作，
right? And so when I look around at our
正确的？所以当我环顾四周时，我们
office and our organization, we're
办公室和我们组织，我们是
doing, you know, I just I left the
你知道，我刚刚离开了
office yesterday, there was like a
昨天办公室里好像……
fertility seminar going on where there
那里正在举办生育研讨会
were like hundreds of people in the
就像数百人一样
kitchen of our office all learning about
我们办公室的厨房里所有人都在学习
having their eggs frozen and like
把他们的卵子冷冻起来，就像
various different I I I have four kids.
各种各样的我，我有四个孩子。
I clearly didn't need to be in the
我显然不需要待在……
seminar. I'm like, I'm done. Um, but you
研讨会。我心想，我受够了。嗯，但是你
know that that was happening. It's like
知道这件事正在发生。就像
we do things for our employees that are
我们为员工做了一些事情，这些事情是
above and beyond what a workplace back
远超工作场所的范畴
in the day may have considered the norm.
在当时，这可能被认为是常态。
So I just feel like you've got to with
所以我感觉你必须这样做
that like something has to give and
就像总得有所改变一样，
there are certain things that are the
有些事情是
employees responsibility within that and
员工在此方面的责任
you figuring out what works for your
你正在摸索什么方法对你有效
life, how you're going to pick up your
生活，你打算如何重新开始
kids, how you get home, how you get to
孩子们，你们怎么回家，你们怎么到
work, what happens in like these are all
工作，诸如此类的事情都属于此类。
things that you need to figure out
你需要弄清楚的事情
within the construct of your life. That
在你的人生结构中。那
isn't the
不是吗？
employer's job. That isn't the
雇主的工作。那不是……
employer's responsibility. I'm going to
雇主的责任。我要
play devil's advocate. So, what people
扮演一下反方角色。所以，人们会怎么做呢？
are, I guess, when they hit that that
我想，就是当他们遇到那个情况的时候。
button and they say, "I want work life
按下按钮，他们说：“我想要工作生活
balance," what they are maybe alluding
他们或许是在暗示“平衡”。
to is am I expected to work seven days a
我是否需要每周工作七天？
week because I need that information to
一周，因为我需要这些信息
be able to figure up figure out if I'm
能够弄清楚我是否
going to be able to pick up my kids and
我将能够去接我的孩子，
be able to do my totally dejing or
能够完全做到我或
whatever on the weekend. So, what is the
周末随便做什么。那么，什么是……
expectation in your business? I don't
您对业务有何期望？我不
think the expectation is that anyone is
认为人们的期望是任何人都可以
going to have to work seven days a week
我得一周工作七天。
in order to get, you know, to have an
为了得到，你知道，拥有一个
average job. Like, they're not going to
普通的工作。比如，他们不会……
have to do that. If you have ambition,
必须这么做。如果你有抱负，
if you want
如果你想
to do the most, if you want to grow, if
要想做到最好，如果你想成长，如果
you want to be one of those people
你想成为那样的人吗？
that's like, you know, at the top of the
那就像，你知道，在顶端
organization, the chances are you might
组织，你很有可能
have to work a little bit more. That's
还得再多花点时间。那是
the truth. Like, what are we talking
真相。我们到底在说什么？
about here? We're gonna lie to everyone.
这附近吗？我们要对所有人撒谎。
Do you work five days a week, Stephen?
斯蒂芬，你一周工作五天吗？
No, babe. You're working on a Saturday
不，宝贝。你周六要上班
and a Sunday. And if I text you wherever
还有一个星期天。如果我给你发短信，无论你在哪里
you are in the world, you come back to
你身处世界，你最终会回到
me within about an hour. I'm assuming
大约一个小时后我就会收到。我假设
that that's not just what you do for me.
这不仅仅是你为我做的事。
That that's just how you roll. And
这就是你的行事风格。和
that's how I roll. And that's how most
我就是这么做的。而大多数情况就是这样。
successful people roll. And you know,
成功人士会翻滚。你知道，
it's like there is something to speed
感觉好像有什么需要加快速度的。
and agility. And I don't listen, I think
以及敏捷性。我觉得我根本不听。
I have a tremendous work life balance. I
我的工作生活平衡得非常好。我
am in Malibu most weekends. um on the
我大多数周末都在马里布。嗯，关于
beach. But I think that we have to have
海滩。但我认为我们必须拥有
a level of honesty about what it takes
对所需条件保持一定的诚实度
to be really successful. And I think
要想真正成功。我觉得
that everybody is tired of hustle
每个人都厌倦了忙碌奔波。
culture. People are tired of burnout and
文化。人们厌倦了倦怠，
figuring out how you can do what you
弄清楚你如何才能做到你
need to do and be really successful at
需要做某事并取得真正的成功
the same time is like what I consider
同时，这就像我认为的那样。
personal responsibility. But at the same
个人责任。但与此同时
time, if we tell everybody that to be
时间，如果我们告诉所有人这一点的话
really successful, you can do that in a
真正成功的话，你可以这样做
way that um is, you know, without being
这种方式，嗯，你知道，无需……
150% without waking up most days and
大多数日子里，不用醒来就能达到150%的效率。
doing some type of work, without
做某种工作，但没有
thinking about work a lot. It's just not
经常想着工作。根本不是这样
it's not honest and it's not um it
这不诚实，而且也不太好。
wouldn't connect with what I see and
无法与我所看到的产生共鸣，
what my experience are of most people
我的经验与大多数人的情况类似
that are truly successful. Why do some
真正成功的人。为什么要做一些
people hate what you just said? I think
人们讨厌你刚才说的话吗？我认为
because it hits them in a place of like
因为它触动了他们内心深处的痛点。
I just don't want to do that. I want I
我就是不想那样做。我想要我
want all the benefits but I don't want
我想要所有的好处，但我并不想要
to do the bit in the middle. And I get
完成中间那部分。我明白了
that it's not for everyone then don't do
如果这不适合所有人，那就不要做。
it. But is it possible to have the
它。但是，是否有可能拥有
success to be number one to be on the
成功就是成为第一名
magazines to be Emma? And is there like
杂志是艾玛的吗？有像这样的吗？
not a way where I can have my evenings
我无法拥有自己的夜晚。
and weekends but still get like the I
周末也一样，但还是会像我一样
have some evenings and weekends but like
有些晚上和周末，但喜欢
I want all of my evenings and weekends.
我想要所有的晚上和周末。
No, you're not. No. No. If if it's
不，你不是。不，不。如果……
possible, tell me who she is and I'll
如果可能的话，告诉我她是谁，我会
tell you. I'll show you a liar.
告诉你。我会让你见识见识谁在说谎。
You know, I I I don't think so. And and
你知道吗，我……我不这么认为。而且
and honestly, Stephen, like what what
说实话，斯蒂芬，这到底是怎么回事？
are we talking about? Because we I think
我们在讨论什么？因为我认为
that most people most people want
大多数人都想要
a you know, they they don't want
你知道，他们不想
everything, right? It's like most people
一切都对吧？就像大多数人一样
don't are not sitting here being like, I
不要坐在这里像这样，我
need to be in all the magazines. I want
需要出现在所有杂志上。我想
this. I want that. It's like most people
这。我想要那个。就像大多数人一样
want to have uh security of a
想要获得某种安全保障
well-paying job. They want to, you know,
高薪工作。他们想，你知道，
be able to afford their rent or their
能够负担得起他们的房租或他们的
mortgage and have a nice car and live
房贷，买辆好车，过着舒适的生活
well and go on a few holidays and and
嗯，然后去度假几次，
that's like a good life. Should you be
那才叫美好生活。你应该
able to do that? Absolutely. Should you
能做到吗？绝对地。你应该
be able to do that without working
无需工作就能做到这一点
evenings and weekends and putting all of
晚上和周末，以及把所有时间都投入到……
the hours in? Yeah, I really think that
几个小时？是的，我真的这么认为。
you should. But if you are leading an
你应该这么做。但如果你领导一个
extraordinary life, to think that
非凡的人生，想想看
extraordinary effort wouldn't be coupled
非凡的努力不会与之相伴
to that somehow is crazy.
这简直太疯狂了。
It's interesting post pandemic how it
疫情后的发展很有意思。
feels like leaders got gas lit a little
感觉领导层有点被蒙蔽了。
bit. founders got gas lit by platforms,
少量。创始人被平台蒙蔽了双眼，
you know, like if you go on LinkedIn,
你知道，就像如果你上LinkedIn，
you got all these people telling you how
很多人都在告诉你该怎么做
to run a business and that what you're
经营一家企业，这就是你的目标。
doing wrong and work life balance and
做错事以及工作与生活的平衡
you got to be more like this and you've
你应该更像这样，而且你已经
got to be this kind of leader and you
你必须成为这样的领导者，而你
have to be this empathy and do this and
必须有这种同理心，并且这样做。
that and the other. And if you're a
那个和另一个。如果你是
young founder growing up in this world
在这个世界成长的年轻创始人
where this everyone is telling founders
这是每个人都在告诉创始人的事情。
what to do, um it can feel incredibly
该怎么办呢？嗯，这可能会让人感觉非常难以置信。
confusing. And I think in particular
令人困惑。而且我认为尤其如此
post pandemic where like how we work was
疫情后，我们的工作方式发生了怎样的变化？
like shuffled up and it's now like take
就像重新洗牌一样，现在就像是拿走
a mix. It's like before the pandemic, it
混合。就像疫情之前一样，
was like we all got it. We come to the
感觉我们都明白了。我们来到了
office 5 days a week, we work, you know.
我们每周五天都在办公室工作，你知道的。
Um, it's a difficult time to be a
嗯，现在做个……真不容易。
founder because you've almost got to
创始人，因为你几乎必须
step out if you know what I mean. Yeah,
如果你明白我的意思，就出去走走。是的，
you do. Yeah, you have to. And listen, I
你做。是的，你必须这么做。听着，我
don't think that that is as hard as
不要认为这像……那么难
people are making it. You have to
人们正在制作它。你必须
understand that, you know, you can't be
要明白，你知道，你不能
a leader and a people pleaser at the
一位领导者，也是一位讨人喜欢的人
same time. And if you're walking around
同时。如果你正在四处走动
trying to make everybody happy, guess
我想，我只是想让每个人都开心。
what you won't do? You won't have a
你不会做什么？你不会有
great business. You have to have a focus
很棒的生意。你必须集中精力
on what it is that you're trying to do.
关于你想要做什么。
And you have to be relentless in the
你必须坚持不懈。
pursuit of doing those things. And you
追求做这些事。你呢
need the people that are going to, you
需要那些要去的人，你
know, I am I'm so much about the people
我知道，我非常在意人。
that help you. You know, I I hate that
这对你有帮助。你知道吗，我讨厌那样
idea of like being um, you know, like a
感觉就像……你知道，就像……
a you know, I get called like a
你知道，我经常被人叫做……
self-made whatever. And I'm like, I'm
自创的任何东西。我当时就想，我是
really not self-made if you understood
如果你明白的话，就会发现这其实并非完全是白手起家。
how many people there were around me
我周围有多少人？
that just like getting me here today. Do
就像是把我带到今天这个位置一样。做
you know what I mean? There's like a a
你知道我的意思？就像有一个
village sitting outside. But nothing
坐在外面的村庄。但什么也没有
happens on your own. And it takes so
事情是自然发生的。而且这需要很长时间
many people and so so much skill and so
很多人，而且技术非常精湛，所以
much that I don't have. And so when you
很多我没有的东西。所以当你
start a company, this idea that you
创办一家公司，这个想法
should make all of the if you if you're
如果你是的话，就应该把所有事情都做完。
thinking about making all of these
考虑制作所有这些
concessions before you're thinking about
在你考虑之前先做出让步
what the goal is, what the the the the
目标是什么，这是什么
you know I I call it and everybody it's
你知道，我把它叫做“它”，每个人都这么叫它。
like enterprise mentality. It's like you
就像企业思维一样。就像你
have to put the business first, the
必须把业务放在第一位，
needs of the business. And sometimes
满足业务需求。有时
that is about thinking about your people
这关乎于思考你的人民。
and being a certain type of leader.
以及成为某种类型的领导者。
Sometimes it's not. So you've got to
有时并非如此。所以你必须
balance those things, right? We're
要平衡这些因素，对吧？是
trying the point of a business is to
尝试经营一家企业的意义在于……
make profit. It's to create like a
赚取利润。它是为了创造类似……
company to serve, you know, your
公司为您服务，你知道，您的
customers, all of those things. It
顾客，所有这些。它
really isn't about what I think so many
其实这跟我所想的并不多。
people are trying to make it about. Now,
人们试图把这件事变成焦点。现在，
your leadership style is, you know, it's
你的领导风格，你知道，就是
it's going to be such a huge part of
这将成为非常重要的一部分
what makes that business successful, but
是什么让这家企业成功？
it isn't it isn't everything. And so, I
并非如此，并非一切。所以，我
think that we've just got to try and
我觉得我们必须尝试一下。
separate these things like a little bit.
把这些东西稍微分开一点。
That can't be the first thing that
那不可能是第一件事
you're thinking of like
你想到的是类似这样的东西
how you know like how you're doing all
你怎么知道你做得怎么样
of that stuff. The first thing that you
就是那种东西。你做的第一件事
think about is like how is the business
想想看，比如，这家公司是怎样的？
going to grow? How are we going to
会增长吗？我们该如何……
thrive? What are we what are we actually
蓬勃发展？我们究竟是什么？我们到底是什么？
here to do? I think founders are scared
来这里做什么？我认为创始人很害怕
as well because we live in this age of
也因为我们生活在这个时代
social media where you know if
社交媒体上，你知道吗
especially if you have a profile if you
尤其是如果你有个人资料的话
do something wrong there's this really
做错事的话，真的会有这么回事。
interesting incentive that the employee
有趣的激励措施，员工
has where they can they can pop back.
他们可以随时返回。
And so if if you fire me from your
所以，如果你把我从你的公司解雇……
company, Emma, and you know, I didn't
公司，艾玛，你知道，我没有
feel so good when I was
当我……的时候，感觉真好
there, I now have you by the balls a
好了，我现在完全掌控了你的命根子。
little bit, if you know what I'm saying.
有点儿，你懂我的意思吧。
Yeah, totally. Because I can post on my
是的，完全正确。因为我可以在我的……上发帖
TikTok and say, you know what, Emma is
TikTok 上有人说，你知道吗，艾玛是
not who you think she is. Yeah. That's
不是你想象中的她。是的。那是
just part of being in business though,
这只是经商的一部分而已。
right? But then because you're living
正确的？但因为你还活着
under that threat from some kind of
在这种威胁下，来自某种……
activist employee, how do you stop that
积极参与维权的员工，你如何阻止这种情况？
from changing the way that you live with
从改变你的生活方式开始
that enterprise mentality and do what's
那种企业精神，以及做该做的事。
right for the business? I don't think
适合企业吗？我不认为
you do. I've had so many founders say
你做。我听过很多创始人这么说
this to me in my portfolio. They've
这对我来说，应该放在我的作品集中。他们有
saying like, "Oh man, I'm like scared of
比如，他们会说：“哦，天哪，我好害怕……”
being canceled." Well, don't do anything
被取消资格。” 好吧，那就什么都别做。
to be cancelled. I mean, look, I think
将被取消。我的意思是，你看，我认为
it's a fine line, right? You're if
这其中的界限很模糊，对吧？你是如果
you're a leader, you're never going to
你是一位领导者，你永远不会
please everybody. And I think that this
请大家注意。而且我认为这一点
is where leadership style and who you
领导风格和你是谁，这才是关键所在。
are as a person really comes out. I
展现出一个人真实的一面。我
don't think anybody I'm somebody that
别以为我是那种人。
leads with no ambiguity. Nobody's like I
明确无误地引导。没有人像我一样。
wonder what Emma's thinking. It's like
真想知道艾玛在想什么。就像
I'm very clear in what I'm thinking. I'm
我的想法非常清晰。我是
very clear in what the goals are. And
目标非常明确。和
the reason that we've been able to do
我们之所以能够做到这一点，原因在于……
what we've been able to do is because of
我们之所以能够取得今天的成就，是因为……
those things. I have a very
那些东西。我非常
straightforward management style and I I
直率的管理风格和我
bring everybody along with me. Now
带上所有人一起来。现在
listen, there's always going to be
听着，总会有……
someone or you know a fraction of people
你认识的某个人或你认识的一小部分人
that will feel disgruntled. I've gone
这会让人感到不满。我走了
through various things in different
通过各种不同的事情
companies where you've had to you know
你知道，你曾经在哪些公司工作过？
downsize or let people go and things
缩减规模或裁员等等
that are really unfortunate and that's
这真的很不幸，而且……
just part of the course of business. Now
这只是业务流程的一部分。现在
are you doing those things in a way that
你做这些事情的方式是怎样的？
is congruent with who you are as a as a
与你作为一个人是一致的
leader and you know really thinking
领导者，你知道，真正思考
about what what that actually like you
关于你到底喜欢什么
know it's it's not again it's like I
我知道它不是，它又来了，就像我
never have like an indiv
从未像一个人那样
individualistic idea about that. It's
这其中蕴含着一种个人主义的观点。它是
like if I have to look at a company and
比如，如果我必须考察一家公司，
downsize I'm not thinking about the 50
缩小规模？我没考虑50。
people that I have to let go. I'm
我不得不放手的人。我是
thinking about the 400 jobs that need to
思考需要填补的400个工作岗位
be saved. And sadly, sometimes there is
得救。遗憾的是，有时确实如此。
a little collateral damage. That's just
一些附带损害。那只是
part of being in business. Um, I
这是经商的一部分。嗯，我
certainly am not sitting here sweating
我当然不会坐在这里汗流浃背。
what somebody might do on TikTok because
某人在TikTok上可能会做什么，因为
I know who I am and I feel good about
我知道我是谁，我感觉很好。
the decisions that I make because of the
我做出的决定是因为
of the where they come from. They come
他们来自哪里。他们来了
from me. They come from my heart and I
来自我。它们源自我的内心，我
know that I'm a good person. So, I would
要知道我是一个好人。所以，我会
never sit here and be like, "Oh no,
千万不要坐在这里想：“哦不，
someone's going to like shame me." What
肯定有人会羞辱我。
was the most important lesson you had to
这是你必须上的最重要的一课。
learn about leadership as a upand
了解领导力作为一种向上和
cominging
即将到来
talented black woman in business? I
有才华的黑人商界女性？我
don't think it's any different than
我觉得这和以前没什么区别。
honest if I if I'm really honest I don't
说实话，如果我真的诚实的话，我不会
think it's any different from any other
我觉得它和其他任何东西都不一样。
woman but I do think it's different for
但我认为女性的情况有所不同。
women. Okay. More generally, I think
女性。好的。更广泛地说，我认为
that probably the most important lesson
这或许是最重要的一课。
was how distinctive and important my
我的特色和重要性体现在哪里？
point of view is and why that gives me
观点是什么，以及为什么这会给我带来什么
an edge, right? But I also understand
优势，对吧？但我也能理解
that, you know, this kind of like
你知道，这种感觉就像
empathy coin has two sides to it, right?
同理心这枚硬币有两面性，对吧？
What makes women phenomenally good
是什么让女性如此优秀
leaders and makes them fantastic at you
领导者，并使他们成为你眼中出色的人。
know mentoring staff and looking after
了解指导员工并照顾
the needs of the team is sure as the
团队的需求是确定无疑的
underbelly when it comes from perhaps
或许，腹部下方
you know downsizing their team or you
你知道，他们正在缩减团队规模，或者你
know firing the wrong person or if
知道解雇错误的人或者如果
people are not getting pay rises like
人们没有像以前那样获得加薪。
how they might feel about that. So, I
他们对此会有什么感受？所以，我
definitely had to learn that there's two
肯定要学习一下，原来有两个
sides to what makes me great and to keep
让我变得伟大的各个方面，并保持
both of those sides in check. So, it's
双方都处于对峙状态。所以，就是这样。
balancing the empathy part of you with
平衡你身上同理心的那一部分
the needing to make difficult decisions.
需要做出艰难的决定。
Yeah.
是的。
Because it doesn't feel like care to
因为感觉不像是在关心
fire someone. It's like because No, it
解雇某人。就像因为不，它
goes against the grain of uh of caring
这与关心的本质背道而驰
for It goes against the grain of being
因为它违背了存在的本质。
like a maternal individual who is
就像一位慈母一样
looking after people, right? because
照顾他人，对吧？因为
that's the opposite of that. You're
恰恰相反。你是
leaving someone to their own devices and
放任他人自生自灭
so that that's been difficult for me for
所以这对我来说一直很困难。
sure. Do you remember the first time you
当然。你还记得第一次……吗？
had to contend with that dichotomy and
不得不面对这种二元对立，
how it felt and Yeah. Yeah, I do. I I
感觉如何，嗯。是的，我有。我 我
think it would have been like way back
我想那会像很久以前那样
when in London in ITV the first time I
第一次在伦敦的ITV电视台，我
had to do like a meaningful downsizing
不得不进行一次有意义的裁员。
of the agency and I had to fire like you
机构和我一样，不得不解雇你。
know it was a small agency. I had like
我知道那是一家小型机构。我当时就像
60 people and I fired 15 people in one
60个人，我一次性解雇了15个人。
day. So we're in a tiny office, Gressy
天。所以我们是在一间很小的办公室里，格雷西
Street in, you know, just off of
你知道，就在街边，
Tottenham Court Road and everyone sits
托特纳姆法院路，大家都坐着。
together. So there was no like giant
一起。所以并没有巨人。
boardroom that you could go into and
你可以进入的会议室
then go out the back door. It was like I
然后从后门出去。就像我
went back upstairs and told everyone,
回到楼上，把事情告诉了所有人。
you know, it was like awful. It was
你知道吗，那简直太糟糕了。那是
absolutely awful. I laugh about it out
简直糟糕透了。我笑着说出来
of just
仅仅
like horror of how it felt at the time
就像当时那种感觉带来的恐惧一样
because it really to me it felt like the
因为对我来说，这感觉就像是
end of the world, the end of my life.
世界末日，我的生命也终结了。
And I felt so
我当时的感觉是
responsible because oftentimes, you
负责任，因为很多时候，你
know, like so much of being in a
我知道，就像身处其中的许多事情一样
competitive dynamic environment, you
在竞争激烈的动态环境中，你
know, like you're pulling people out of
你知道，就像你把人们从……中拉出来一样
other agencies and other jobs and you're
其他机构和其他工作，你
bringing them in and you know, you're
把它们带进来，你知道，你
like that's the best person for this and
就像他是最适合做这件事的人一样。
then all of a sudden you're like, I'm so
然后突然间你就觉得，我太……
sorry, but like it's over. And and that
抱歉，但感觉一切都结束了。而且，那
for me was soul destroying the first
对我来说，第一部简直是毁灭灵魂的。
time I had to do it. But in hindsight,
我不得不这么做了。但事后看来，
how do you look at that decision now
你现在如何看待这个决定？
with your wisdom? Well, look, again, I
凭你的智慧？嗯，你看，再说一遍，我
go back and say I created a better
回去然后说我创造了一个更好的
company be because of it. I created more
公司因此而受益。我创作了更多
discipline in the business because I was
在商业领域，我秉持着纪律，因为我……
able to see the mistakes that I'd done
能够看到我犯的错误
that weren't just about overstaffing,
那不仅仅是人员过剩的问题，
but it was just about running a a less
但这仅仅是运行一个较少的
healthy engine. I do think it made me a
发动机运转良好。我确实认为这让我成为了
better leader in the sense of I had held
在我看来，他是一位更好的领导者。
so much of the anxiety of what was
很多焦虑都源于过去。
happening in that company, it not going
那家公司发生的事情，不会发生。
well to myself. I hadn't really shared
嗯，对自己来说。我其实并没有分享过
with the full senior management team
包括所有高级管理团队
like quite how bad things were because I
真不知道事情到底有多糟糕，因为我
felt I'm the CEO that's all my problem.
感觉自己像个CEO，这就是我的问题所在。
They should be able to just come in and
他们应该能够直接进来。
out. And with that there was a lack of
出去。因此，缺乏
accountability from everybody else. And
其他所有人的责任。和
so I think I've really understood now
所以我想我现在真的明白了。
that you know it's like I'm I'm here at
你知道，就像我在这里一样
the top of the organization. And you
组织的最高层。你呢
know it's like almost like I'm the I'm
我知道这几乎就像我就是那个我
the manager, right? I sit on the
是经理吧？我坐在
sidelines and I have a bunch of people.
场边还有一群人。
I shouldn't be like running on the pitch
我不应该像在球场上奔跑那样
to score the goal. I need to stay on
进球得分。我需要继续待下去
those sidelines and I need to direct
那些场外因素，我需要指导
everybody to do the best job possible.
每个人都要尽力做到最好。
And now I think so much more about
现在我对这件事有了更多思考。
bringing everybody on the journey. And
让每个人都参与到这段旅程中来。和
when you're having difficult times,
当你遇到困难的时候，
which we do all the time in all of our
我们一直以来都在这样做，在我们所有的地方
businesses, despite whatever it might
企业，无论它如何
look like to people, you know, you need
看起来像是在别人眼里，你知道，你需要
to bring people on the journey and get
带领人们踏上这段旅程并获得
them involved in what those solves are.
让他们参与到这些解决方案的制定过程中。
Because if you get to that place where
因为如果你到了那个地方，
you have to downsize or you have to
你必须缩减规模，否则就必须
change the way that you're doing
改变你的做法
business and you have to make meaningful
做生意，你必须做出有意义的事情。
changes, they're there with you. they've
变化，它们与你同在。他们有
been part of the solution. They've been
成为解决方案的一部分。他们一直是
part of those solutions not working out
部分解决方案行不通
and they're going to be part of making
他们将参与制作。
them right for the rest of the business.
让他们负责公司其他业务。
I think there's a lot of business owners
我认为有很多企业主
that can relate to holding on to all of
这可能与坚持所有
that pressure themselves, cash flow
他们给自己施加压力，现金流
issues, the uncertainty around the
问题，以及围绕这些问题的不确定性
business, and you know, they internalize
商业，你知道，他们会把这些内化于心。
it, they take it home with them, it's
他们把它带回家，就是这样。
with them seven days a week. Um, how did
一周七天都和他们在一起。嗯，怎么会这样
it feel for you when you were going
当你离开的时候，我能感受到你的感受。
through those challenges with your your
克服这些挑战，你
first company? Um, and I I asked that
第一家公司？嗯，我问过这个问题。
because I want the person going through
因为我希望经历这一切的人
that, I was going through it, to feel
当时我正在经历这一切，感觉
seen, but also to have a bit of a
看到了，但也有点
blueprint, a road map of what to do
蓝图，一份行动指南。
about that. Well, the the truth is it
关于那件事。好吧，事实是……
feels like the end of the world, right?
感觉像是世界末日，对吧？
Like that that's how it feels when you
就像那样，当你……的时候就是这种感觉
start something from the ground up and
从零开始创建某件事
it's yours. There's such a sense of
它是你的。有一种……的感觉
responsibility. And, you know, I think
责任。你知道，我觉得
that what happens in business, it's
这就是商业中发生的事情。
always like a a confluence of factors,
总是像多种因素汇合的结果，
right? like you try to work out like
正确的？就像你尝试锻炼一样
what has made this thing happen and it's
是什么导致了这件事的发生？
like you know sometimes like death by a
就像你知道的，有时候就像死于……
thousand cuts there's no like one thing
千刀万剐，没有一样东西能与之媲美。
that you can point to and say that was
你可以指着它说那是
it that's what made this like
正是这一点让它如此像
downtrending moment happen it's like
下跌趋势发生时就像……
it's a bit of this and a bit of that and
它有点像这个，又有点像那个，
a bit of this and a bit of that but
这个一点，那个一点，但是
often what it comes from is you know you
通常情况下，它的来源是你知道你
get so into what you're doing that it's
你会太投入你正在做的事情，以至于……
very very hard to rise back up and I
重新振作起来真的非常非常难，而且
think what I've taught myself like this
想想我这样自学了些什么
muscle that I've taught myself is every
我自学的那块肌肉就是每一块。
kind of quarter at least every six
某种类型的季度至少每六
months I try to float up and see like
几个月来，我试图浮出水面，看看自己会是什么样子。
what is happening not what I'm telling
重要的是正在发生的事情，而不是我所说的。
myself not what are we doing like what's
我自己不知道我们在做什么，比如……
happening what's happening with the
发生了什么事？
competition what's happening in the
竞争格局如何？
market and back then I just didn't have
当时我没有市场，也没有
the ability to do that I was so heads
我当时非常有这种能力。
down so in the work so you know like
所以，在工作中，你知道，就像
just deep in like my clients and doing
就像我的客户一样，我全身心投入其中。
the best job that I could that I had no
我能找到的最好的工作，但我没有
ability to zoom out and I do again I'm
能够缩小画面，我又试了一次。
not just blaming myself but it it really
不仅仅是责怪自己，而是真的
was about that inability to see clearly.
是因为看不清东西。
And so I think for anybody that's kind
所以我觉得对于任何善良的人来说都是如此。
of been through a moment like that, it's
经历过那样的时刻，就是
either surrounding yourself with people
要么让自己身边围绕着人
that are able to help you have a little
能够帮助你拥有一些
bit more perspective or trying to make
再多一些视角，或者试图做出一些改变
that a habit that you do that in your
那是你养成的一种习惯，你
business. You know, Bill Gates talks
商业。你知道，比尔·盖茨会说话
about having reading week or like, you
关于举办阅读周之类的活动，你
know, an away week. He takes himself off
知道，这是一次为期一周的客场比赛。他自行离开
and he does it twice a year and he goes
他每年做两次，然后他就去了。
and he just like sits somewhere
他就那样坐在某个地方。
beautiful. It looked like it was like by
美丽的。看起来像是……
the water or something. goes into a
水之类的东西。进入
little cabin and he just reads, but he
他住在小木屋里，就在那里看书，但他
thinks about like what is happening in
思考着正在发生的事情
his business, what is happening in the
他的生意，发生了什么事
world. And I certainly would never want
世界。我当然绝不会想要
the comparison to Bill Gates, but I
虽然有人拿我跟比尔·盖茨比较，但我
think just having the ability to zoom
想想看，仅仅是拥有缩放功能就足够了。
out a little bit is something that all
稍微偏离一点是所有事情
founders should really really think
创始人真的应该好好想想
about and it's given me unbelievable
关于它，它给了我难以置信的
perspective that I've made that a
我从这个角度看待这个问题
practice now. That's so so true. I was I
现在就开始练习。说得太对了。我当时
was talking the other day, I think it
前几天聊到这个，我想是这样的
was actually when I did that solo
实际上，那是我独奏的时候。
episode on on the diary of a sea about
关于海洋日记的一集
this idea of like clouds and trenches. I
这种想法就像云和沟壑一样。我
love the solo episodes. Did you listen
我喜欢单人出场的剧集。你听了吗？
to it? Oh, thank you. Yeah, I love them.
到那里去？哦，谢谢。是的，我喜欢它们。
I think they're so good. One of the
我觉得他们太棒了。中的一个
ideas that emerged from that process was
由此产生的想法是
as I was writing the solo episode, I
当我写那集独角戏的时候，我
thought about the day that I went
我想起了我去的那一天
fishing. Like I don't fish, obviously,
钓鱼。显然，我不会钓鱼。
you know, like, you know, but I went
你知道，就像，你知道，但我去了
fishing because whatever. I just found
钓鱼，因为随便吧。我刚刚发现
myself there and I'm on this boat in the
我自己也在那里，我就在这艘船上。
middle of the lake and the art of
湖中央和艺术
fishing is you sit there and do [__]
钓鱼就是你坐在那儿干些乱七八糟的事。
nothing. You do nothing and you're on a
没有什么。你什么都不做，却被困在……
lake and it's like pissing it down. So
湖水就像往里撒尿一样。所以
I'm sat there in my Mac and it's just
我坐在那里，用我的Mac电脑，就……
like leathering on me. And this boat,
就像皮革一样摩擦着我。还有这艘船，
this is not glamorous. This is a 2 m
这并不光鲜亮丽。这是2米
wooden boat. Oh, babe. We all had an
木船。哦，宝贝。我们都曾有过
idea of like a yacht. No, no, no, no,
就像一艘游艇。不，不，不，不
no. It was like at a castle somewhere.
不。感觉就像身处某座城堡里一样。
And it was the most important like seven
而且它是最重要的，就像七一样。
hours of my life at that exact moment
那一刻，我生命中的几个小时都耗费在我身上。
cuz I'd been in the trenches for so many
因为我已经在前线待了太久了
weeks in a row that sitting out on that
连续几周都坐在那里
boat for seven hours just waiting for
乘船七个小时，只是在等待
this nibble that never came cuz I'm [__]
这口从未到手的口水，因为我太烂了。
at fishing, it turns out, was so
事实证明，钓鱼是如此
powerful. Like this is this is the
强大的。就像这样，这就是
distinction between being able to stand
能够站立与否之间的区别
back from the photo so you can see the
从照片背面看，这样你就能看到
picture and founders like especially
图片和创始人尤其喜欢
when you've got cash flow issues and
当你遇到现金流问题时
clients giving you [__] and and team
客户和团队给你添麻烦
member issues you're like this. Yeah.
你遇到的会员问题就是这样。是的。
And I think that the problem is as
我认为问题在于……
founders we can feel guilt and we kind
创始人，我们可能会感到内疚，我们很善良
of talked about this earlier tremendous
之前已经讨论过这一点，非常棒。
guilt of like not being in there and not
内疚感，就像没能身处其中一样，而且也不是
being in the trenches but because we
身处战壕，但因为我们
don't realize we're serving our company
没意识到我们是在为公司服务
by creating a little bit of space. Yeah.
通过创造一点空间。是的。
So is it a practice for you? It is and
所以这对你来说是一种练习吗？是的，
honestly I've really made it a practice
说实话，我已经把它当成一种习惯了。
and I say that it it's about like first
我说，这就像第一段
of all I have to get out of the office
我得想办法离开办公室。
that's the most important thing um and
这是最重要的事，嗯……
it's really about me creating the
这实际上是关于我创造的
conditions for me to be really
让我真正成为的条件
thoughtful so it's like I prepare to
深思熟虑，就像我准备……
like be with myself like so I'm really
就像和自己待在一起一样，我真的
taking a snapshot of like what's
就像拍张照片一样，记录下眼前的一切。
happening with my competition what are
我的竞争对手发生了什么事？
people doing I'm on the sides of my
人们都在做，我站在我的两侧。
competition like I'm like what is the
就像我一样，竞争到底是什么？
customer seeing I go like in store I
顾客看到我像在店里一样，
really try to understand that what is
真正尝试去理解什么是
everybody else like what are customers
其他人都喜欢顾客。
truly experiencing from this brand and
真正体验到这个品牌的价值
then it's really about looking
那么，关键就在于观察。
objectively at what we're putting out
客观地看待我们所发布的内容
there and I really do that and I've I've
在那里，我真的会那样做，而且我已经……
got a uh I think I have a really really
呃，我想我真的真的
good sense of not
良好的判断力
um I don't know how to say it without
嗯……我不知道该怎么说才好。
swearing like you can swear I just don't
你骂脏话骂得那么厉害，我却不会。
believe my own [__] I I've still got
相信我自己的胡说八道，我仍然有
the ability and it's so interesting
这种能力真是太有趣了。
because I think that when you join a new
因为我认为当你加入一个新的组织时
company you I always say to people that
公司，我总是跟人们说，
come, you know, you got fresh eyes for,
来吧，你知道，你对……有了全新的认识，
I don't know, a couple of weeks, maybe a
我不知道，大概两周吧。
couple of months at best, until you
最多几个月，直到你
start telling yourself the same stories
开始给自己讲同样的故事
that we tell ourselves internally. And I
我们内心告诉自己的那些话。我
am very good at having those fresh eyes.
我非常擅长用全新的视角看待事物。
And so when I have new people in the
所以，当有新人加入时
business, I will go to those people and
做生意的话，我会去找那些人。
be like, what are you seeing? Where were
就像在问：“你看到了什么？”当时
you before? What have you like versus
你以前是吗？你喜欢什么？
what we're telling you? Like what are
我们想告诉你们什么？比如……
you seeing in this company? And so I
你对这家公司有什么看法？所以，我
make a point to like get around to any
务必抽出时间去做任何事。
new starters and that's just like part
新员工，这就好比一部分人。
of the process. Competition, new
过程。竞争，新的
starters, having the zoom out, what am I
开场白，拉远镜头，我是什么？
actually like serving and delivering to
其实很喜欢服务和送货
customers and I kind of take all of that
顾客和我基本上都接受了这一切。
and come up with like just a one pager.
然后写出一份只有一页纸的简介。
Like for me it's always very simplistic,
对我来说，它总是非常简单。
you know, it's like three things. I'm
你知道，这就像三件事。我是
like this, this, this, go and work on
像这样，这样，这样，去工作
those things. And it will often be in
那些东西。而且它通常会在
line with the priorities that I have
符合我的优先事项
like the broader priorities of the
例如，更广泛的优先事项
business. But sometimes it's just like a
商业。但有时候，它就像……
random thing that I'm like, didn't see
一些我没注意到的随机事件
that happening. I didn't see how [__]
那件事正在发生。我没看到有多糟糕
would we become at that, you know? And
我们会变成那样吗？你知道吗？和
so it's like I try to I try to have that
所以，我就像在努力，努力去拥有那种感觉。
level of objectiveness all the time. Are
始终保持客观性。是
you paranoid?
你疑神疑鬼的吗？
Definitely. 100%. Yes. Well, also I'm
确实。 100%。是的。嗯，我也是
par rightly paranoid. Like I work with
部分人确实有理由感到偏执。就像我与……一起工作
some of the most like copied duped
一些最像抄袭的受骗者
brands in the whole world. Do you know
全球品牌。你知道吗
what I mean? It's like I'm not actually
我的意思是？感觉就像我其实并不在场一样。
paranoid. I'm just like everybody's
偏执。我和大家一样
copying me. And how do you think about
模仿我。你觉得呢？
people copying you? Because anyone
有人在模仿你吗？因为任何人
that's successful, all of my friends
我的所有朋友都成功了。
that have done anything well, they're
凡是做过任何好事的人，他们都是
just everyone just copies. I'm totally
大家都在抄袭。我完全
unbothered. We've moved already, babe.
毫不在意。我们已经搬家了，宝贝。
I'm like, by the time they've copied me,
我心想，等他们抄袭完我之后，
I'm, you know, I'm a year and a half in
你知道，我已经在这里一年半了。
the future. I'm like, go for it. Done.
未来。我的想法是，放手去做吧。完毕。
It's over. You got your first um I guess
结束了。你第一次……嗯，我想是这样的。
your first foray into the world of
你第一次涉足……的世界
fashion was that internship you had at
时尚就是你在……的那份实习经历。
19 years old. You became a show producer
19岁。你成为了一名节目制作人
after that at Inca Productions. You
之后在印加制作公司工作。你
worked at a marketing agency between
曾在一家营销机构工作过
sort of 23 25 years old um called
大概23、25岁左右，嗯，叫
Saturday Group which is now known as
周六小组，现在被称为
Wednesday Agency co-founded by your now
星期三机构由你现在的共同创始人共同创立
husband Yens. Yes indeed. Which is where
丈夫 Yens。确实如此。那就是
you met him? Yes. Now I'm you know I'm
你见过他吗？是的。现在你知道我是
in business with Yens. So we started our
与日元进行商业往来。于是我们开始了我们的
relationship as I was an employee and
因为我是员工，所以建立了关系。
then he was my investor. So he and his
那时他就是我的投资人。所以他和他的
business partner invested alongside
商业伙伴共同投资
somebody else that I bought in in my
我买入的另一个人
first company. Then I married him. Um,
第一家公司。然后我嫁给了他。嗯，
then we had four kids together and it
然后我们一共生了四个孩子，
has been an
一直是
unbelievable relationship and one of the
难以置信的关系，也是其中之一
kind of most important things in my life
我生命中最重要的事情之一
and still remains one of the most
至今仍是最……之一
important things in my life. But it
我生命中的重要事情。但是它
hasn't always been easy because he is
并非一直都很容易，因为他
obviously, you know, doing his thing and
很明显，你知道，他一直在做他自己的事。
he's very ambitious and he has his own
他很有野心，而且他有自己的打算。
things going on. Um, and when you bring
事情正在发生。嗯，当你带来
kids into the equation, everything
把孩子也考虑进去，一切就都变了。
changes again, right? that it it shifts
又变了，对吧？它转移了
a little bit. I think what is important
一点点。我认为重要的是
is to have somebody
就是要有人
who just
谁刚刚
sees all of your talent and sometimes
他看到了你所有的才华，有时
sees it before you do yourself. And I
他比你更早看到。我
think that Yens has been like
认为燕子一直像
unbelievably encouraging of me at every
每次都给予我难以置信的鼓励
turn. Every time I've had any doubt,
转动。每当我心存疑虑时，
every time I've been like, "God, that
每次我都会想，“天哪，那……”
feels like a little bit outside my
感觉有点超出我的掌控范围
comfort zone." And he's been like, "But
舒适区。” 他一直说，“但是
you did this, but you did that." you
你做了这个，也做了那个。
know, and I'm like, "Oh, yeah, I did,
我知道，然后我就说：“哦，是的，我做了。”
didn't I?" And he's like, "No, everybody
难道我不是吗？”他回答说：“不，每个人都是。”
has that." And you'll know people,
有那种能力。”而且你还会认识一些人，
right, who are really ambitious
对，那些真正有野心的人。
themselves and maybe their partner is
他们自己，或许还有他们的伴侣
envious, resentful, maybe
嫉妒，怨恨，或许
lowkey, subtly plays them, like plays
低调地、巧妙地玩弄他们，就像玩游戏一样。
them down or diminishes their ability to
削弱或降低他们的能力
them. What would you say to someone who
他们。你会对一个……说些什么？
right now is listening to this and has a
现在正在听这个，并且有一个
partner who they feel doesn't want them
他们觉得伴侣并不想要他们
to climb to the top of the mountain and
爬到山顶
isn't willing to help carry them up
不愿意帮忙把他们抬上去
there and actually sees their work
在那里亲眼看到了他们的工作
as a competition. What would you say to
作为一项竞赛。你会怎么说？
that person because I know we probably
那个人，因为我知道我们可能
got a couple million listening.
有几百万人收听。
I say this all the time.
我一直都这么说。
Everything starts with
一切都始于
yourself. And you have to be willing to
你自己。你必须愿意
put what it is that you care about, what
把你关心的事情写下来，什么
it is that
正是如此。
you want more than
你想要的不止
anything
任何事物
first. You have to be able to do that
第一的。你必须能够做到这一点。
first. And if you have somebody who
第一的。如果你有这样的人
isn't necessarily like a big
不一定像一个大
cheerleader, which not everybody can be
啦啦队长，但不是每个人都能成为啦啦队长。
for everyone else, that's one thing. But
对其他人来说，那是一回事。但
if you've got someone that sucks your
如果你遇到一个很讨厌你的人
energy and your ability to believe in
能量和你的信念能力
yourself, that's a problem, right? So I
你自己，那也是个问题，对吧？所以，我
don't think that everybody needs the
不要认为每个人都需要
like cheerleader husband, but you need
就像啦啦队长老公一样，但你需要
somebody that at least supports your
至少有人支持你
belief in yourself so that you can go
相信自己，这样你才能前进
off and do what you need to do. But I
离开去做你该做的事。但我
don't know that there's any big secret.
不知道有什么重大秘密。
The secret is just being interested in
秘诀就在于对……感兴趣
each other. The secret is
彼此。秘密在于
just growing together. And I think that
一起成长。而且我认为
we are so fortunate that we've been able
我们非常幸运，能够……
to work with one another, but it comes
彼此合作，但这并非易事。
from like this place of like interest
来自类似这样的地方，有着相似的兴趣
and respect. And I'm interested in the
以及尊重。我对……很感兴趣
person that he was. Is it 16 or 17 years
他本来的样子。是16年还是17年？
ago? I wish I knew. But I'm interested
前？我真希望我知道。但我对此很感兴趣。
in the person that he's becoming. And I
在他正在成为的那个人身上。我
think he's interested in the person I'm
我觉得他对我是感兴趣的人。
becoming.
成为。
Quick one. I want to talk about
简单问一个。我想谈谈……
something we all need to take seriously,
这是我们所有人都需要认真对待的事情。
which is cyber security. Whether you're
这就是网络安全。无论你是
a first-time founder facing your very
一位初次创业者面临着你
first audit or a seasoned professional
首次审计或经验丰富的专业人士
who's been through it all, staying
经历过这一切的人，依然坚守。
compliant is getting more critical than
合规性变得越来越重要
ever and more complicated, I have to
情况变得越来越复杂，我不得不
say. And that is where Vanta comes in,
说。而这正是Vanta的用武之地。
who is a sponsor of this podcast. Vant
谁是本播客的赞助商？范特
takes the pain out of security
减轻安全方面的痛苦
compliance, automating the tedious but
合规性，自动化繁琐但
essential process of proving your
证明你的必要过程
business is secure across over 35
业务在超过 35 个方面都安全可靠
frameworks like SOCK 2, ISO 2701.
诸如 SOCK 2、ISO 2701 等框架。
centralize your workflows, answer
集中管理您的工作流程，回答
security questions up to five times
最多五次安全问题
faster, and protect your business
速度更快，并保护您的业务
without losing focus on growth. And this
在不偏离增长轨道的前提下。而这
is really a critical part of this. A new
这确实是其中至关重要的一部分。新的
IDC white paper found that companies
IDC白皮书发现，公司
using Vant save over
使用 Vant 保存
$535,000 a year, and it pays for itself
每年53.5万美元，而且它能收回成本。
in just 3 months. For a limited time, my
仅用了3个月。在限定时间内，我的
community gets $1,000 off Vanta at
社区成员购买Vanta可享1000美元折扣
vanta.com/stephven. That's
vanta.com/stephven。那是
van.com/stephven for $1,000 off.
访问 van.com/stephven 可享 1000 美元折扣。
So 25 years old, you start ITB. Yes.
所以，25岁的时候，你开始从事ITB工作。是的。
Worldwide. And you run that 25. 24
全世界。你跑了25.24
maybe. Yeah. Something like that for a
或许。是的。类似这样的东西
decade roughly. A decade. A decade of
大约十年。十年。十年
your life up until 35ish.
你35岁左右之前的人生。
And you meet Chris. Yes. Jenna. Yeah. In
然后你遇到了克里斯。是的。珍娜。是的。在
this process of these 10 years, when did
这十年间，这个过程是什么时候开始的？
you meet Chris Jenner? I met her for the
你见过克里斯·詹纳吗？我与她相识于
first time like on a job that I'd done
第一次像我做过的那种工作
for one of the girls. I was actually and
给其中一个女孩。我当时确实在……
I'm sure they must be pretty furious
我敢肯定他们一定非常愤怒。
now. Actually, I was actually introduced
现在。实际上，我其实是被介绍认识的。
through an agent at WMA. They just gave
通过WMA的代理人。他们只是给了
me her number directly, so I just called
直接把她的电话号码发给我，所以我直接打了电话。
her. Why would they be furious now? Cuz
她。他们现在为何如此愤怒？库兹
they Well, you know,
他们，你知道的，
probably, you know, maybe they should
或许，你知道，也许他们应该
have ushered that introduction slightly
略微地引入了这一介绍。
more, but hey ho. Yeah, I just called
还有更多，不过算了。是的，我刚打过电话。
her. At that time, you know, at that
她。那时候，你知道，那时候
time, Chris wasn't the Chris of now. She
那时的克里斯已经不是现在的克里斯了。她
was still extremely famous. I remember
仍然非常有名。我记得
when we went for lunch there um you know
我们去那里吃午饭的时候，嗯，你知道的
there was like a little crowd forming
好像有一小群人正在聚集。
outside but it was very different from
外面的情况与此截然不同。
how it is today. And what was she like
如今的情况就是这样。她是个什么样的人呢？
when you met her? Amazing you know but
你们是什么时候认识的？你知道吗，这太不可思议了。
also like not in that way that when you
也不是那种意义上的喜欢，当你
you go and meet someone for me it was
你去见某人，对我来说就是这样。
just like meeting any other manager,
就像和其他经理见面一样，
agent, publicist and of course it was
经纪人、公关人员，当然还有……
Chris and she was you know on the show
克里斯和她，你知道，都参加了那个节目。
and so I had an understanding of who she
因此，我对她有了一定的了解。
was but also I was trying to get
是，但我也试图得到
something done. you know, I would have
事情已经完成了。你知道，我本来会……
been doing some type of endorsement and
一直在做一些代言之类的工作，
trying to, you know, get some
想，你知道，弄到一些
information about whatever it was that,
关于那件事的信息，
you know, I was working on at the time.
你知道，我当时正在做这件事。
So, it was just like a means to an end
所以，这只是达到目的的手段而已。
wherever I would go at that point in my
无论我当时要去哪里，我的
life. You know, I was meeting with
生活。你知道，我当时正在和……会面
managers, agents, publicists all the
经理人、经纪人、公关人员等等
time. Um, and that was part of my job
时间。嗯，那是我工作的一部分。
and part of what I did on behalf of
以及我代表……所做的一部分工作
brands. What was that journey from
品牌。那段旅程是从哪里开始的呢？
meeting Chris that first time to getting
第一次见到克里斯，就……
into business with Chris and pitching
与克里斯一起做生意并进行推销
her as to be a business partner and then
她必须成为商业伙伴，然后
what happens to ITB the agency you were
ITB，也就是你所在的机构，现在怎么样了？
running in the background? Mhm. So it
在后台运行？嗯。所以它
was a really interesting time for me
对我来说，那真是一段非常有趣的时光。
actually because there was this big
实际上，因为当时有这么大的事。
shift and what I'd done in the agency
转变以及我在机构里所做的事情
was built this you know entertainment
这是娱乐业的产物。
marketing agency and we really kind of
营销机构，我们真的有点像
sat at the intersection of where like
坐在十字路口，就像……
brands and entertainment get together.
品牌与娱乐的融合。
So film product placement, endorsement
所以，电影中的产品植入、代言
deals, influencer packages like and that
优惠、网红套餐等等
was like the very early days of
就像早期阶段一样
influencers. Most of the like we were
影响者。大多数人都和我们一样。
calling them bloggers at that time,
当时称他们为博主
right? So the agency was growing and I'd
正确的？所以公司在发展壮大，而我
opened an office in New York that was
在纽约开设了一家办事处，
really doing like the majority of the
真的像大多数人那样做
business and it was fantastic. So the
生意很好。所以
business become very kind of US-facing
企业对美国市场非常友好
from a client-based point of view. And
从客户的角度来看。和
then this idea of like talentbased
然后，这种基于才能的想法就出现了。
equity deals kind of like raised its
股权交易有点像提高了它的
head. And I read something about Ashton
头。我读到了一些关于阿什顿的文章。
Kutcher taking I don't know equity in
库彻拿走了我不知道的股权
some Silicon Valley startup. And I
一家硅谷创业公司。我
started to get calls and you know people
开始接到电话，你知道，那些人
would always phone me when they wanted
他们想给我打电话的时候总是会打。
to put an alias talent in a fragrance ad
在香水广告中使用化名
for example. But people started calling
例如。但人们开始打电话
me and saying hey we've got this startup
我跟他们说，嘿，我们有个创业公司。
we'd be willing to give X Y and Z 10% of
我们愿意给 X、Y 和 Z 10% 的资金。
this thing for you know for an
你知道，这东西是为了一个
endorsement. And I was like well that's
代言。我当时就想，好吧，就这样吧。
interesting but how do I commission
很有意思，但我该如何委托创作呢？
that? Right? because usually I would be
那？正确的？因为通常我会
getting paid a percentage of whatever
按比例领取报酬
cash was taking was crossing hands. So
现金被交叠着交接。所以
for me it was this new interesting part
对我来说，这是个很有趣的新部分。
of the business that I had to figure out
我必须弄清楚的业务
how to
如何
monetize. So fast forward I did a couple
实现盈利。快进到后来，我做了几个
of deals and instead of you know taking
交易，而不是你知道的，拿
a piece of equity like you know because
就像你知道的那样，一部分股权，因为
at the end of the day my agency wasn't
最终，我的机构并没有
it wasn't in that way shape or form it
事情并非如此。
wasn't figured out that we could like
我们还没意识到我们可能会喜欢
bring equity into the business like
为企业注入股权，例如
where does that go? that wouldn't go to
那东西要放到哪里？那不会发生
me, that would go to this shareholder
对我来说，那笔钱会给这位股东。
base. It would then mean nothing to
根据。那样的话，它就毫无意义了。
anybody. So I was like, do you know
任何人。所以我就问，你知道吗？
what? A flat fee. And so I did a bunch
什么？固定费用。于是我做了很多。
of deals with a bunch of talents and I'd
与众多人才达成交易，而我……
say, you're going to pay me a couple
比如说，你要付我几块钱
hundred,000. I'm going to work out for X
十万。我要去健身 X
to take 10% of your company. And I did
拿走你公司10%的股份。我确实这么做了。
three that were very, very successful.
其中三个非常非常成功。
Then what happened is I kind of sat back
然后，我就有点儿往后靠了靠。
and I was like, "Wow, it's so
我当时就想，“哇，这太……”
interesting." And I remember this
真有趣。”我还记得这件事。
company reporting
公司报告
some just reporting some numbers and I
有些人只是在汇报一些数字，而我
was like I cannot believe that they've
我当时就想，我简直不敢相信他们竟然……
gone from there to there. And in my head
从那里到那里。在我的脑海里
I made a direct correlation between the
我直接建立了两者之间的联系
talent that had been brought into that
被引入到那个领域的人才
company. It was Fel Williams at the time
公司。当时是费尔·威廉姆斯
and I was like wow because Farel did
我当时就想，哇，因为法雷尔确实
this thing the value of the company
这件事就是公司的价值
jumped like this. I got my little couple
像这样跳了起来。我得到了我的小情侣
of hundred grand and wasn't incentivized
十万美元，却没有得到任何激励
and you know by any of the value that
你知道，通过任何一个值，
was created and therefore you know I was
被创造出来，因此你知道我是谁
like god I'm really losing here. Maybe I
天哪，我真的要输了。也许我
should do one of these for myself. Maybe
我也应该做一个。或许
I should create a company and bring a
我应该成立一家公司并带来一家
talent into that company and give them a
把人才招进那家公司，并给他们一个机会
piece of equity in order to accelerate
为了加速发展，获得部分股权
the business. That was the start of Good
这家公司。那是美好事物的开端。
American. That was the initial thought
美国人。那是最初的想法。
because I wasn't getting paid what I
因为我没有拿到我应得的工资
needed to from my clients. So I was like
需要从我的客户那里获得。所以我就想
well who's going to who's going to pay
那么，谁来付钱呢？
me correctly? no one. So, I'll create it
我说的对吗？没有人。所以，我会把它创建出来。
myself. At that time, Yenz and Eric had
我。当时，Yenz 和 Eric 都
started Frame, which is an incredibly
启动了 Frame，这是一个非常
successful denim company. And so, I had
一家成功的牛仔布公司。所以，我当时……
kind of thought in my head that between,
我脑子里闪过这样的想法：
you know, I had clients like Gar and
你知道，我的客户中就有像Gar这样的人。
Calvin Klein and I've worked with
我和卡尔文·克莱恩都合作过
Topshop for a long time, very
Topshop 很长一段时间以来，非常
denimheavy. Yens had um frame. And so, I
牛仔布材质。 Yens有框架。所以，我
was like, I know something about denim.
我当时就想，我对牛仔布略知一二。
Like, that's a category I can do. No,
比如，这是我能胜任的类别。不，
what I knew was denim marketing. I had
我所了解的是牛仔布营销。我曾
no idea about how to make a product. And
完全不知道该如何制作产品。和
then fast forward, I sit down, I sit at
然后快进到后来，我坐了下来，我坐在
a dinner and next to some guy who had
晚餐时，旁边坐着一个男人，他……
invested heavily in a big plus-size uh
大量投资于大码……
retailer in America. And he said to me,
美国零售商。他对我说：
"Emma, this space is exploding." And he
“艾玛，这里快要爆炸了。”而他
was telling me all about it. And I
他把事情的来龙去脉都告诉我了。我
looked on my phone, I looked at the
我看了看手机，我看了看
retailer, and I was like, "That's gross.
零售商，我当时想：“真恶心。”
Nobody wants to dress in those clothes.
没人愿意穿那样的衣服。
That product is horrible." And then
“那个产品太糟糕了。”然后
everything just came together. I was
一切都水到渠成了。我当时
like, "Oh my goodness, I'm going to
比如，“我的天哪，我要……”
create a denim company. I'm going to
创办一家牛仔服装公司。我要
make all of the sizes all the time and
始终生产所有尺寸
I'm going to make everyone look hot.
我要让每个人都看起来很性感。
Buster end off." That was it. I was
“巴斯特结束了。”就这样。我当时
like, "Ding, ding, ding." And it just
就像“叮叮叮”。就这样
came together and I was like, "Oh, and
大家聚在一起，我当时就想，“哦，而且……”
you know what I know how to do? I know
你知道我擅长做什么吗？我知道
how to book talent and bring them into
如何预订人才并将他们带入
the brand and converge all of those
品牌并将所有这些融合起来
things and it's going to be explosive."
事情会变得非常复杂，而且会引发爆炸。
And so the idea was kind of set in my
所以这个想法就这么在我脑海里形成了。
head. And at that point, I'd had the
头。那时，我已经……
conversation with Chris who had said,
与克里斯的对话，他曾说过：
you know, we're looking for these type
你知道，我们正在寻找这类人。
of partnerships now. And so I just went
现在就建立合作伙伴关系。于是我就去了
back to her and I was like, I have an
我回到她身边，然后我说，我有一个
idea and I'd really love it if I could
这个想法我非常希望能够实现。
pitch your daughter. The rest is
推销你的女儿。其余部分是
history. You pitched her? I pitched her.
历史。你向她推销过？我向她推销了。
You pitched Chloe? Mhm. What did Chloe
你向克洛伊推销过？嗯。克洛伊做了什么
say? I don't remember the exact words.
说？我不记得确切的措辞了。
And you know, I never like to It's so
你知道，我从来不喜欢那样。
interesting. We have a great working
有趣的。我们工作非常出色。
relationship, the family and I,
我和家人之间的关系
because I don't speak on their behalf,
因为我不能代表他们发言，
you know, and I'm very careful not to
你知道，我非常小心，不会……
speak on their behalf. And it feels
替他们发言。而且感觉
really unfair because what they are so
真的太不公平了，因为他们是如此
unbelievably famous that anything that
非常有名，任何事物都如此。
you say becomes news. So I prefer never
你说这成了新闻。所以我宁愿永远不
to talk about what she said. What I
谈谈她说过的话。我
remember is the end result is that she
记住，最终结果是她
said yes and you know we're in business
他说“是”，你知道，我们开始做生意了。
together eight years later. What was the
八年后，他们终于在一起了。是什么？
process of making Good America a good
使“美好美国”成为一个好的过程
company in terms of you have that
就你拥有的公司而言，
initial hypothesis when you're sat at
当你坐在那里时，最初的假设是
that dinner. You think, okay, this is
那顿晚餐。你心想，好吧，这是
what it's going to be. It tends to be
它将会是什么样子。它往往是
the case that almost everyone's initial
几乎每个人的最初情况都是如此。
hypothesis is like a little bit wrong.
这个假设似乎有点问题。
Yeah. At least in part. No, it's so
是的。至少部分如此。不，就是这样
interesting actually. That's the that's
真有意思。那就是那个
the thing that we got right. I think
我们做对的那件事。我认为
that what we understood intrinsically is
我们从内心深处理解的是
that there was this huge subset of
存在这样一个庞大的子集
customers that were left out of the
被排除在外的顾客
fashion conversation. if you're above a
时尚话题。如果你高于 a
size 12 that there was almost nothing
12号尺码，几乎什么都没有
cute in the market for you. And what we
市场上有很多可爱的商品等着你。而我们
didn't do was create any separation. We
并没有造成任何隔阂。我们
just like we're going to make 19 sizes
就像我们要生产19种尺寸一样
of clothes. And what happens
衣服。然后会发生什么？
traditionally in most retailers is that
传统上，大多数零售商都是这样做的。
you've got one set of sizes and then you
你有一套尺寸，然后你
go up to floor five and there's this
上到五楼，那里有这个
like horrible little subsection and
就像一个糟糕的小节
you've got bit of, you know, the
你有点，你知道的，
assortment for petite and a bit of the
适合娇小身材和略微丰满身材的各种款式
assortment for plus-siz women and it's
专为大码女性设计的系列，而且是
completely not reflective of what's
完全不能反映事实
downstairs for everybody else. And so we
其他人都在楼下。所以，我们
were like, do you know what? We're just
我们当时就想，你知道吗？我们只是
going to connect all of those things.
我要把所有这些都联系起来。
We're just going to make one product.
我们只打算生产一种产品。
We'll make it in 19 sizes and whatever
我们会做成19种尺寸，等等
we do, we'll let the customers choose.
我们会，我们会让顾客自己选择。
So, if we're making a dress with a giant
所以，如果我们用一个巨大的……来制作一件连衣裙
slit up the side of it, we're not going
从侧面划开一道口子，我们不去了
to moderate it because we think that a
为了缓和这种情绪，我们认为……
girl at a certain size doesn't want the
达到一定身材的女孩不想要
slit as high, cuz you know what? We bet
把缝隙开得尽可能高，因为你知道吗？我们打赌
she does. If we make a teeny tiny
她确实有。如果我们做一个非常小的
fluorescent pink bikini, we're going to
荧光粉色比基尼，我们要去
make it in every size and we'll let the
我们会把它做成各种尺寸，然后让
decision be down to the woman. And it
最终决定权在于女方。而且它
turns out we were 100% right with our
事实证明，我们的判断百分之百正确。
instinct because these girls weren't
出于本能，因为这些女孩并非如此
buying or because they didn't want to
购买或因为他们不想购买
buy it. They weren't buying because it
买吧。他们不买是因为……
wasn't available anywhere. And so our
到处都找不到。所以，我们的
instinct to just like make the stuff and
出于本能，我就想做这些东西。
put it out there and see who comes was
把它发出去，看看谁会来。
the right thing to do. What part of the
这是应该做的。哪一部分
strategy and the games you played in 201
策略以及你在201年玩的游戏
18? 18
18？ 18
could not be replicated now. That was so
目前无法重现。那真是太……
important back then because the the game
当时很重要，因为游戏
is changed so many the game has so
游戏已经发生了如此多的变化。
changed. you know, the arbitrage that
改变了。你知道，套利
existed in social media then, like how
当时社交媒体上就存在这种现象，就像……
you could pay to acquire a customer is
你可以付费获取客户。
almost entirely gone. And so, when I
几乎全部消失了。所以，当我
think about how we could work with
想想我们如何才能与……合作
Facebook and how we could work with
Facebook 以及我们如何与它合作
Instagram, how powerful those followings
Instagram，那些粉丝真是太强大了。
were back then, you can't compare it to
那时候的情况，根本无法与现在相提并论。
now. And so, you could acquire a
现在。因此，你可以获得
customer very cheaply. You could um you
价格非常便宜。你可以……嗯……你
know, I think that the the algorithms
我知道，我认为算法
worked completely differently.
运作方式完全不同。
Therefore, the cohorts in your business
因此，你企业中的同事们
behave completely differently. And if I
行为方式截然不同。如果我
think about it, we had a three-year
想想看，我们有过三年时间
golden period of runway. The good thing
跑道的黄金时代。好事
is I think we knew and I always talk
我想我们都知道，而且我总是谈论它
about the beauty of my board members at
关于我的董事会成员的美貌
that time going back to people like
那段时光可以追溯到像他们这样的人。
Andrew Rosen and John Howard who were
安德鲁·罗森和约翰·霍华德
the total opposite to everybody else on
与其他人完全相反
my board that was like, Emma, you need
我的板子上写着：“艾玛，你需要……”
to just double down, acquire as many
为了加倍下注，尽可能多地收购
customers as possible. don't worry about
尽可能多地服务客户。别担心
profitability. Just spend, spend, spend.
盈利能力。只管花钱，花钱，花钱。
And they were like, absolutely do not do
他们说，绝对不能这样做。
that. You need a profitable business
那。你需要一家盈利的企业
that works when this is over. And so I
等这一切结束了，那才行得通。所以，我
just was like, I'm going to do what
我当时就想，我要做什么？
these guys are telling me. They have a
他们告诉我的。他们有一个
lot of experience. They have a lot of
经验丰富。他们有很多
successful businesses. They've been
成功的企业。他们一直是
doing it for a lot longer. And so I
持续做更长时间。所以，我
think that while we, you know, created a
想想我们，你知道，创造了一个
foundation for the business that was
该企业的基础是
really important, that was rooted in
非常重要，这源于
being digitally native, we never we
作为数字原住民，我们从未想过
never rested on that being the only way
从未认为那是唯一的方法
that we could meet customers. We were
我们可以与客户见面。我们曾
immediately saying, "We've got to open
他立刻说道：“我们必须开业。”
our own stores. We've got to create a
我们自己的门店。我们必须创建一个
wholesale footprint." And when the tide
批发足迹。”而当潮水
turned, which it inevitably did, and
事情果然发生了转变，而且这种转变是不可避免的。
that really happened, you know, COVID
那件事确实发生过，你知道，新冠疫情。
kind of gave you an acceleration, but
它有点像给了你加速，但是
then the falloff was pretty quick. we
然后，下滑速度就很快了。我们
had this buffer of an incredible
拥有如此强大的缓冲作用
business that allowed us to stay the
这项业务使我们能够继续经营下去
course. So if one is, you
课程。所以如果其中一个是，你
know, 2025 and they're trying to deploy
知道，到2025年，他们正试图部署
a strategy to build any kind of brand um
打造任何类型品牌的策略
and they're thinking about the channels.
他们正在考虑各种渠道。
If we think about uh B2C companies, so
如果我们考虑一下B2C公司，那么
things like Good American or it could
比如 Good American 之类的，或者它可能
be, I don't know, an energy drink or
是，我不知道，一种能量饮料，或者
whatever. What what kind of strategy are
任何。是什么类型的策略？
you thinking about now to acquire
你现在考虑购买吗？
customers as being some of the most
顾客是其中最重要的一部分
interesting but maybe unobvious? Yeah, I
有趣，但或许并不显而易见？是的，我
really am blown away by what happens
我真的被发生的一切震惊了。
when you meet customers in real life,
当你在现实生活中遇到客户时，
you know, and I think that some of the
你知道，而且我认为其中一些
more experiential things that we've done
我们做过更多体验性的事情
that stay with people, you know,
那些会留在人们心中的东西，你知道的。
postcoid people want to be together and
患有产后抑郁症的人都想在一起，而且
they want to be in person and they want
他们想亲自到场，他们想要
experience and they want memories and
他们想要体验，也想要留下回忆。
they want things that last and they want
他们想要经久耐用的东西，他们想要
physicality and and what's tangible. And
物质性和有形性。和
so whatever you can do that brings those
所以，无论你做什么，只要能带来这些好处就行。
type of experiences like in real life
类似现实生活中的经历
experience is always going to be out
经验总是会过时的。
anything that is like more digitally
任何更数字化的东西
native. And so a good example of that is
本国的。因此，一个很好的例子是：
we just opened a store on Sunset for
我们刚刚在日落大道开了一家店
Skiims and we connected the store
Skiims 和我们连接了这家商店
opening with this incredible diner next
接下来要介绍的是一家非常棒的餐馆。
door that's like a 24-hour kind of like
就像那种24小时营业的门一样
Hollywood staple diner. There were cues
好莱坞标志性餐厅。有线索
around the block. Every single slot for
绕着街区走一圈。每一个槽位
in the entirety of the six days, and
整整六天，以及
it's 24 hours, was booked within five
24小时内就预订好了，五分钟内就订好了。
minutes. And this is to get pancakes
分钟。这是为了吃煎饼。
and, you know, chicken tenders and like
还有，你知道，鸡柳之类的。
a root beer float. And what was so
根汁汽水漂浮冰淇淋。而那又是什么呢？
interesting to me is I took my kids and
令我感兴趣的是，我带了我的孩子们……
it was so cute. You know, it's like a
它太可爱了。你知道，这就像……
50s diner with a juke box and we
一家 50 年代风格的餐馆，配有点唱机，我们
skimified the whole thing. It looked
粗略浏览了全文。它看起来
amazing. My three-year-old two days
惊人的。我三岁的孩子两天
later said, "I want to go back to the
后来又说：“我想回到……”
cafe." And I was I was like, "You're
咖啡馆。”然后我就想，“你是……”
English? That's so cool." um you want to
英语？太酷了。”嗯，你想……
go to the diner. She's like, "Yeah, I
去餐馆。她回答说：“是啊，我
want to get the thing with the cherry on
想买带樱桃的那件东西
the top." And I was like, "Wow." Like in
“最上面。” 我当时就想，“哇。” 就像在
a three years, three-year-old's head
一个三岁孩子的头
that even like she had an impression of
即使她似乎对……有印象
like that being like a special moment
就像那是一个特别的时刻
and something that stuck in her mind.
还有一些事情一直萦绕在她心头。
And I was like that those type of things
我当时就是这样，喜欢做那种事。
for me are just way more valuable. Now
对我来说，它们更有价值。现在
look, if you're starting a business,
你看，如果你要创业，
it's really hard to do experiential in
在体验式学习中，实践真的很难。
real life things like that. I think the
诸如此类的现实生活琐事。我认为
point is like getting in front of
关键在于抢占先机
customers like getting to them and and
顾客喜欢联系他们，而且
that physicality of being in front of
站在前面的那种身体感受
them and whether that is if you're
他们以及你是否是
starting a new drink like being in the
开始喝一种新饮料，就像身处其中一样
supermarket being in front of like the
超市就在前面，就像
point of purchase like that is really
这样的购买点真的
important to tell your story and have
讲述你的故事很重要，并且要有……
some physicality around what you're
你所拥有的某些物质特性
doing. Are you seeing this idea of
正在做。你明白我的意思吗？
community becoming more and more
社区变得越来越
important for building brands? Because
对品牌建设来说重要吗？因为
you know a couple of years ago it was
你知道，几年前是
all like just throw some Facebook ads at
就像直接投放一些 Facebook 广告一样
them or get some influencers to tell
要么让他们说，要么找一些有影响力的人告诉他们
them about it. Now we're seeing this
告诉他们这件事。现在我们看到了这一点
transition towards like run clubs and
向类似跑步俱乐部的模式过渡
yoga thing with the brand present and
瑜伽活动与品牌合作举办
yeah I think it's I definitely think
是的，我觉得是，我肯定这么认为。
it's community um and I you know when I
这是社区，嗯，你知道，当我
think about what that means um for our
想想这对我们意味着什么
businesses you know often times it's
你知道，很多时候，企业都是如此。
really about
真的关于
like owning that customer experience you
就像拥有那种客户体验一样，你
know it's like if you if you know for
知道这就像如果你知道的话
example Skiims has an app which is like
例如，Skiims 有一个类似这样的应用程序
an incredible place for customers to
对顾客来说，这是一个绝佳的去处
experience the brand and I think there's
体验过这个品牌后，我觉得……
like a lot again it's like there's high
感觉又像很多时候一样，就像有很高的
low ways. There's very very few brands
低洼地带。品牌非常非常少。
that can be successful in an app, right?
这在应用程序中是可以成功的，对吧？
You've got to really have so much brand
你必须拥有非常强大的品牌影响力。
affinity and so much love to that brand
对这个品牌有着深厚的感情和喜爱。
that people will come get off of
人们会来下车
whatever they're doing and like click
无论他们在做什么，比如点击
and be in your app. So, I think that's
并添加到您的应用程序中。所以，我觉得就是这样。
certainly not for everybody. I don't
当然，这并不适合所有人。我不
think that would work for a lot of the
我认为这对很多人来说都行得通。
brands that I'm involved in. But the
我参与的品牌。但是
sense of like standing for something,
有代表某种信念的感觉
having some kind of purpose, galvanizing
具有某种目的，激励
people around something that isn't just
人们围绕着一些不仅仅是……的东西
about your product is is probably the
关于您的产品，可能是
way to go, I think. And and you know,
我觉得做得很好。而且你知道，
Good American has been so successful
Good American 非常成功
because it always stood for something.
因为它总是代表着某种意义。
At the end of the day, we were selling
最终，我们还是卖出去了。
blue jeans and white t-shirts, but
蓝色牛仔裤和白色T恤，但是
people understand why they come to that
人们明白他们为什么会走到这一步。
brand. They understand that there's a
品牌。他们明白存在着
purpose, but you also have to evolve
目的，但你也必须进化
that purpose continuously. And when I
持续朝着这个目的努力。当我
think about where we started eight years
想想我们八年前的起点。
ago and where we are in the middle
过去以及我们现在所处的位置
somewhere we became BC Corp certified
我们在某个地方获得了BC公司认证。
and that was another like real push for
那又是一次真正的推动。
the company it was very very very heavy
这家公司非常非常非常重
lifting but that was something that for
举重，但那是……
our staff became so important to them
我们的员工对他们来说变得非常重要。
you know denim is a tough business to be
你知道牛仔布生意不好做。
in it's a very pollutive business I have
这是一个污染非常严重的行业，我……
a lot of really young people a lot of
很多非常年轻的人，很多
young mothers that work at the company
在该公司工作的年轻妈妈们
and they wanted to know that they worked
他们想知道他们是否有效
in a place that cared about the world
在一个关心世界的地方
that they live And so it really was
他们活着，而事实的确如此。
something that was an undertaking by
这是一项由……发起的事业
that company to say we all feel that we
那家公司表示，我们都觉得我们
could do so much better. And I think
本来可以做得更好。我觉得
that the underlying values of that
那是其潜在价值观。
company are about it being about our
公司的核心在于我们
customers and the people that work for
客户和员工
work there and whatever is true to them
在那里工作，做任何对他们来说真实的事情。
being the most important thing. And so
是最重要的事。所以
that has really evolved over time. How
随着时间的推移，它确实发生了很大的变化。如何
old are you here in this photo? I must
照片里的你年纪大了吗？我必须
be well. Okay. So if Katie is she looks
祝您一切安好。好的。所以如果凯蒂是她，她看起来
like I must be 16. 16. 15. No. 15. 15.
好像我一定是16岁。16岁。15岁。不。15岁。15岁。
Oh yeah. Yeah. A
哦，是的。是的。一个
if you were to speak to this Emma and
如果你和这位艾玛交谈，
this Emma was keen to start a business
这位艾玛很想创业。
and she came to you and said, "What are
她走到你面前说：“你好吗？”
the like first principles of business?
类似于商业的基本原则？
What are the the the three most
最……的三个
important things in being successful in
成功的关键因素
business that you've learned in your
你在商业领域学到的东西
decades now of wisdom and experience?
几十年的智慧和经验积累？
What what would you take to say to her?"
你想对她说些什么？
A bless her. Well, I'd say I love your
愿上帝保佑她。嗯，我想说我爱你
curly hair first of all. Um, it's not a
首先，我的头发是卷发。嗯，这不是一个
bad place to start actually
实际上，这真是一个糟糕的开始。
because I would say that it's so
因为我会说，它是如此
important to be true to yourself in
忠于自己很重要
whatever you do. And, you know, I think
无论你做什么。你知道，我觉得
that I have an incredible gut instinct
我拥有惊人的直觉。
and I have very strong feelings that
我强烈地感觉到这一点。
guide the decisions that I make and that
指导我做出的决定，以及
has really led me so well. So, I'd be
他真的给了我很好的指导。所以，我会是
like have conviction about what it is
就像对它是什么有坚定的信念一样
that you feel deeply and go and go with
你内心深处感受到了，并且一直坚持下去。
that. But by the same token, I'd say
那。但同样地，我想说
know what you don't know because there's
要知道自己不知道什么，因为总有未知领域。
a lot of places where I'm weak. And one
我有很多弱点。还有一个
of my greatest strengths and a
我最大的优势之一
superpower of mine has been know what
我的超能力一直为人所知。
you don't know and hire people into the
你不知道，却雇佣了这些人。
kind of gaps and the holes that you have
各种缝隙和孔洞
in your own knowledge. That's been
以你自己的认知。那是……
really important for me. And it's I I
对我来说非常重要。是我
feel like I'm so privileged that I've
我觉得自己非常幸运，因为我……
worked with people in one company and
与一家公司的人一起工作
been able to bring them into another
能够将它们带到另一个
company and another and I start almost a
公司和另一家，我几乎开始了
lot of things with like a similar group
很多东西都和类似的群体有关
of people and I love that because they
这些人，我喜欢这一点，因为他们
fill in for where I'm not so good. Um,
请你弥补我的不足。嗯，
and that's been really key. And then
而这才是关键所在。进而
despite everything you've been
尽管你经历了这一切
told, you're going to have to take some
被告知，你得接受一些
risks. And I think that everything that
风险。我认为所有这些
this kid knew was like don't be risky.
这孩子明白的道理是：不要冒险。
Don't take any risks. Like figure
不要冒任何风险。像个
everything out and be really safe. And
所有东西都拿出来，一定要注意安全。和
what I've learned is
我学到的是：
that nothing is going to come easy. And
没有什么是轻而易举就能得到的。和
I think that when I moved here, I moved
我觉得我搬到这里的时候，我就搬走了
to America with a 2-year-old and a
带着一个两岁的孩子和一个婴儿去美国
newborn baby. And I had no friends here,
新生儿。我在这里没有朋友。
not like real friends. And it was a
不像真正的朋友。那是一个
really scary move because you move away
真是个可怕的举动，因为你要搬走
from you know you forget when you move
你知道，搬家后你会忘记。
country you move from all senses of what
你移居的国家，从所有意义上来说，是什么
is familiar to you and that's
你很熟悉这一点，那就是
very it's very difficult in any stage of
在任何阶段都非常困难
your life but there's a special
你的生活，但有一种特殊之处
vulnerability that comes along with
伴随而来的脆弱性
having a new baby and having a new
有了新生儿，又有了新生命
venture that you don't really understand
你并不真正理解的冒险
how to run at the time and so I would
当时该如何跑，所以我会
say like learning to take risks has
比如说，学会承担风险已经
probably been the best thing that I've
这可能是我做过的最好的事。
done. How do you feel about her?
完毕。你对她有什么感觉？
Oh, you know, I think she's so cute and
哦，你知道吗，我觉得她好可爱，
so lovely. You know, I don't like I feel
太可爱了。你知道，我不喜欢这种感觉。
like that's, you know, I still look
就像那样，你知道，我仍然会这样看
exactly the same, don't I? Yeah, you do.
完全一样，不是吗？是的，你确实有。
You know, like I feel like this person
你知道，感觉就像这个人
was like dying, like dying
就像死亡，就像死亡
to dying to just do something
渴望做点什么
differently and dying to escape her
截然不同，她渴望逃离她
circumstances.
情况。
Some of the skills that I think you have
我认为你具备的一些技能
that are unappreciated. One of them is
那些不被赏识的人。其中之一是
the ability to articulate an idea and
表达想法的能力和
some people call this like sales. How
有些人把这称为销售。如何
critical do you think it is for for
你认为这很重要吗？
women, for men, for everybody to
女性，为了男性，为了所有人
cultivate that particular skill and how
培养这项特定技能的方法
did how did you cultivate it? Oh, I I
你是如何培育它的？哦，我
think it's one of the most important
我认为这是最重要的事情之一。
things. You know, when I think about who
事物。你知道，当我想到谁
I am investing in, when I think about
当我想到投资时，我意识到
what businesses to support, I don't care
支持哪些企业，我不在乎。
if a founder has a lot of missing
如果创始人有很多缺失
pieces, but if you can't sell, you ain't
作品是可以有的，但如果卖不出去，你就什么都不是。
getting my money. Like, no way. Like,
拿到我的钱了。不可能。喜欢，
it's just no way. You can't you can't
绝对不可能。你不能，你不能
outsource that stuff. You either have an
把这些事外包出去。你要么拥有
ability to convince somebody of what
能够说服某人接受什么
you're doing and sell your idea uniquely
你要做的，以及你推销的，都是独一无二的。
or you don't. And I've never invested in
或者你不这么做。我从未投资过
any founders that didn't have that as a
任何没有把这一点作为创业目标的创始人
skill that couldn't bring me on a
这项技能无法让我获得……
journey and tell me their story and
踏上旅程，讲述他们的故事
convince me that this was something that
让我相信这是件……
the world needed. How do you sell? So,
世界需要。你如何销售？所以，
if you were selling something to me,
如果你要卖东西给我，
what what are the core what would you be
核心是什么？你会是什么？
thinking about as you're preparing that
在准备的时候要考虑到这一点
pitch and putting it together? Oh,
提案和整合？哦，
you'll see. You're just so much more
你会看到的。你远不止如此。
thoughtful than I am. I would just I
比我更深思熟虑。我只想
would be so you know like my whole thing
就是这样，你知道，就像我的整个过程一样。
is like I have to be passionate about
就好像我必须对某事充满热情一样。
the thing that I'm doing. I have to like
我正在做的事情。我必须喜欢
see the need. I have to figure out the
认识到这种需求。我必须弄清楚
like what am I solving for and then I go
比如，我要解什么方程，然后我就……
in on that. I'm like, you know, I'm I'm
我也参与其中。我就像，你知道，我，我
painting the picture of like where the
描绘出一幅画面，就像……
problem sits and then I'm showing you
问题就在这里，然后我给你展示一下。
how I've uniquely come up with the
我是如何独创地想出这个办法的
solution. And then I'm, you know, I I'm
解决方案。然后我就，你知道，我，我
like old school, right? It's like I
像老派的做法，对吧？就像我
create a value proposition. And I'm all
创造价值主张。我全都
about like the perfect place for pricing
这里简直是定价的理想之地。
and then it's like I'm going to get it
然后我就感觉自己要成功了。
to you in a a unique way. But I don't
以一种独特的方式送给你。但我没有
think it's like so complicated. I'm I'm
我觉得这太复杂了。我 我
I'm like a born saleserson. That's just
我天生就是个推销员。那只是
who I am. When you reference this, you
我是谁。当你提到这一点时，你
touch your chest a lot. Oh, do I? No,
多摸摸胸口。哦，是吗？不，
no, but it's interesting to me. That's
不，但我对此很感兴趣。那是
what I'm saying. So intuition, feeling.
我说的就是这个意思。所以，直觉，感觉。
Yeah. And I do get that from you that I
是的。我确实从你那里得到了这一点。
think you've cultivated the trust with
你认为你已经建立了与对方的信任
your intuition which obviously took some
你的直觉显然花了一些时间。
time because I remember the comment
因为我记得那条评论，所以才有了时间。
Yen's made to you said you're acting
燕子跟你说你在演戏
like an employee. You need to like it
就像一名员工一样。你需要喜欢它
almost sounded like trust yourself a bit
听起来有点像是在说“相信自己”。
more so you can call the shots.
这样你就能掌握主动权。
Is that something we cultivate? And and
这是我们需要培养的吗？而且
how how do we know whether to trust our
我们如何知道是否应该信任我们
intuition? Because so many people like
直觉？因为很多人喜欢
their intuition is trying to say
他们的直觉想说的是
something to them and maybe they like
对他们来说，这或许是件好事，他们可能喜欢。
gaslight themselves and tell themselves
自我欺骗，并告诉自己
or other people tell them to to sort of
或者其他人告诉他们要这样做
dim down that internal voice. How have
压低你内心的声音。如何才能
you learned to get that conviction to
你学会了如何获得那种信念
act upon feeling?
付诸行动？
How have I learned to act upon feeling?
我是如何学会根据自己的感受采取行动的？
Well, I guess there's an element of
嗯，我想这里面确实存在某种因素。
doing it and turning out to be right.
这么做了，结果证明是对的。
But I think that you've got to know the
但我认为你必须了解
difference
不同之处
between having intuition and a gut
直觉和本能之间
feeling and then just sort of general
感觉，然后就是一些总体情况。
excitement and being able to separate
兴奋和能够分离
those things cuz I get really excited
那些东西让我非常兴奋
about things, right? And I'll be like,
关于事情，对吧？然后我就会想，
"Oh my god, that's amazing." And it's so
“我的天哪，太棒了！”真是如此
interesting because when you sit on a
有趣的是，当你坐在……
show like, you know, Dragon's Den or
比如像《龙穴》之类的节目，你知道的。
Shark Tank, like you really need to
《创智赢家》，你真的需要吗？
learn like very quickly to separate
学会很快地分离
those feelings. And so that that helped
那些感觉。所以这很有帮助。
me a little bit. But I think that that
我有点儿。但我认为……
is the like is it coming from a place
就像它来自某个地方一样
that kind of hits you in your heart spot
那感觉直击你的内心深处。
or are you just feeling like some sense
或者你只是感觉有点不对劲
of excitement? And that that is two very
兴奋吗？而这非常
different things for me. Like are you
对我来说，情况就不同了。你是吗？
are you moving me emotionally or am I
你让我感动了吗？还是我？
just like oh that feels like money over
就像，哦，感觉就像钱花光了一样。
there. It's like that looks like it's
那里。看起来就像是……
going to chop up into some you know nice
准备切成一些你知道的美味佳肴
dividends at some point. That's that's
总有一天会分红。就是这样。
not how I make decisions. It's like I
这不是我做决定的方式。就像我
never I never go that way with that sort
我绝不会那样做。
of general excitement of something to
对某事普遍感到兴奋
that's going to be like more financially
那将更像是财务方面的事情
exciting for me. They never work out.
这让我很兴奋。他们从来就没成功过。
Have you thought much about as you look
你有没有仔细想过，当你看着……的时候
back through your career and now you
回顾你的职业生涯，现在你
have the clarity of hindsight how
事后诸葛亮的清晰视角
important the size of one's dreams are
梦想的大小很重要
because I imagine that if you spoke to
因为我猜想，如果你和……
that Emma now you'd be like like listen
艾玛，你现在应该会像这样听着吧
go [__] hell like dream [__] big
去他妈的，做个他妈的远大梦
like it's going to you know and I I was
就像它会变成你知道的那样，而我当时
I think it was when I heard about how we
我想那是在我听说我们如何
work took investment in the back of a
这项工作需要投资。
car from Mash what's his name son
来自《陆军野战医院》的汽车，他叫什么名字来着？儿子
something from Soft Bank the big like
软银集团旗下的某家大型公司
billionaire investor and he gave the we
亿万富翁投资者，他给了我们
work founder a billion dollar check and
给创始人一张十亿美元的支票
said you know the only problem with you
你说你知道你唯一的问题是什么
is you don't dream big enough. He just
是因为你梦想不够远大。他只是
given him a billion dollars and he was
给了他十亿美元，他就
criticizing him for not asking for more.
批评他没有提出更多要求。
And as I reflect back through my career
当我回顾我的职业生涯时，我意识到这一点。
I go Jesus Christ like so many moments I
我常常想起耶稣基督，就像很多时候一样。
like undersold myself because I just
感觉自己低估了自己，因为我就是
like couldn't see it. I didn't have the
就像看不见一样。我没有
friends. Yeah. What happened in the end
朋友们。是的。最后发生了什么
of that story right Steven? Yeah yeah
史蒂文，你讲的是那个故事吧？是啊是啊
but still like listen this guy walked
但还是像听着，这家伙走了
away with a billion dollars even he did
即使他卷走了十亿美元，他仍然这么做了。
he did all right. He did all right but
他做得还不错。他做得还不错，但是
you know it's like I'm I'm not investing
你知道，就好像我没有投资一样。
in his next thing a year. He's just
在他接下来的一年里。他只是
raised 250 million. I saw it. I saw it.
筹集了2.5亿美元。我看到了。我看到了。
I I can't believe people are just
我简直不敢相信人们竟然会这样
walking back into that. But there you
重新回到那个场景中。但是，你
go. The the thing that put in my mind
去。让我想到这件事
was actually that you know that whole
实际上，你知道，那整个过程
adage of like aim for the cloud like aim
就像瞄准云端一样，就像瞄准一样
for the stars and you land on the
为了星星，你降落在
clouds, whatever. I was like there's
云，随便吧。我当时就想，这下糟了。
truth to this idea of just like aiming
这个想法确实有道理，就像瞄准一样。
higher. Yeah. I think there is some
更高。是的。我认为有一些
truth to it. I mean, look, I I don't
确实如此。我的意思是，你看，我没有
know that I even
我知道我甚至
had an idea of how high high was, you
你大概知道“高”到底有多高吧。
know, and I think that it's perspective
我知道，我认为这是一种视角问题。
and your environment that gives you an
以及你所处的环境，它赋予你
idea of like what is high, you know? I
你知道，就是那种“高”的概念。我
often talk about this idea, you you
你经常谈到这个想法，你
can't be what you don't see. And for me,
你看不见的东西，不可能存在。对我而言，
I don't think that I had a lot of role
我觉得我并没有扮演太多角色。
models and being in England at that
模特，而且当时还在英国
time, it just wasn't like who was there
时间，只是当时在场的人不一样。
like do you know what I mean? Like I
你明白我的意思吗？就像我
don't remember anybody being
不记得当时有人在
particularly like you know I I I kind of
特别是你知道我有点
honed in on Oprah because she was on the
之所以关注奥普拉，是因为她当时正在……
TV when I would come home from school
我放学回家的时候经常看电视。
and I was like that is aspirational.
我当时就想，这真是令人向往。
There's a black woman who reads all
有一位黑人女性，她阅读所有书籍。
these books that has these crazy ideas
这些书里充满了疯狂的想法
around gratitude and at the time she you
围绕着感恩，在她和你在一起的时候
know she was talking a lot about um
我知道她一直在谈论……
manifesting and it wasn't mindfulness
显化，但这并非正念。
meditation right but that then kind of
对，冥想是对的，但那样就有点……
moved in to mindfulness but the exposure
开始接触正念，但暴露
to those ideas to me at that time it
当时那些想法对我来说……
felt fresh and new and I was like I am
感觉焕然一新，就像我本人一样
going to watch Oprah and I'm going to be
我要去看奥普拉脱口秀，我打算……
like Oprah in my way of thinking not
在我看来，就像奥普拉那样，不是吗？
that I wanted to be on TV but it's like
我以前想上电视，但感觉就像……
that's the type of level of thought I
这就是我所处的思维层次。
wanted I wanted to be thoughtful and
我想，我想体贴周到，而且
articular and and and move like Oprah
关节，而且，像奥普拉一样动起来
because I thought she'd moved good. So
因为我觉得她搬家搬得很好。所以
when it comes to like your dreams and
当谈到你的梦想时，
your ambitions for me I think that
我认为你对我的期望是
they've maybe aside from the
除了……之外，他们或许还有……
visualization side of things where I
在可视化方面，我
like drew this beautiful home for me
就像为我画了这栋美丽的房子一样
they've always been a little bit more
他们总是稍微多一点。
bite-sized. It's been like let's get out
一口大小。感觉就像是，我们赶紧离开吧。
of this place, get out of plasau, then
离开这个地方，离开普拉绍，然后
let's like get a job and surround
比如找份工作，然后围绕着它
yourself with the right people and then
让自己与合适的人在一起，然后
like and you know it's all been very
就像，你知道，这一切都非常
kind of like much more incremental and I
更像是循序渐进的过程，而且我
always think about this idea of how I've
我一直在思考我是如何……
leveraged everything that I've had into
我充分利用了我所拥有的一切
the next thing and I'm pretty good at
接下来这件事，我做得相当不错。
doing that. I'm I have grand plans that
这样做。我有一些宏伟的计划，
I started writing when I was 30, but
我30岁才开始写作，但是
they're much more theoretical about how
他们对如何进行理论探讨要多得多。
I want to feel and how I want to be
我想感受，也想成为我想成为的人。
spending my time as opposed to like what
我把时间花在了其他事情上，而不是像……
will I be doing at that moment. One of
那一刻我会做什么？之一
the things you said over and over again
你一遍又一遍地说的那些话
as well when talking about building
谈到建筑时也是如此。
business is hiring and how important
企业正在招聘，以及招聘的重要性
that is to you. Um it's taken me a long
那对你来说。嗯，这花了我很长时间
time, longer than I would have liked to
时间比我预想的要长。
realize the importance of hiring. In my
认识到招聘的重要性。在我的
first business, I think it was an
我想，我的第一家公司是……
afterthought. I thought most important
事后补充。我认为最重要的是
things are if I work seven days a week
如果我一周工作七天，情况就不同了。
and I don't leave this office and I have
我不会离开这个办公室，而且我有
good ideas, we'll be good. Yeah. Not so
好主意，我们会成功的。是的。并非如此
much. Not scalable. Yeah. And you learn
很多。不具备可扩展性。是的。然后你就会明白
the hard way. You learn the hard way
走最艰难的路。你得付出惨痛的代价才能学到东西。
because you start hiring your friends
因为你开始雇佣你的朋友
and you go off vibes, etc. So the hiring
然后你会根据感觉等等来判断。所以招聘就是这样。
advice that you needed at the start of
你在开始时需要的建议
your career that would have helped you
你的职业生涯本可以帮助你
to make less mistakes. What is that
减少错误。那是什么？
advice? The hiring advice was learn to
建议？招聘建议是学习如何
fire. Oh, really? Well, that's what you
火。哦真的吗？嗯，那就是你
know because I think that what happens
我知道，因为我认为发生的事情
in businesses is the people that get you
在商业领域，最重要的就是那些真正了解你的人。
to 10 million are not the people that
1000万并非指……
get you to 100 million. The people get
让你达到1亿。人们得到
you to 100 million are not the people
你们这些人，包括1亿人，都不是普通人。
get you to 500 and then to a billion.
先让你达到 500，然后再达到 10 亿。
And so what happens is as a founder you
所以，作为创始人，你就会遇到这种情况：
get so um you know you know what it's
所以，嗯，你知道，你知道那是什么。
like like that startup vibe, those early
就像那种创业氛围，那些早期阶段
people, the work that they do and the
人们，他们所做的工作以及
times you have together that all becomes
你们在一起的时光，最终都会变成……
like so much part of your success story,
就像你成功故事中的很多部分一样，
right? And if you hold on to that for
正确的？如果你坚持下去
too long, you kind of miss what is next
时间太长，你会错过接下来的内容。
and you miss that ability to be able to
你会失去那种能力。
pivot and to level up. And so I think
转型升级。所以我认为
that the mistakes that I made early on
我早期犯下的错误
were not moving people out of the
并没有将人们迁出
business quickly enough. And so because
业务进展迅速。所以，因为
because I just didn't want to fire them.
因为我就是不想解雇他们。
I was so lo cuz I have loyalty and I'm
我当时很伤心，因为我忠诚，而且我是
like such a nice girl and I was like I
她真是个很不错的女孩，我当时就想……
you just needed to go and I didn't want
你只是想走，而我不想。
to I didn't want to say that. And what
我本来不想说那些话。还有什么
was the harm that they did by staying or
他们留下造成的伤害是什么？
by you and Oh, we it restricted my
被你和哦，我们限制了我的
growth. it restricted my ability to be
生长。它限制了我的能力
able to move up and level up and have
能够晋升和升级，并且拥有
better clients. And you know, you you
更优质的客户。你知道，你
don't know what you don't know until
直到你意识到自己不知道什么，你才会明白。
it's like right in front of you. And so
它就在你眼前。所以
I needed to keep a as the as the
我需要保持……
business grew, you need to keep
业务增长了，你需要保持
constantly upleveling your people. And
不断提升员工能力。和
so that's what I that's what I missed.
所以这就是我错过的。
So if I could bring that old Emory in
所以如果我能把那个老埃默里带进来就好了
that didn't want to fire and I sat her
她不想开枪，我就让她坐下。
here, what would you say to her? Because
你会对她说些什么？因为
I asked this because I know cuz kids
我问这个问题是因为我知道孩子们
come up to me all the time saying this
他们总是走过来跟我说这些话
that there are so many people who can
有那么多人可以
relate who can relate. Can relate. Oh,
能感同身受的人才能感同身受。感同身受。哦，
no doubt. You know, people pleasing.
无疑。你知道，就是讨好别人。
We're a family. Yeah. No, we're not a
我们是一家人。是的。不，我们不是
family. We're not a family. And that's
家庭。我们不是一家人。就是这样。
the first thing. It's like I think
第一件事。我觉得
everybody really needs to understand
每个人都真的需要理解
like why they are there. And this is
比如他们为什么会在那里。这就是
about leadership style, right? Like are
关于领导风格，对吧？就像
you clear in what you're all there to
你们都清楚自己来这里的目的。
do? Because it's like I am not building
做？因为感觉就像我没有在建造什么。
a family. I am here to run an
一个家庭。我来这里是为了主持一个
organization. That organization is here
组织。那个组织在这里
to create a profit. And we all have to
创造利润。我们都必须这样做。
be very very clear about our goals and
务必非常清楚地了解我们的目标，
how we're getting there. And I think
我们如何实现目标。我觉得
that in the past what happens and
过去发生的事情以及
especially when you have successful
尤其是在你取得成功的时候
companies, success masks a lot of
公司的成功掩盖了很多问题
problems in a business, right? Like and
企业遇到问题，对吧？点赞和
when you get successful, you've got to
当你成功时，你必须
allow yourself and your team to be
允许自己和你的团队
equally critical. Even when everything's
同样至关重要。即使一切都……
going well and even if the bottom line's
一切顺利，即使最终结果是
well, there'll still be dysfunction
嗯，功能失调依然会发生。
within that organization and you can't
在那个组织内部，你不能这样做。
let the success masked what that
让成功掩盖了真相。
dysfunction is, you've got to get into
功能障碍是指，你必须进入
it. And actually, it's even more
它。实际上，情况甚至更糟。
important when you are successful that
当你成功时，这一点很重要。
you deal with those things because
你之所以要处理这些事情，是因为
otherwise the problems get bigger and
否则问题会越来越大。
bigger as the company gets bigger and
随着公司规模的扩大而增大
bigger and you end up with a problem
规模越大，最终就会出现问题。
that you could have stamped out much
你本可以消灭很多东西。
earlier on that you then didn't. So,
之前你没有。所以，
it's just a really key thing and it's a
这真的是一件非常关键的事情，而且是……
muscle. It's like anything you get
肌肉。就像你得到的任何东西一样
better at this like all the time. I've
一直以来都做得更好。我已经
become better and better at spotting who
越来越擅长发现谁
are the right people and inevitably
是合适的人选，而且不可避免地
actually I spend more and more of my
事实上，我花在身上的时间越来越多
time bringing the right people into the
是时候把合适的人招进来了。
company. I reckon we were talking about
公司。我想我们当时在谈论……
this the other day. I think it's like 20
这是前几天发生的事。我觉得大概是20
maybe even 25% of my time is spent on
或许我25%的时间都花在了……
talent and and and cultivating like the
才能和培养就像
right people to come into the company.
需要合适的人才加入公司。
It's a lot of time. It's a lot of time.
时间很长。时间很长。
It's a lot of time. Oh my god. But
时间很长。我的天啊。但
that's the difference between good and
这就是好与坏的区别
great. 100% agree that who you bring in
伟大的。 100%同意你引进的人
you know when we talk about culture in a
你知道，当我们谈论文化的时候
company culture is like who you hire who
公司文化就像你雇佣谁一样。
you fire and who gets promoted now that
你解雇了别人，现在谁会升职？
is my job that's my decisions to make
这是我的工作，这是我的决定。
within the organization and so I really
在组织内部，所以我真的很
think about how how much more thoughtful
想想如何才能更加深思熟虑
can I be about those decisions and the
我可以参与这些决定吗？
majority of that is put in like who I
大部分内容都像“我是谁”这样放进去的。
hire. So on that point then how does one
聘请。那么，关于这一点，一个人该如何做呢？
get truly exceptional people to come and
邀请真正杰出的人才前来。
join them? And I I say this because you
加入他们？我之所以这么说，是因为你
know in the last 5 years I've become
我知道在过去的五年里，我已经变成了
increasingly obsessed with hiring. It's
越来越痴迷于招聘。它是
like my your team will tell you I feel
就像我的团队会告诉你的那样，我感觉
like I'm the head of recruitment. I
就好像我是招聘主管一样。我
built the process sign off everybody
建立流程并签字确认所有人
that joins every company obsessing about
这使得每家公司都痴迷于此。
it. Building tools myself in my bedroom
它。我在卧室里自己制作工具
to make our like the screening process
为了让我们的筛选过程更顺利。
that I talked about built it myself.
我之前说过，那是我自己建造的。
It's my absolute obsession because I now
我对此完全着迷，因为我现在
have the clarity of hindsight where I
事后看来，我看得更清楚了。
go, "Oh my god, my net worth and my
走吧，“我的天哪，我的净资产和我的
outcomes can be correlated to like 10
结果可能与 10 等因素相关
exceptional people that I brought into
我引进的优秀人才
my ecosystem 10 years ago and the
我的生态系统在10年前和
downstream impact of them hiring more
他们招聘更多员工的后续影响
exceptional people, etc." So this So,
杰出人士等等。”所以，就这样。
but me and you're in a different place
但你我处境不同。
now. And if you go back to when you
现在。如果你回到过去……
first started your agency all those
首先，你创办了你的代理公司，所有这些
years ago,
几年前，
you didn't have the same leverage. Oh,
你没有同样的筹码。哦，
no way. So if you're a startup founder
决不。所以，如果你是一位创业公司创始人
now and they agree with this principle
现在他们也认同这一原则。
that hiring is so critical, a players
招聘如此重要，球员们也深有体会。
really matter, how do they go about like
真的很重要，他们是如何做的？
how would you go about now getting
你现在打算如何获取
exceptional people to come and join
欢迎杰出人士加入
Emma's company? Yeah. Well, Stephen,
艾玛的公司？是的。斯蒂芬，
that's the reason that you've got to be
这就是你必须……的原因
a great salesperson otherwise I'm not
我不是一个优秀的销售员，否则我就不是。
going to invest in you. But it comes
我会投资在你身上。但它来了
back down to that, right? Because in the
最终还是会回到那种状态，对吧？因为在
beginning, you've got to sell a dream, a
一开始，你得兜售一个梦想，一个
vision. You might be willing to give
想象。你或许愿意付出
someone some equity, but chances are
有人获得了一些股权，但可能性不大。
that equity is worth zilch in the
那笔股权在……中一文不值。
beginning. So, you've got to be that
开始。所以，你必须成为那样的人。
person that can say, "Here's where we're
能够说出“我们现在的情况是……”的人
going. We're going to paint a vision,
去。我们将描绘一幅愿景，
but you got to have the strategic chops
但你必须具备战略眼光。
to say, you know, anybody good is going
也就是说，你知道，任何优秀的人都会离开。
to understand that a founder alone goes
要理解，创始人独自一人
nowhere, right?" So, it's like what am I
“哪儿也没有，对吧？”所以，我到底是什么？
coming into? Like, if it's the founder
进来了吗？比如，如果是创始人的话。
and it's like very little, then what's
而且数量很少，那又如何呢？
the vision that I'm buying into and
我所认同的愿景以及
what's the strategy to get there? So, it
实现目标的策略是什么？所以，它
comes back down to this like idea of
归根结底，就是这种想法……
like, can you sell a vision? Can you
比如，你能推销一种愿景吗？你可以吗
sell the strategy these people are going
推销这些人正在采取的策略
to come into and actually work towards?
真正投入其中并努力实现？
And I think that that is probably like
我觉得那大概就像
the thing that I'm good at after. I've
我擅长的事。我已经
had a pretty clear idea about what I'm
我对自己是什么有一个相当清晰的想法
doing. And I can do that because I don't
正在做。我能做到这一点，是因为我没有
do very much. Everybody always says to
做了很多事。每个人都总是说
me, "How do you do so much?" It's like,
我问：“你是怎么做到这么多的？”就像，
"I don't do very much. What I do is
“我没做什么特别的事。我所做的是……”
obsessed over the customer. I obsess
以顾客为中心。我着迷了。
over a set of products and then I get
超过一系列产品后，我就会……
them to them really quickly. That's it.
很快就把它们送到他们那里。就是这样。
Like that's all I do. And so it's not
好像我除了做这个就什么都不做了。所以，事实并非如此。
really that much that I do. And I think
我真的就做了这么多。我觉得
that it's like so so so important for
这真的非常非常重要
you to be able to do very very very few
你必须能够做非常非常非常少的事情
things really really well. I think
一切都非常顺利。我认为
that's it really goes against what a lot
这与很多人的看法截然相反。
of startup founders think they have to
创业公司创始人认为他们必须
be doing because they think they have to
这样做是因为他们认为自己必须这样做。
be good at everything. No. No. I think I
样样精通。不，不，我想我
I honestly think it's the opposite. And
我个人认为恰恰相反。和
I think that if you start to tell
我认为如果你开始讲述
yourself that it's a slippery slope
你自己也意识到这是一个危险的滑坡
because no one is good at everything,
因为没有人擅长所有事情。
right? You've got to find people that
正确的？你必须找到那些
have expertise that can do things that
具备能够完成以下事情的专业知识
you can't do. And that can be really
你不能这样做。而且这可能真的
difficult in the beginning, but again,
一开始很难，但是，
it's like you have to have it's like so
就好像你必须拥有它一样。
much of it is about curiosity, asking as
很多时候都与好奇心有关，喜欢提问。
many questions as you can so you can
尽可能多地提问，这样你就可以……
start to figure out who is going to be
开始弄清楚谁会是
the best person to solve that problem.
最适合解决这个问题的人。
in the beginning like I just feel like I
一开始，我感觉自己就像……
had no idea how so many parts of my
我完全不知道我的很多部分是如何形成的。
business worked but it's like I would
生意做对了，但感觉就像我会……
make sure that I would be the person to
确保我就是那个人
ask enough questions to get to the point
多问问题，直到说到重点。
where I could hire somebody that would
我可以在哪里雇佣一个
be competent to do that role right so
要有能力胜任这个角色，所以
it's like you train yourself and you you
就像你训练自己一样，你
train these muscles that get you better
锻炼这些肌肉，让你变得更好
at hiring and you're going to make some
在招聘过程中，你将做出一些贡献。
mistakes like I I never feel like we
像我这样的错误，我从来没有感觉我们
spend enough time talking about failure
花足够的时间谈论失败
about the mistakes I've made so many
关于我犯下的那么多错误
mistakes. I moved a whole bunch of
错误。我搬走了一大堆
people here to LA and shut the office
来洛杉矶的人都关了办公室
down 18 months later cuz I was I thought
18个月后我倒下了，因为我当时是这么想的。
I had something that I just didn't have.
我拥有了我原本没有的东西。
I thought that the reputation I'd built
我以为我建立起来的声誉……
in London would translate to LA. What I
在伦敦，就相当于洛杉矶。我
didn't understand is LA is a community
我不明白洛杉矶是一个社区
and I wasn't part of it. You know, it
而我并没有参与其中。你知道，它
was like a closed door. I got here and I
就像一扇紧闭的门。我到了这里，然后我
was like, "What?" like I like just
我当时就想：“什么？”我喜欢这样
frozen frozen out completely like like
完全冻住了，就像……
that. Yeah. Yeah. They're not like us
那。是的。是的。他们和我们不一样。
like this is it. So you know and it
就是这样。所以你知道，而且
really was and so I think that you know
确实如此，所以我想你知道
learning like not just understanding
学习不仅仅是理解
okay I had this thing it went wrong but
好吧，我之前有个东西出了点问题，但是
it's like really going deep and being
这就像真正深入其中一样。
like where and how did I fail and how do
比如我在哪里、怎么失败了，以及如何……
I consistently get better at that and
我在这方面一直在进步，
staffing is one of those things that you
人员配备是那种你……的事情之一
just get better and better and better at
就是要越来越好，越来越好。
it the more you do it. I'm really
你做得越多，就越喜欢。我真的
obsessed about this idea of like truly
痴迷于这种“真正”的想法
exceptional people and truly exceptional
杰出的人才，真正杰出的人。
people. Yeah. Like truly exceptional
人们。是的。真是非凡之作
people. I was I was listening to
人们。我当时正在听
something Steve Jobs was saying a couple
史蒂夫·乔布斯说过的一些话
of weeks ago. I'll throw it up on the
几周前。我会把它上传到……
screen for anybody. I've built a lot of
任何人都可以观看。我建造了很多
my success off finding these truly
我成功地找到了这些真正
gifted people and not settling for B and
有天赋的人，不满足于B级和B级。
C players, but really going for the A
C级球员，但目标是A级
players. And I found something. I found
玩家。我发现了一些东西。我发现
that when you get enough A players
当你拥有足够多的A级球员时，情况就会改变。
together, when you go to through the
一起，当你们一起穿过
incredible work to find, you know, five
真是了不起的工作，居然找到了五个，你知道的。
of these A players, they really like
这些A级球员中，他们真的很喜欢
working with each other because they
他们之所以合作，是因为他们
they've never had a chance to do that
他们从来没有机会这样做。
before and they don't want to work with
之前他们不想和
B and C players and so it becomes self-p
B级和C级球员，因此就变成了自我设限。
policing and they only want to hire more
他们正在加强警务工作，而且他们只想招募更多警力。
A players and so you build up these
A级球员，所以你才能培养出这些球员。
pockets of A players and it propagates.
一些顶尖人才聚集在一起，这种现象会不断蔓延。
Have you found that to be the case? And
你发现情况确实如此吗？和
also I want to address another point
另外，我还想谈谈另一点。
here which is the insecurity of an early
这里指的是早期阶段的不安全感。
stage founder who looks up and sees
舞台创始人抬头望去，看到了
someone that's really experienced and
一位真正有经验的人，
then they have that sort of self-doubt
然后他们就会产生那种自我怀疑。
and go how the [__] am I going to manage
然后我就想，我他妈该怎么应付？
them? Mhm. You know what at the risk of
他们？嗯。你知道冒着怎样的风险
disagreeing with anybody so prolific and
不同意任何如此多产的人的观点
amazing. I think as someone who has been
惊人的。我认为，作为一个曾经……的人
able to move people between
能够将人们在
organizations or between companies
组织或公司之间
sometimes it can be the company that can
有时候，可能是公司本身的问题。
make people great. You can have a truly
造就伟大的人。你可以拥有一个真正的
exceptional person in a kind of
某种意义上的杰出人物
dysfunctional company and then they
这家公司经营不善，然后他们
don't do as well, right? Like you can
表现不太好，对吧？就像你可以
bring in somebody not quite exceptional
找个不算特别出色的人。
into an exceptional culture and company
融入卓越的企业文化和公司
and the organization makes them great,
而组织架构成就了他们的伟大。
makes them look great or makes them No,
让它们看起来很棒，还是让它们看起来不？
makes them great. Because what people
这使它们变得很棒。因为人们
tend to do is level up, right? whether
通常情况下，人们只会升级，对吧？无论
you you you end up the average of the
你你你最终会成为平均值
people that you surround yourself most.
你身边最常接触的人。
And I have in some cases bought people
在某些情况下，我确实买通过人。
in, you know, I'd be like a B minus and
你知道，我大概只能考个B-吧。
they've turned into an A+. And I the
他们已经变成了A+。而我
more I think about this, Stephen, the
斯蒂芬，我越想越觉得……
more I think that's happened on a number
我认为这种情况已经发生过很多次了。
of occasions and when the organization
各种场合以及组织
is exceptional and when the people there
非常出色，而且那里的人们也都很优秀。
are doing exceptional work, they can
他们正在做着非常出色的工作，他们可以
actually level up the people. Now, they
实际上提升了人们的生活水平。现在，他们
have to be somebody that wants to level
必须是那种想要提升自身水平的人。
up for sure, but I've definitely seen it
肯定会有，但我肯定见过它。
work that way. One of the things I think
那样做是行的。我认为其中一件事
a lot about, it's kind of dovetales into
很多方面，有点像鸽子的故事
this a little bit because I was
这有点儿是因为我是
referencing how we can sometimes be our
提到我们有时会如何成为我们自己
own worst enemies and doubt ourselves
我们最大的敌人和自我怀疑
away from like finding the truly
远离寻找真正的
exceptional person. So, we end up hiring
杰出的人。所以，我们最终决定招聘。
our friends is the idea of I love this
我们的朋友就是我喜欢这个想法的原因。
idea that you've hired friends. Who are
你雇佣了朋友的想法。谁是
these friends that you're hiring? Did
你雇佣的这些朋友？做过
you hire a bunch of friends? It's a
你雇佣了一群朋友？这是一个
terrible bloody idea. 18 says me who
真是个糟糕透顶的主意。 18岁，我说的是谁
works with my husband.
与我丈夫一起工作。
I was 18 and I I um they weren't
我当时18岁，嗯……他们不是
actually friends but they weren't they
实际上是朋友，但他们并不是。
weren't qualified. I just met them at
不具备资格。我刚刚在……遇到了他们
like I met one guy at a Prada store and
比如我在一家Prada店里遇到了一个男生，
I was like you can be my account manager
我当时就想，你可以做我的客户经理。
and then I met some guy at like a rap
然后我在一家酒吧遇到了一个说唱歌手。
battle and I was like you should be my
战斗中，我心想你应该是我的
marketing director and he this is great
市场总监，这太棒了
between Prada and the rap battle I get
在Prada和说唱对决之间，我明白了。
it I can see these things weren't
我看得出来这些东西并非如此。
happening no rigor in deciding who No
在决定谁不参与时，没有采取任何严格的措施。
but that's what it comes down to like
但归根结底就是这样。
rigor right it's like you again you've
严谨，没错，就像你又来了一样。
developed systems and processes that
已开发的系统和流程
have helped you get to where you are and
帮助你走到今天这一步
it's like now I have a giant
现在我感觉自己像个巨人
organization and you know a head of
组织，你认识一位负责人
people that that spend their life like
那些终其一生都像这样生活的人
not just again bringing people into the
不仅仅是再次把人们带入
organization, but then like making them
组织，但就像制作它们一样
great once they get there. Like I had no
他们到了那里之后就很棒了。就像我没有
such thing. I don't even think I knew
这种事。我甚至觉得我都不知道
where the HR office was when I was in in
我当时在的时候，人力资源办公室就在那里。
employment. I mean like who are they?
就业。我是说，他们到底是谁？
Where are they? Some I don't know girl
他们在哪里？我不认识的一些女孩
called Joe that sits in accounts. I
名叫乔，负责会计工作。我
don't know where she was. Um but the I
不知道她去了哪里。嗯，但是我
say that because we're in a different
这么说是因为我们身处不同的境地
time now where there is such an ability
现在正是具备这种能力的时候。
for us to be more thoughtful about who
以便我们更认真地思考谁
we're bringing in. And so I think anyone
我们正在引进。所以我认为任何人
who's really smart and any founder
谁是真正聪明的人，以及任何创始人
that's really smart is going to use all
真正聪明的做法是充分利用所有资源
the tools. All you need to do is know
工具。你只需要知道
that it's a really important thing that
这是一件非常重要的事情
you will do. Who those first three,
你会做到的。前三个人是谁？
five, 10 people that you bring into your
你带来的五到十个人
organization will be the difference
组织能力将决定成败。
between good and great. And so being
介于优秀和卓越之间。因此，
slow and thoughtful and purposeful and
缓慢、深思熟虑、目标明确
using everything at your disposal to
利用你所掌握的一切资源
make those decisions is probably the the
做出这些决定可能是
best time that a founder can spend
创始人可以度过的最佳时光
outside of developing product or
除了产品开发之外，或者
whatever the end product is. How do you
无论最终产品是什么。你如何
think about prejudice, Emma? I I mean
艾玛，想想偏见这件事吧？我的意思是
what I really mean here is being being
我真正想表达的是存在。
counted out before you walk in the room.
在你走进房间之前就已经数好了。
So people hear that you're it might be a
所以人们听说你可能是一个
woman or something else and you feel
女人或其他什么人，你会感觉
that they're not taking you seriously.
他们根本没把你当回事。
Has that happened in your career? Um, as
你的职业生涯中遇到过这种情况吗？嗯，作为
a black person, as a woman, as anything
一个黑人，作为一个女人，作为任何身份
that puts you in the minority, as it
那会让你成为少数派，因为
relates to the accomplishments you've
这与你取得的成就有关
made? Actually, you know, I'm going to
制成？实际上，你知道，我要……
give you a bit more context as to why I
再给你解释一下我为什么这么做。
ask. Yeah. Go on. Frame. Is because one
问。是的。继续。框架。因为一个
of my fears, Yeah. is with some people,
是的，我的恐惧。和某些人在一起，
they count themselves out before they
他们还没来得及把自己排除在外就放弃了
walk in the room because prejudice is
走进房间，因为偏见是
real. So, they limit themselves. And
真实的。所以，他们会自我设限。和
there's a really great study they did
他们做了一项非常棒的研究。
many, many years ago where they got a
很多很多年前，他们得到了
group of black people, I believe it was
一群黑人，我相信是
on a vocabulary test, just to talk about
在词汇测试中，只是为了谈论
their race before they did the
他们比赛之前
vocabulary test. And if they got them to
词汇测试。如果他们能做到
talk about their race before, their
之前谈论过他们的种族，他们的
performance dropped. If they didn't get
性能下降。如果他们没得到
the group to talk about their race
该小组讨论了他们的种族问题
before in a different study, performance
在另一项研究中，表现
was the same. They did the same with
是一样的。他们对……也做了同样的事。
women. They got them to um identify
女性。他们让他们……辨认
their gender before doing a maths test.
在进行数学测试之前，先询问他们的性别。
because there's a
因为存在一个
stereotype around mass or at least there
围绕大众的刻板印象，或者至少在那里
was at the time in women. Women on that
当时主要针对女性。那些女性
test would perform worse if they'd
如果它们……，测试结果会更差。
talked about their gender right before
在谈论他们的性别之前
they did the test. But importantly, if
他们做了测试。但重要的是，如果
they didn't, the results were the same
他们没有这样做，结果还是一样。
as everybody else. So stereotype threat
和其他人一样。刻板印象威胁
is a real thing. And the UN unpopular
这是真实存在的。联合国不受欢迎。
conversation is there could be ways that
对话可能存在一些方法
we're holding ourselves back before we
我们是在自我设限之前就放弃了
even walk into the room because of that
甚至因此走进了房间。
stereotype threat. Mhm. It could be age,
刻板印象威胁。嗯。可能是年龄问题。
it could be race, it could be gender, it
可能是种族问题，可能是性别问题，它
could be anything else. It could be a a
也可能是其他任何东西。这可能是一个
disability. And I just wonder how you
残疾。我只是好奇你是怎么想的
think about like, you know, that I mean,
想想看，你知道，我的意思是，
look, it's undoubtable that that is real
你看，那绝对是真的，这一点毋庸置疑。
for so many people in their lives and
对于他们生活中的许多人来说，
the way they think about themselves. I
他们如何看待自己。我
think that any thoughtful organization
任何深思熟虑的组织都会认为
has and
有和
certainly in more recent times, if we
当然，在最近一段时间，如果我们
think about what's happened in the last
想想过去发生了什么
5 years, anybody that didn't look at
5年，任何没看过的人
their company hiring process and and and
他们公司的招聘流程以及
beyond the hiring process, look around
除了招聘流程之外，还要四处看看。
their business and see is it a true
看看他们的生意是否真实
reflection of our customer base, of
反映了我们的客户群体
society, of what we're trying to achieve
社会，以及我们努力想要实现的目标
and who we want to be, you know, making
以及我们想成为什么样的人，你知道，创造
decisions. We're talking about foolish
决定。我们说的是愚蠢
companies here. I feel like any anybody
这里的公司。我觉得自己和任何人一样
and everybody did that. Look, the the
大家都这么做了。你看，这
great thing the great thing about
很棒的事情，很棒的事情
prejudice is you very rarely know if it
偏见就是你很少知道它是否……
actually happened to you. Nobody nobody
这件事真的发生在你身上了。没有人
likes to point out. They're like,
喜欢指出。他们就像是：
"Listen, you didn't get this thing
听着，你没明白这个。
because actually I'm prejudiced against
因为实际上我对……抱有偏见
you." I'm sure it has happened. It's
你。”我确信这事发生过。
never something that for me, knowing how
对我来说，从来没有过这样的事，知道如何
I'm
我是
hardwired, I would have let get to me in
根深蒂固的观念，我会让它影响到我。
any way, shape, or form. you know, I'd
任何方式、形状或形式。你知道，我会
get in a room and would never feel any
走进房间，你永远不会感到任何不适
such like like held back by my educa
比如，就像被我的教育所阻碍一样
education, held back by my accent or
教育，因我的口音而受阻
anything like that or being a black
诸如此类的事情，或者身为黑人
woman. In fact, to the contrary, to me,
女士。事实上，恰恰相反，对我而言，
I always felt like it was a bit of an
我一直觉得这有点像……
advantage. There was only one of me. I
优势。我只有一个。我
used to walk into these offices and work
过去常常走进这些办公室工作
experience and everybody would always
经验，每个人都会总是
single me out because I was the only one
因为只有我一个人，所以就单独挑出来。
that kind of looked like she might have
她看起来好像……
a different opinion. and everyone came
不同的观点。大家都来了
from the same kind of, you know, like
来自同一种，你知道，比如
private school stock and there I was
私立学校股票，而我当时就在那里。
with the accent, with the big curly
带着口音，带着大卷发
hair, black girl sitting in the corner
角落里坐着一个黑人女孩，头发蓬乱
and inevitably they'd be like, "What do
他们肯定会问：“怎么办？”
you think?" So, you know, it just played
你觉得呢？” 所以，你知道，它就这么播放了。
out differently for me and and therefore
对我来说结果不同，因此
my experiences kind of are a reflection
我的经历某种程度上也是一种反思。
of that. That's what I wanted to know. I
就是那件事。这正是我想要知道的。我
wanted to understand that because
想弄明白这一点，因为
it's it's um it's something that I
是，是，嗯，是……我
really want people to realize which is
真心希望人们意识到这一点
like prejudice. Yes, it's real as you
比如偏见。是的，这是真的。
said but it doesn't have to be your
有人说，但这不一定是你的。
problem. It can remain theirs. Yeah. And
问题。它可以继续属于他们。是的。和
I really worry that people will
我真的很担心人们会
internalize other people's prejudice and
内化他人的偏见和
then limit themselves. Yeah. And I think
然后限制自己。是的。我觉得
this is a very different Listen, you and
这是一个截然不同的听着，你和
I speak as two British people,
我以两个英国人的身份发言，
right? I've lived here now for eight
正确的？我在这里住了八年了。
years.
年。
It ain't the same here in America. How
美国的情况不一样。如何
do you mean? Well, the the way people
你是说？嗯，人们的方式
relate to race is extremely different
与种族相关的因素截然不同。
here. And if I'd have been born in
这里。如果我出生在
America, maybe I'd have had a different
在美国，或许我会有不同的经历。
feeling about how the color of my skin
关于我的肤色的感受
impacted my life on a daily basis
它对我的日常生活产生了影响
because it's very very very different
因为它非常非常非常不同。
here and very much more prolific and a
这里，而且产量更高，而且
point of everyday
日常要点
uh not just conversation but everyday
呃，不只是对话，而是日常生活
prejudice comes up and manifests itself
偏见出现并表现出来。
in a very very different way here. uh in
这里的情况截然不同。呃，在
with negative connotations. And so I
带有负面含义。所以，我
thank God that I was raised in London
感谢上帝，我是在伦敦长大的。
and I I had a very very different way
而我，我的方式截然不同。
of associate like how I felt about
就像我感觉自己像个同事一样
myself. I had a very very different way
我。我的方法截然不同。
of um the way in which I was raised and
嗯，关于我的成长方式，
how I experienced like race as a kid.
我小时候对种族问题的经历。
How you felt about yourself seems to be
你对自己的感觉似乎是
more internal than external in that
更多的是内在因素而非外在因素
regard. And that brings me to my next
看待。这就引出了我的下一个问题。
question, which is just about how do we
问题在于我们如何
not give so many [__] because
不太在意，因为
it's hard to live and it's hard to
生活不易，也很难
strive and it's hard to take risk if
努力奋斗，就很难承担风险。
we're imprisoned by the amount of [__]
我们被“操”的次数所囚禁
that we we get. Yeah. This is I feel
我们得到的。是的。这就是我的感受
like this is like my specialtity, you
这就像我的专长一样，你
know? It's really interesting because so
知道？这真的很有意思，因为……
much of that is just
其中很多只是
like in us, right? It's like hardwired
就像我们一样，对吧？这就像是硬性规定一样
who we are and how many [__] we give.
我们是谁，以及我们有多在乎。
And I just so happen to be the type of
而我恰好就是那种人
person that has such sort of self
拥有这种自我意识的人
asssurance and such
保证等等
conviction
定罪
that I don't care or I just have I have
我不在乎，或者我只是有。
such high it's not that I don't care. I
这么高，并不是我不在乎。我
just have such a high value on how much
只是对多少东西有如此高的重视程度
I care about what I think that maybe
我关心的是我的想法，也许
what other people think just kind of
其他人的想法大概就是这样
like pales into insignificance for me.
对我来说，喜欢这件事显得微不足道。
That that that's the honest truth. And
这就是实话。和
so I just have very very high selfworth.
所以我的自我价值感非常非常高。
I've heard you talk before about how as
我以前听你说过关于……的事情
well we kind of misunderstand how much
我们有点误解了多少
people actually give a [__] about us. I
居然有人真的在乎我们。我
think about that all the time because
时刻想着这件事，因为
it's just one of those things that we
这只是我们遇到的其中一件事。
just imagine that people spend a lot of
试想一下，人们花费大量时间
time crafting texts to us that you would
花时间精心撰写短信给我们，你会……
like sit and be like what did they mean
就像坐着，然后想：他们是什么意思？
by that? You know like I it just was
那样做？你知道，就像我当时那样。
sent. Do you know what I Like I didn't
发送。你知道我喜欢什么吗？我没有
even think about the words and now you
甚至想想这些话，现在你
know whether I was using caps or the
知道我当时是用大写字母还是小写字母
wrong emojis or like whatever it is. And
表情符号用错了，或者诸如此类的事情。和
I do think that there is this thing that
我确实认为存在这样一种情况：
we imagine because we're at the center
我们之所以能想象，是因为我们身处中心。
of our universe that we're at the center
我们身处宇宙的中心
of everybody else's. And it's just not
其他人的。但这并非事实
the truth. Nobody's watching you. Like I
真相。没人看着你。就像我
think about it all the time. Nobody
我一直都在想这件事。无人
wakes up and thinks about me as much as
醒来后，她会像我一样频繁地想起我。
I do. So it can feel like we just got to
我愿意。所以感觉我们好像刚刚……
relax. Well, maybe it feels like it for
放松。或许感觉是这样吧
you, but I just don't think that
你，但我并不这么认为。
anybody's that interested. It doesn't
有人对此感兴趣吗？它不
feel like it for me. But when you're in
我觉得是这样。但当你身处其中时
the I think humans like from an
我认为人类喜欢从……
evolutionary perspective, we're like our
从进化论的角度来看，我们就像我们的
brain is built to deal with like 20
大脑的设计容量大约是20个。
tribes people. Yeah. Yeah. So we we
部落人民。是的。是的。所以我们
interpret we we we we have a probably
我们解释一下，我们可能有一个
hardwired to our fault of being
我们天生就有缺陷
interpreting everything as coming from a
将一切都解释为来自
member of the tribe. Yeah. Whereas in
部落成员。是的。然而在
reality it could be like Dave and
现实情况可能就像戴夫和
Swindon with like an egg emoji who's
斯温顿就像一个鸡蛋表情符号，他是谁？
telling you that those genes suck suck.
告诉你，那些基因糟透了。
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Totally. Listen. And
是的。是的。是的。完全。听。和
David Swindon is like allowed to have
大卫·斯温顿似乎被允许拥有
his egg emoji. I just don't think his
他的鸡蛋表情符号。我只是觉得他
egg emoji needs to like ruin my day. I'm
鸡蛋表情符号简直毁了我的一天。我是
like, poor [__] Like, what's he
真是个可怜的家伙。他到底是什么人？
doing? How
正在做？如何
embarrassing. Bad skin. I've had it. And
令人尴尬。皮肤不好。我受够了。和
I'm sure many of you listening have had
我相信很多听众都经历过这种情况。
it, too. Or maybe you have it right now.
也是。或许你现在就拥有它。
I know how draining it can be,
我知道这有多累人。
especially if you're in a job where
尤其是如果你从事的工作是……
you're presenting often like I am. So,
你和我一样，经常做演讲。所以，
let me tell you about something that's
让我跟你说说这件事……
helped both my partner and me and my
这对我和我的伴侣都很有帮助。
sister, which is red light therapy. I
姐姐，也就是红光疗法。我
only got into this a couple of years
我入行也就几年时间。
ago, but I wish I'd known a little bit
虽然是很久以前，但我希望我当时能多了解一些。
sooner. I've been using our show
尽快。我一直在使用我们的节目
sponsors Boncharg's infrared sauna
赞助商 Boncharg 的红外线桑拿房
blanket for a while now, but I just got
这条毯子我已经用了很久了，但我刚刚才拿到
hold of their red light therapy mask as
他们拿着红光治疗面罩
well. Red light has been proven to have
出色地。红光已被证明具有
so many benefits for the body. Like any
对身体有很多好处。像任何
area of your skin that's exposed will
暴露在外的皮肤区域
see a reduction in scarring, wrinkles,
疤痕和皱纹明显减少。
and even blemishes. It also helps with
甚至包括瑕疵。它还有助于……
complexion. It boosts collagen, and it
肤色。它能促进胶原蛋白生成，而且
does that by targeting the upper layers
这是通过针对上层来实现的。
of your skin. And Boncharge ships
你的皮肤。而 Boncharge 船
worldwide with easy returns and a
全球范围内均可轻松退货
year-long warranty on all of their
他们所有产品均提供一年保修。
products. So, if you'd like to try it
产品。所以，如果你想尝试一下的话
yourself, head over to
你自己，前往
bondcharge.com/diary and use code diary
bondcharge.com/diary 并使用代码 diary
for 25% off any product sitewide. Just
全场商品享25%折扣。只是
make sure you order through this link,
请务必通过此链接下单。
bondcharge.com/diary with code diary.
bondcharge.com/diary，代码为 diary。
One of the um the next seasons of life I
人生接下来的几个阶段之一
find myself moving towards quickly is
我发现自己正迅速地朝着……方向前进。
parenthood. M when did you start trying
为人父母。 M，你是什么时候开始尝试的？
and what was your fertility journey
你的生育历程是怎样的？
like? I love that you asked this and I
喜欢？我很高兴你问了这个问题，而且
was I'm very surprised that you are. Um
我很惊讶你会这么想。嗯
I had the most
我拥有最多的
easy,
简单的，
unbelievable,
难以置信，
brilliant fertility journey with my
我与我的奇妙生育之旅
first two and then probably the saddest,
前两个，然后可能是最令人难过的，
most disappointing, hardest time in my
最令人失望，最艰难的时期
life with the second two. And so it
与另外两个孩子一起生活。所以就是这样。
really was a tale of two halves because
这确实是一个分为两部分的故事，因为
I have an 11 and an 8-year-old and you
我有一个11岁的孩子和一个8岁的孩子，而你
know without too much information I like
无需太多信息就能知道我喜欢
literally you know came off the pill and
实际上，你知道，我停了避孕药。
puff I was pregnant which was amazing.
噗，我怀孕了，这真是太棒了。
31 I had gray when Yeah. So 30 30 years
31岁的时候我头发都白了。是的。所以是30年
old, you know, was had had got married.
你知道，年纪大了，已经结婚了。
Actually had zero ambition to ever have
实际上我从未想过要拥有什么。
kids ever. And then it was like one of
孩子们总是这样。然后就像是其中之一
those fairy tale things where I
那些童话故事里，我
literally walked down the aisle and was
真的就这么走过了过道，然后……
like, "Oh my god, I just can't wait to
比如，“我的天哪，我简直迫不及待了……”
have a baby." What is going on here? No,
“生个孩子。”这是怎么回事？不，
I don't know who that girl was. Um, so I
我不知道那个女孩是谁。嗯，所以……
got pregnant uh very easy with my first
怀第一胎的时候非常容易。
child. Couple of years later, had my
孩子。几年后，我有了
second child. You know, life happens.
第二个孩子。你知道，人生就是如此。
Moved to the US. Oh, everything's like,
移居美国。哦，一切都像这样，
you know, going fantastic. I decide baby
你知道，一切都棒极了。我决定宝贝
number three. Come off the pill again.
第三。再次停止服用避孕药。
And I'm like,
我当时就想，
waiting. I'm waiting again. And it
等待。我还在等待。而且它
doesn't happen. And so I'm like, honey,
不会发生。于是我就说，亲爱的，
you need to go and get yourself
你需要去接自己
checked. Okay. You know, so we do the
已确认。好的。你知道，所以我们这样做
things that you do when you don't get
当你得不到满足时，你会做的事情
pregnant so easily. And there was just
很容易怀孕。然后就只有
no explanation for my infertility. And
我的不孕症没有任何解释。和
so I went through um a few rounds of
所以我经历了几轮……
IVF. And for me, you know, what age is
试管婴儿。对我来说，你知道，多大年纪……
this? Sorry, just so I am at this point,
这？抱歉，我目前的情况是这样的。
how old am I now? I'm 42. The kids are
我现在多大了？我42岁。孩子们是
three f So 38. You're 38. I'm 38. So
三个 f 所以 38。你 38 岁。我 38 岁。所以
I'm, you know, I'm not like quite yet a
你知道，我还没完全……
geriatric pregnancy as they like to call
他们喜欢称之为高龄妊娠。
it in this country when a woman over the
在这个国家，当一个女人超过
age of, you know, 40 has a baby. But I'm
你知道，40岁左右生了个孩子。但我
I'm skimming, right? I'm on the edge of
我这是在略读，对吧？我正处于……的边缘
where f fertility starts to um become,
生育能力开始下降的地方，嗯，
you know, more of an issue. And anyway,
你知道，这才是真正的问题。总之，
for me it was devastating because I
对我来说，这简直是毁灭性的打击，因为我
really really had something and and I'm
真的真的有件事，而且我是
sure so many women will tell you this.
肯定会有很多女性这么说。
Once you've made up your mind that
一旦你下定决心……
you're having another baby, that was it
你又要生孩子了，就这么简单。
for me. Then it was just like, well, how
为我。然后就好像，嗯，怎么会这样
is this going to happen? And I was so
这会发生吗？我当时真是太
lucky in some ways that I was here in,
从某种意义上说，我很幸运能来到这里。
you know, I lived in Beverly Hills at
你知道，我以前住在比佛利山庄。
the time. Access to the best doctors was
时间。能够接触到最好的医生是
like so so easy. And so I went on what
简直太容易了。于是我继续前进。
would become a journey through IVF. And
这将是一段试管婴儿之旅。和
it was one of the hardest, most soul
这是最艰难、最触动灵魂的经历之一。
destroying times of my life. I couldn't
我生命中最痛苦的时光。我不能
think about anything else. You know, you
想想别的事吧。你知道，你
could be like, "Emma, what do you want
可能会这样问：“艾玛，你想要什么？”
for dinner tonight?" I'd be like, "A
今晚吃什么？”我会说，“A
baby." You know, like I just I just was
“宝贝。”你知道，就像我刚才那样
single track like the all I could think
单曲就像我能想到的一切
about was I need this. I need to be
我大概需要这个。我需要是
pregnant. Why soul destroying? You know,
孕。为什么会摧毁灵魂？你知道，
it was so destroying because I went
那件事太令人崩溃了，因为我去了
through multiple rounds of IVF and every
经过多轮试管婴儿治疗，每
single time for me actually it did work
实际上，对我来说，它只奏效了一次。
out but then I lost a baby three times
后来我流产了三次。
and it was really it was just awful you
真是太糟糕了。
know and for me it happened at 9 weeks
我知道，对我来说，那是在怀孕9周的时候发生的。
11 weeks and 16 weeks and so you know at
11周和16周，所以你知道
that point 16 weeks you you're about to
到那时，也就是16周后，你即将……
tell people you are you know you think
告诉别人你是你知道的你认为
you're past the sort of danger zone so
你已经脱离了危险区，所以
to speak something in my heart told me
内心深处有话要说。
that it wasn't going to work out for me
我觉得这对我来说行不通。
like I I actually think I knew deep
就像我，我其实觉得我了解很多。
down, but you're doing all the things.
虽然情绪低落，但你仍然在做所有的事情。
You know, I'm having the acupuncture and
你知道，我正在接受针灸治疗，
the doctors all feel great about it. And
医生们对此都感到非常满意。和
of course, you know, you have IVF and
当然，你知道，你可以做试管婴儿。
then it's successful. You're like,
如果成功，那就说明成功了。你就像，
great, now I'm pregnant. I'm having a
太好了，我现在怀孕了。我正在经历
baby. Um, and so that that loss was just
婴儿。嗯，所以那场损失仅仅是
an it was so hard to deal with. And
这件事太难处理了。和
again, you know, it was a very isolating
再说一遍，你知道，那是一种非常孤独的体验。
time because it was like like co I was
时间，因为就像我当时一样。
on my like driving in a, you know, in
就像开车一样，你知道的，
gloves and a hazmat suit, you You know,
手套和防护服，你知道的。
it was like the time where we really
那就像我们真正……的那段时间。
didn't know and you know, and the roads
不知道，你知道，还有道路
were empty and it was tough. You know,
空荡荡的，日子很艰难。你知道，
the police would pull you over and I'd
警察会把你拦下来，然后我会
be like, I'm going to the IVF clinic,
比如，我会说，我要去试管婴儿诊所。
which was like one of the few things
这几乎是为数不多的事情之一。
that you were allowed to be on the road
你被允许上路
and driving around for. So, it was just
开车四处转悠。所以，就只是
very, very difficult. Um, but you know,
非常非常难。嗯，但是你知道，
I had a happy ending. And so for me, my
我得到了一个圆满的结局。所以对我来说，我的
journey ended in something that I never
这段旅程以我从未想过的方式结束了。
thought would be uh a way that I would
我觉得这会是一种方式……
go, but I ended up deciding that I would
去吧，但我最终决定我会
have a surrogate. And I met an
找代孕妈妈。我遇到了一个
incredible woman. And she carried my
了不起的女人。她抱着我
twins, which was
双胞胎，
the like single
像单身人士
biggest thing that anyone can ever do.
这是任何人所能做的最伟大的事。
You're like, "What? Like this is so
你会想，“什么？这简直太……”
crazy." Um, and it was amazing. I had
太疯狂了。”嗯，真是太棒了。我曾
like such a profound, incredible
就像如此深刻、不可思议的事情
pregnancy with this amazing, wonderful
怀着这令人惊叹、美妙的孕期
woman who beyond what our contractual
超出我们合同范围的女人
commitment was, you know, because you
你知道，承诺是因为你
hear horror stories like she asked me
听她讲那些恐怖故事，就像她问我的那样
for nothing. It was a beautiful, amazing
毫无意义。那真是一次美妙绝伦的体验
partnership and my twins were born via
伴侣关系，我的双胞胎是通过这种关系出生的。
surrogacy and that was that complicated
代孕，事情就是这么复杂。
emotions.
情绪。
No. And you know, I have to tell you,
不。而且你知道，我必须告诉你，
Stephen, I'd love to like and maybe I
斯蒂芬，我很想喜欢你，也许我
approached it more like a bit of a like
更像是某种类似的东西
I was very transactional about it. Not
我当时只是抱着一种交易心态去看待这件事。不是
the surrogacy in the moment before of
代孕发生在……之前
beyond beyond beyond complicated
超越复杂程度
emotions because you are, you know, I've
因为你的情绪，你知道，我
had pregnancy loss before before I
我之前有过流产史。
decided to have children. Uh, you know,
决定要孩子。呃，你知道的，
I've had a complicated, as so many women
我的经历很复杂，就像很多女性一样。
have, complicated fertility journey. It
有着复杂的生育历程。它
was emotions that
是那种情绪
were, I would say, too hard to bear. And
我觉得，这太难以忍受了。和
for somebody who's used to being able to
对于一个习惯于能够……的人来说
get her way and work towards things
按照她的意愿努力实现目标
being as they should be, and to me it's
就应该如此，对我来说是这样。
like the amount of effort I put in
就像我投入的努力程度一样
directly correlates to the result. And
与结果直接相关。和
there was no such thing in this. You
这里面根本没有这种事。你
could have all the shots and all the
可以拍到所有镜头和所有
acupuncture and do everything that
针灸，以及做所有能做的
you're supposed to do, not work out too
你应该做的是，不要过度锻炼。
much, don't go in a sauna, you know,
别去桑拿房，你知道的。
like be an angel, eat all of the right
就像天使一样，吃光所有东西
things, and still I couldn't, you know,
事情，但我仍然做不到，你知道吗？
hold on to the pregnancy. So to me it
坚持妊娠。所以对我来说
was just something that I couldn't I
那是我无法做到的事。
couldn't bear in that moment. Are there
那一刻我无法忍受。有吗？
any like are there decisions that you
有没有类似这样的决定？
wish you'd made or is there something
希望你做了什么，或者有什么其他事吗？
you'd wish you'd known? Because we don't
你希望自己早点知道吗？因为我们没有
talk about this enough so people end up
谈论这件事足够多次，人们最终会
going through this themselves. You you
他们自己也在经历这一切。你你
know what I'll tell you I wish I'd have
我知道我会告诉你我希望我曾经拥有过什么。
spoken about it more with all of my
我跟我的所有人都更多地谈论过这件事。
friends that had gone through it. And I
经历过这件事的朋友们。我
will tell you this story. I was a couple
我会把这个故事讲给你听。我当时是一对情侣
of summers ago. You know, I'm often the
往年的夏天。你知道，我经常是
person people confide in. And I happened
人们信任的人。而我恰巧
to be, I won't say where. I was in this
至于会在哪里，我就不说了。我当时就在这个
place. I'm very confined, like on a
地方。我感觉很局促，就像被困在……
boat. And all of the women were in some
船。所有女性都处于某种状态。
type of fertility thing. Like they had
某种生育方面的问题。就像他们曾经那样
different things going on. And I looked
各种事情同时发生。我看了看
around and I knew I was the only one of
周围都是我，我知道我是唯一的人。
all five of us that knew everybody's
我们五个人都认识所有人
thing. And I was like, we could be
事物。我当时就想，我们可能会
having such a good conversation now,
现在聊得真好。
right? like it would be so rich and so
正确的？就像它会如此富有，如此
useful because again like there was
有用，因为就像之前那样。
somebody that had like had kids by by
曾经有过孩子的人
IVF. There was someone who had just come
试管婴儿。刚刚有人来了
from somewhere. There was somebody that
来自某个地方。有一个人
was in the middle of like diagnosing
当时正在诊断病情
endometriosis and there was somebody who
子宫内膜异位症，而且有人
was pregnant but not telling everyone
她怀孕了，但没告诉所有人。
she was pregnant because it was IVF and
她怀孕是因为做了试管婴儿。
she'd have all the problem. But anyway,
她会遇到所有的问题。不过，总之，
like everybody had their own unique
就像每个人都有自己独特的经历一样。
circumstances and I was like in a group
当时的情况是，我身处一个群体之中。
of women where we discuss I won't even
谈到女性，我们讨论的话题我甚至都不愿意提及。
say what we discussed but we discuss
说说我们讨论的内容，但我们讨论
every single thing that that is like the
每一样东西都像
last taboo. It says something about your
最后一个禁忌。这说明了一些关于你的问题。
womanhood that it would that it would be
女性气质，那将是，那将是
such a deeply held secret and something
如此深藏的秘密，以及某种
that you just can't discuss is such a
你根本无法讨论的就是这种
shame. And I'm not saying that that's
耻辱。我并不是说那就是
what it is for all women and all groups
这对所有女性和所有群体来说意味着什么
of friends, but it's definitely um it's
是朋友，但肯定是……嗯，是……
definitely something that people really
绝对是人们真正关心的事情
really struggle with talking about. And
真的很难开口谈论这件事。和
certainly for me going down the
对我来说，当然是下去
surrogacy route, I really felt an
通过代孕这条路，我真的感觉……
element of I wouldn't say shame, but it
某种程度上，我不会说是羞耻，但确实如此。
was like
就像
Why could I was willing to do this
我为什么愿意这样做
myself? Like why couldn't I? Like you,
我？为什么我不能？和你一样，
you know, I should have just been able
你知道，我本应该能够
to do it. I was ready, you know, at 38
去做这件事。你知道，我38岁的时候就已经准备好了。
to like have to like go back on the
就像不得不回到过去一样
workouts and, you know, like, you know,
锻炼，还有，你知道，就像，你知道的，
figure myself out again. And so I felt
重新认识自己。于是我感觉
like I'd been robbed of of an
就像我被抢劫了一样
opportunity to do something. And then,
一个做事情的机会。进而，
you know, coming out of it, I was like,
你知道，从那件事里走出来之后，我就想，
"Wow, that was such a profound
哇，这真是意味深长
experience. I would never have had had
经验。我永远不会有
all of these things not happened." And
这些事都没有发生过。”
so in a weird way, I was just kind of
所以从某种程度上来说，我当时就有点……
grateful for the opportunity to have
感谢有机会拥有
been, you know, to have been able to see
你知道，能够看到
how selfless like another human being
多么无私，就像另一个人一样
could be. Were you aware of the
有可能。您是否了解……
biological clock in the way that people
人们的生物钟以某种方式
are now aware of it back then? Yeah, I I
当时你们知道这件事吗？是的，我
was. Although I have to tell you that
曾是。虽然我必须告诉你……
there's nothing, you know, for most
你知道，对大多数人来说，什么都没有。
women, we spend all of our time thinking
女人啊，我们把所有时间都花在思考上
about how to not get pregnant. He's just
关于如何避免怀孕。他只是
like, you know, I just want to like not
你知道，我只是想……
get pregnant forever until it's your
一直怀孕，直到怀上你的孩子。
moment that you want to get pregnant and
你想怀孕的那一刻
then there's this second moment where
然后还有第二个时刻，
it's like it's no longer your choice and
就好像这不再是你的选择权了。
the window's really really narrow. And
窗户真的很窄。和
so I I you know, again, I have hundreds
所以，你知道，我还有几百个。
of women in my office and I mentioned to
我提到了我办公室里的女性同事们
you at the start of this conversation,
对话开始时的你，
you know, there was some fertility
你知道，当时有一些生育能力。
seminar yesterday. I think that there's
昨天的研讨会。我认为有
still so many myths around it. You know,
关于它仍然存在很多误解。你知道，
there is no good time. You can freeze
没有所谓“合适时机”。你可以冷冻
eggs, but it's not like freezing
鸡蛋，但这和冷冻不一样
embryos. it's very different, right? And
胚胎。差别很大，对吧？和
so the idea that the decision is all
所以，认为这个决定就是一切的想法
ours is just not realistic and that
我们的方案根本不现实，而且
there is there is a window and it is
那里有一扇窗户，而且
narrow and it is something that you have
狭窄，而且是你所拥有的。
to think about. And I think that there
值得思考。而且我认为……
are a lot of women that know that they
有很多女性知道这一点
don't want children, that's fine. But if
不想生孩子，没关系。但是如果
you do, it's really something that you
确实如此，这真的是你做的事。
ought to be more planful of because it's
应该更有计划性，因为……
bloody difficult and it's not how you
太难了，而且这不是你应该做的。
think. Thank you. Thank you for talking
思考。谢谢。谢谢你的谈话
about that because there, as you say,
关于这一点，因为正如你所说，
there's not enough people that talk
会说话的人不够多。
about it. And actually, had I not had
关于它。事实上，如果我没有
the the access to information on doing
获取有关开展工作的信息
this podcast and meeting these women who
这个播客以及与这些女性的相遇
have been very open about it, I would
我一直都很坦诚地谈论这件事，我会
have had no idea. And I would have
我完全不知道。我本可以
probably found myself in a bit of a
我可能发现自己陷入了一种……
struggle because me and my partner
因为我和我的伴侣而感到困扰
weren't thinking about that. We're
我们当时没考虑到这一点。是
thinking about getting the back. We're
考虑把后背拿回来。是
thinking about building our businesses.
思考如何发展我们的业务。
And we're 32 now. Yeah. So, when I hear
我们现在32岁了。是的。所以，当我听到
people like you say, "Listen, if this is
像你这样的人会说，“听着，如果这是
something you want, then plan, make a
把你想要的东西，然后计划，制作
plan." And I don't think many people
计划。”而且我认为没多少人
listening actually have a plan for for
认真倾听实际上有一个计划
children. They're going to they see it
孩子们。他们会去看的
as the thing they'll get round to when
他们会在什么时候处理这​​件事
they're ready. But this clock, man, it's
他们准备好了。但是这钟，老兄，真是……
like the clock is ticking. Work like
就像时间一分一秒地流逝。工作方式
that. I've got an idea. I think you
那。我有个主意。我觉得你
should start a podcast.
应该开始做播客。
Steven, whatever you say, I will do.
史蒂文，你说什么，我都会照做。
It's a great idea. Let's go. What should
这是个好主意。我们走吧。应该
What should it be called? I think you
它应该叫什么名字？我觉得你
should call it Aspire. I think you
应该叫它“Aspire”。我觉得你
should launch it in May. Stephen, you're
应该会在五月份推出。斯蒂芬，你是
so incredibly smart and thoughtful. And
真是太聪明、太体贴了。和
I feel like if my podcast could be born
我觉得如果我的播客能够诞生就好了
here and be just half the podcast that
这里，我只能做播客的一半。
you have, I think you can do it even
我觉得你完全可以做到
better. I think you can I think you can
更好的。我认为你可以。
level up. You This is what you said. You
升级。你，你就是这么说的。你
said people come and see something then
人们过来观看一些东西
they level up. So they level up. Why
他们升级了。于是他们升级了。为什么
podcasting? So your podcast launches in
播客？所以你的播客在……上线了
May. It's called Aspire. Yeah.
可能。它叫做Aspire。是的。
What are the what are you trying to
你想表达什么？
achieve? What's the mission there? Yeah.
达到？那里的任务是什么？是的。
You know, and it I'm so glad that you
你知道吗，我真高兴你
asked a question like that because for
问这样的问题是因为……
me it is a little bit of a mission and I
对我来说，这有点像一项任务，而且
think that the more success I've had and
我认为我取得的成功越多，
I'm sure this is very similar to you and
我相信这和你的情况非常相似。
you you've mentioned it on a few
你之前在一些场合提到过这件事
occasions and actually I remember being
场合，实际上我记得当时
out with you in Manchester. You remember
和你一起在曼彻斯特玩。你还记得吗？
when we had to like walk like from the
当我们不得不像从……走出来的时候
studio to the bar where everyone was
从工作室到酒吧，那里所有人都在那里。
doing that thing and you know it's like
做那件事，你知道就像
inundated with people and questions and
人山人海，问题纷至沓来，
people just wanted like just get like
人们只是想得到类似的东西
this one thing that they're trying to
他们正在努力做的这件事
figure out across the line and say like
弄清楚线对面的情况，然后说“就像
Stephen like how does how do I do this?
Stephen 问：“我该怎么做？”
And so that happens to me all the time
所以这种情况经常发生在我身上。
wherever I go and I've made it a habit
无论我去哪里，这都成了我的习惯。
of mine in the morning on the way to the
早上我去上班的路上
work to just like jump on the phone to
工作就是拿起电话
someone for half an hour. I do it almost
某人半小时。我几乎做到了
every day, four days out of five. And
每天，五天中有四天。和
I'll speak to some founder and give them
我会和一些创始人谈谈，然后告诉他们。
like 30 minutes of whatever it is that I
比如30分钟的不管是什么我
can. And so the podcast was honestly
能。所以，说实话，这个播客……
from the beginning about figuring out
从一开始就弄清楚
like how can I scale mentorship? How can
我该如何扩大导师制的规模？如何才能
you get to this place where all of these
你到达这个地方，所有这些
people that want to ask me questions can
想问我问题的人可以
actually get some answers from me? And
你能从我这里得到一些答案吗？和
you know the podcasting was not the
你知道播客并不是
first thing that came to my head. But
我脑海中浮现的第一个念头。但
the more I looked into it because I am a
我越深入了解，因为我是一个
huge podcast listener. I listen to so
我是个播客忠实听众。我听了这么多
many podcasts. But it's kind of
许多播客。但这有点……
interesting that for such a kind of
有趣的是，对于这种类型的
broad space there is kind of such a
那里有一片广阔的空间，有点像这样
narrow point of view in so many ways.
很多方面都缺乏客观视角。
There's so many men hosting podcasts.
现在有很多男性主持播客节目。
And when we start to think about
当我们开始思考……
business, it becomes even more
商业上，它变得更加……
male-dominated. And so in my head I was
男性主导。于是，我脑海里浮现出这样的画面：
like, well, I just have a very different
嗯，我的情况就完全不同。
point of view. I have very different
观点看法。我的情况截然不同。
experience. I have a very different, you
经验。我和你截然不同。
know, access. And what's been so
了解，获取。而过去究竟发生了什么？
interesting is all the people I called
有趣的是，我给所有人都打过电话。
up to do a podcast, they'd never done a
他们决定做播客，但之前从未做过。
podcast before. Really? Yeah. Everyone
播客之前。真的吗？是的。每个人
that I was like, "Hey, would you come
我当时就说：“嘿，你愿意来吗？”
on?" They were like, "I've never done
“开始吗？”他们说：“我从来没做过。”
this." And I was like, "Well, that's
“就是这样。” 我当时就想，“嗯，这……”
interesting." And immediately, even just
很有意思。”而且立刻，甚至只是
from that kind of casting point of view,
从这种选角角度来看，
I was like, "Oh, maybe I have a a
我当时想，“哦，也许我有一个……”
distinct point of view that could be
独特的观点，可能是
interesting here." But all I want to do
这里很有意思。”但我只想做
is very very simply is take what I've
非常简单，就是接受我拥有的
learned and take the people that I know
学会了，并且带上了我认识的人
and have it be impactful because I feel
并希望它能产生影响，因为我觉得
like everyone aspires to something.
就像每个人都有自己的追求一样。
Everybody wants to build the life of
每个人都想建立自己的生活
their dreams. And so I was really
他们的梦想。所以，我当时真的
thinking about this as something that
把这件事看作是……
maybe if I could facilitate
也许如果我能帮忙的话
conversations and tell people more about
对话并向人们讲述更多信息
the journey that I've been on and be
我所经历的旅程以及我
really thoughtful about what it takes,
认真思考过需要付出什么，
right? Because I just feel like again
正确的？因为我感觉又一次
in like the female like media landscape,
在类似女性主导的媒体环境中，
there's so much toxic positivity and I'm
这里充斥着太多有害的正能量，而我……
like babe, you're not going to be able
宝贝，你肯定做不到。
to manifest your way there. like I'll
用你的方式去实现它。就像我会
tell you the truth if you want to listen
如果你想听，我就告诉你实话。
and if you're willing to put the work in
如果你愿意付出努力的话
like all of these things could be, you
就像所有这些事情都可能是这样一样，你
know, applicable and, you know, you
知道，适用，而且，你知道，你
could have access. Um, and so that's
可能拥有访问权限。嗯，就是这样。
what I want to do. I want to just like
我想做的事。我只想喜欢
do things how I do them, be honest with
按照我的方式做事，要诚实。
people, bring in people that I know and
把人，带上我认识的人，
be honest about my journey. And I'm I'm
坦诚地讲述我的经历。而我，我
excited to do it. Like it's been I've
我很兴奋能做这件事。就像我一直那样
done a couple of episodes and I'm like
看了几集之后，我就觉得
just having a chat. I think of all the
只是闲聊。我想到了所有
things you've done in your life, I think
我认为，你一生中做过的事情。
the more and more that you find yourself
你越发发现自己
in the public eye,
在公众视野中，
um, and the more of the work that you do
嗯，而且你做的工作越多
on your podcast, Aspire. Um, I think
在你的播客节目《Aspire》中。嗯，我想
that is ultimately going to be
最终将会是
the greatest part of your legacy. And I
你留下的最伟大的遗产。我
say that
这么说
because there is nobody
因为没有人
else, able, and capable of occupying
否则，能够且有能力占据
that space that I can see. There is no
我能看到的那个空间。没有
one who comes from where you come from,
来自你家乡的人，
who has been on the journey that you've
谁走过你走过的路？
been on both in the UK and in the US,
曾在英国和美国都参加过。
that's climbed both mountains that is
已经攀登过这两座山峰的那个人
relatable even though that they're so
即使他们如此，也让人感同身受。
high up the mountain, that is had to
在山顶上，那是很困难的
contend with some of the things you've
应对你所遇到的一些事情
contended with, which many women and men
对此，许多妇女和男子都感到担忧。
contend with, which is like parenthood
应对这种情况，就像为人父母一样
and family, that is articulate, that is
还有家人，这很能表达，这很……
seasoned across a variety of different
经验丰富，涉猎广泛
environments and spaces, that is also a
环境和空间，这也是
black
黑色的
woman, there is nobody. And if you
女人，这里没有人。如果你
reflect on you as that young girl
回想一下你，那个年轻女孩
looking up at Oprah or me like looking
抬头看着奥普拉或者我，就像看着
up at Jamal Edwards, it was so
在贾马尔·爱德华兹那里，情况就是这样
important. Yeah. It was the it was the
重要的。是的。就是它就是
kernel of belief that stays in your mind
留在你脑海中的核心信念
that says if they can, there's no reason
也就是说，如果他们能做到，就没有理由不去做。
I can't. And I've said this to my team
我不能。我已经把这些话告诉了我的团队。
before a ton of times over the last
过去很多次
couple of months about you. I'm like,
关于你，我几个月前就开始关注你了。我当时就想，
there's no other Emma. So, she almost
世上没有第二个艾玛。所以，她几乎
has
有
a
一个
responsibility to that gap because
因为要对这个差距负责
you've done incredible things in your
你已经取得了令人难以置信的成就
life. You've done so much philanthropic
生活。你做了很多慈善工作
work which I'll I'll put all in the
我会把所有精力都投入到这项工作中。
description below um to help so many
下面描述是为了帮助很多人。
people. But it's not lost on me that
人们。但我并非没有意识到这一点
like the older I've gotten, just seeing
就像我年纪越大，就越觉得……
someone that you can that makes you
一个你可以让你……的人
realize that that brings down those like
意识到这会打击那些喜欢
limiting beliefs that you have or that
你所持有的或那些限制性的信念
society has has passed to you could go
社会已经过去，你可以走了
on to create a 100,000 Emma and that you
继续创造一个10万个艾玛，而你
it's hard to think of a more like
很难想到比这更像的了。
astonishing important legacy than than
比……更惊人的重要遗产
that. Like the 10 million Emma that you
那。就像你拥有的那1000万个艾玛一样
will create and so I'm so glad you're
将会创造，所以我很高兴你是
doing this because I've said to my team
这样做是因为我已经对我的团队说过。
a time like there's not there's not
就像没有时间一样，没有时间
another Emma. there's not someone else
另一个艾玛。没有其他人了。
that could occupy that position. So,
这个人可以胜任那个职位。所以，
it's so important that you're successful
你的成功至关重要。
in it and it's so important that you
在其中，这一点非常重要，你
continue to do it. So, so thank you for
继续这样做。所以，非常感谢。
that. That means so much. It's so true
那。这意义非凡。确实如此
though. I say it all the time behind
尽管。我总是在背后说。
your back. I'm like, there's not another
你的背部。我心想，没有别的了。
one. There's only Emma. So, she has to
一。只有艾玛一个人。所以她必须
not has to cuz it's not it's not an
不必，因为它不是，它不是一个
obligation, but it's a responsibility.
这是义务，也是责任。
It's a responsibility. I see as a
这是责任。我认为这是一个
responsibility. It's one that I'm taking
责任。这是我正在考虑的。
really seriously because I feel like
真的非常认真，因为我觉得
there is um there is an amazing
嗯，这里有一个惊人的
opportunity there. And if you take
那里有机会。如果你采取
anything seriously and you apply
认真对待任何事情，你都会申请
yourself and you think about like who
你自己，你会想，比如谁
are you here to serve, you know, and I
你来这里是为了服务他人吗？你知道，还有我
think about that every day. I told you
每天都想想这件事。我告诉你了
it's like I'm obsessed with customers.
我好像对顾客有点着迷了。
I'll be obsessed with listeners. And at
我会非常在意听众。而且
the end of the day, I just want to do
说到底，我只想做这件事。
something where it's like it's just
感觉就像……
about doing a good job. Right now, I'm
关于做好工作。我现在是
obsessed with like what is the content
痴迷于内容是什么
that you put out? How do you have a
你发布的那些？你如何拥有一个
conversation that's not currently being
目前没有进行的对话
had? And I feel like there are such
有？我觉得有这样的
incredible people like yourself that are
像您这样杰出的人
having beautiful conversations that are
进行美好的对话
actually moving us forward in ways. You
实际上在某些方面推动我们前进。你
know, it's like I, you know, I text you
你知道，就像我，你知道，我给你发短信一样
when you have an amazing episode. I'm
当你遇到精彩的一集时。我是
like, I love that episode. And I'm so
我超喜欢那一集。我真是太……
proud that, you know, you could be an
你会为自己能成为……而感到自豪。
like black guy from England who's doing
就像来自英国的黑人那样
these things, who's at the top of the
这些事情，谁处于顶端
charts. And I I look at that and I think
图表。我看了之后觉得
that's so important. And so for me, it's
这太重要了。所以对我来说，就是这样。
like it's interesting to think about how
思考这个问题很有意思。
this could be important for a certain
这对于某些人来说可能很重要。
group of people right now. It's going to
现在这里有一群人。它将
be important beyond what you'll ever see
其重要性远超你所能看到的。
or realize or understand or be able to
或意识到、理解或能够
measure. And hoping and we've and you
措施。并且希望，我们和你
know if you know that if that's
你知道你是否知道如果那是
15year-old Emma there had seen this Emma
15岁的艾玛在那里见过这个艾玛
what that would have meant to her. Yeah.
那对她来说意味着什么。是的。
You know what that would have meant
你知道那意味着什么
quite a lot. Exactly. We have a closing
相当多。确切地。我们即将结束
tradition here Emma where the last guest
艾玛的传统是，最后一位客人是在这里度过的。
leaves a question for the next guest not
给下一位客人留下一个问题，不是吗？
knowing who they're leaving it for.
知道他们要把房子留给谁。
And the question that's been
而这个问题一直是……
left
左边
is what about you is better or has
你身上有哪些方面更好或更有优势？
vastly
非常
improved because of the
由于以下原因而得到改善：
person who loves you the
爱你的人
most? Who loves you the most? Well, Yens
最多？谁最爱你？嗯，日元
loves me the most, doesn't he? More than
他最爱我，对吗？多于
more than my mom. More than my lovely
比我妈妈还多。比我亲爱的还要多
mom. You know, I would say whether it
妈妈。你知道，我会说是否
was my mom or it was Yen's, you know,
是我妈妈还是 Yen 的，你知道的。
when you
当你
are when you're so loved, you know, and
就是那种被深深爱着的感觉，你知道吗？
I feel like someone who is so loved, you
我觉得自己像个被爱包围的人，你
know, my sisters love me, my kids love
你知道吗，我的姐妹们爱我，我的孩子们也爱我
me, my mom really loves me, Yens loves
我，我妈妈真的很爱我，燕子也爱我
me. You have like such
我。你就像这样
capacity, right? And that's what I
容量，对吧？这就是我
always feel, you know, when when I think
总觉得，你知道，每当我想到……
about what it is that kind of like keeps
关于它究竟是什么，就像是保持某种联系一样。
me going and gets me up. I have such a
我走了，然后我起床了。我有一个这样的
huge capacity
巨大容量
for more. I have such a like huge
更多内容。我非常喜欢
capacity to give, to put the work in, to
付出能力，投入工作的能力
receive, to make things better. And I
接受，让事情变得更好。我
honestly think that that is what's
真心认为就是这样。
happened to me that I've like my
我遇到过这种情况，我喜欢我的
ability has just grown so much and
能力提升如此之大，
continues and my capacity just keeps
持续进行，我的容量也一直保持着
growing. And it's a really interesting
生长。这真是一件很有趣的事
thing as you get older to see that like
随着年龄增长，你会逐渐明白这一点。
happen within you, you know, because you
你知道，这一切都发生在你内心深处，因为你
we always talk about like having insane
我们总是谈论像疯了一样的事情
energy in our 20s and then, you know,
我们在二十多岁时精力充沛，然后，你知道的，
it's like I'm 42 now and I think I have
感觉我现在好像42岁了，而且我觉得我已经……
more capacity for learning, for giving,
更强的学习能力和奉献精神
for being, you know, open to new things
因为他乐于接受新事物
than I've ever had in my life. And I
比我一生中经历过的任何时候都要多。我
think that that is because I'm really
我觉得那是因为我真的
loved. And it's so interesting. I don't
喜爱。真是太有趣了。我不
think it's about what I've achieved. I
我认为这关乎我取得的成就。我
don't think it's about anything else. I
别以为是别的事。我
think that I know I feel so safe and so
我想我知道自己感到非常安全，而且
secure and so seen that I can do
安全可靠，因此我可以看到我可以这样做。
anything because even the biggest
任何事，因为即使是最大的
mistakes like these people would they'll
像这些人一样犯错，他们会……
always love me like it's totally fine
永远像一切都没问题一样爱我
whatever I do. So it's like I would say
无论我做什么。所以就像我会说的那样
that that's a beautiful thing. Emma,
那真是一件美好的事。艾玛，
thank you so much. Thank you darling.
太感谢了。谢谢亲爱的。
I'm a huge fan of yours in every way and
我各方面都是你的超级粉丝，
um you're like a big sister to me and I
嗯，你就像我的大姐姐一样，而我
really appreciate our relationship and
非常珍惜我们之间的关系
long may it continue. Oh, I hope so. I'm
但愿它能一直持续下去。哦，但愿如此。我是
so I'm so proud of you. I really am. I
所以我为你感到非常骄傲。我确实是。我
look at everything you're doing and I'm
看看你做的一切，而我……
so happy that you're here in America
真高兴你来美国了。
about to take it over. Come on, babes.
即将接管。来吧，宝贝们。
No pressure.
别有压力。
This has always blown my mind a little
这件事一直让我有点难以置信。
bit. 53% of you that listen to this show
少量。 53% 的听众收听了这个节目
regularly haven't yet subscribe to the
经常还没有订阅
show. So, could I ask you for a favor?
展示。那么，我能请你帮个忙吗？
If you like the show and you like what
如果你喜欢这个节目，并且喜欢什么
we do here and you want to support us,
我们在这里确实这样做了，而你们也想支持我们。
the free simple way that you can do just
你可以用这种免费又简单的方法做到这一点
that is by hitting the subscribe button.
也就是点击订阅按钮。
And my commitment to you is if you do
我对你的承诺是，如果你这样做
that, then I'll do everything in my
那样的话，我就会做我的一切。
power, me and my team, to make sure that
我和我的团队拥有权力，以确保
this show is better for you every single
这个节目对你来说更好！
week. We'll listen to your feedback.
星期。我们会认真听取您的反馈意见。
We'll find the guests that you want me
我们会找到你想要的客人。
to speak to and we'll continue to do
我们会与他们沟通，并继续这样做。
what we do. Thank you so
我们做什么。非常感谢
[Music]
[音乐]
much. Heat. Heat. N.
很多。热。热。 N.